<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<opml version="1.0">
  <!--Generated by FeedDigger-->
  <head>
    <title>
      grep last 15 minutes 201310030714
    </title>
    <dateCreated>
      2013-10-03 07:14:30.049712
    </dateCreated>
    <dateModified>
      2013-10-03 07:14:30.049712
    </dateModified>
  </head>
  <body>
    <item>
      <title>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Verge -  All Posts
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4791934/snapchats-next-big-thing-stories-that-dont-just-disappear
      </link>
      <author>
        Ellis Hamburger
      </author>
      <content>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 19 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Apps Exclusive Report Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear The app that introduced ephemeral messages sets its sights on Facebook By Ellis Hamburger on October 3, 2013 03:00 am @hamburger 1 Comments Jump To up Top Comments down Close Snapchat CEO Evan Spiegel's hands are shaking as he points to his iPhone. He's unmistakably nervous, and not in a sweaty, early-Mark Zuckerberg kind of way. There must be a lot on his mind as the young CEO of a company bounding toward a $1 billion valuation — a company that has changed the course of being a teenager in the year 2013. Spiegel brushes off Snapchat’s latest bragging right: the service sees 350 million snaps sent per day. He seems anxious, as if he's about to interview for a job or deliver a commencement speech to his graduating class. Instead, he tells me about Stories, his team’s latest invention : a rolling compilation of snaps from the last 24 hours that your friends can see. You create your Story as you go about your day by tapping &quot;My Story&quot; above the friends you want to send a snap to. Or, you can tap a new shortcut button in the app's camera screen to instantly post a snap to your Story. But unlike conventional snaps, Stories don't disappear in a puff of ephemeral smoke after you've watched them. You can watch a friend’s (or your own) Story over and over. Each Story is the sum of all the snaps you’ve added over the last 24 hours, which means its size is always fluctuating. What doesn’t change is that every piece of the Story is less than a day old, so viewing one might be the fastest way to see what a friend's been up to. Snapchat may not look much like Facebook, but with Stories, the company is taking its first steps toward competing with Facebook’s most important product: News Feed. Behind Stories is a deep understanding, or perhaps loathing, of the way social apps work today. Spiegel claims to have no special knowledge of the way we work as social organisms aside from what he learned as a college student, but has thus far proven himself and his colleagues to be surprisingly thoughtful about our hidden social behaviors and desires. Stories is the next big piece of how Snapchat thinks social media should work, and everybody’s watching. No wonder Spiegel’s a little nervous. Stories, one of Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s most visible feature additions in its two-year lifespan, was first conceived as a way to address perhaps the most common request from users: a way to send a snap to your entire friends list. Spiegel and his team thought that a &quot;Send All&quot; button could destroy Snapchat, and instead sought a more passive means of sharing an image or video with everyone you know. Over the next year they built Stories, which live inside Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s &quot;My Friends&quot; page &amp;mdash; one of just four screens in the entire app. The final result recalls the early days of Facebook, where the quickest way to catch up with a friend was to visit their profile. Each person in your friend list is now flanked by a circular thumbnail of the most recent moment in their daily Story. Holding your finger on a friend&amp;rsquo;s name starts a stream of every snap they&amp;rsquo;ve shared to their Story within the last 24 hours. &quot;When you have a minute in your day and are curious about what your friends are up to, you can jump into their experience,&quot; says Spiegel. If you&amp;rsquo;re bored, you can skip ahead by tapping with a second finger. Unlike most forms of social media updates, Spiegel stresses, Stories play back in the order they occurred, and not in reverse chronological order. There&amp;rsquo;s also no algorithm to decide which stories are more important than others. &quot;The last snap today will also be the beginning of tomorrow,&quot; says Spiegel, &quot;so there&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Without naming any rivals, Spiegel digs at the Facebooks, Twitters, and Pinterests of the world that implicitly ask you to build an identity online. &quot;There's this weird thing that happens when you contribute something to a static profile,&quot; he says. &quot;You have to worry about how this new content fits in with your online persona that&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be you . It's uncomfortable and unfortunate.&quot; He seems to say that when Facebook released Timeline , a simple way to pore through years of updates and photos, it inadvertently cursed itself. By providing users with an enormous degree of transparency into their posts, Facebook may have also given its users anxiety about posting new content. Stories operates on the opposite principle. By providing users with fleeting, pocket-sized &quot;live profiles&quot; that last at most 24 hours, Spiegel hopes that users will feel free to act more like their true selves. He cites the practice of &quot;white-walling&quot; as evidence: where social media users on Facebook or Twitter post updates, only to delete the posts a short time later. The term was coined by one of Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s role models, researcher danah boyd , who describes it as a &quot;Risk Reduction Strategy&quot; on sites like Facebook. &quot;The internet is a timeless void &amp;mdash; you put something in there and it's there forever and loses a lot of context,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;There&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Snapchat actually has its own sociology researcher on staff, Nathan Jurgenson, made famous for &quot;The IRL Fetish,&quot; an essay on the augmented reality of our digital lives. &quot;He invented a concept called &amp;lsquo;digital dualism&amp;rsquo; &amp;mdash; something our company is fascinated by,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;It&amp;rsquo;s the notion that people conceptualize the world into online and offline, which makes for a lot of very awkward experiences.&quot; Spiegel doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly say that Snapchat is meant to emulate our real-life relationships, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t shy about saying that his app is doing a better job at it than competitors. &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out,&quot; he says. &quot;We believe that the next generation of powerful mobile companies have a deep understanding of the world as a unified whole,&quot; Spiegel argues, with the kind of hubristic, starry-eyed optimism only possible in the insular world of startups, &quot;where digital and analog experiences affect each other, rather than transporting analog experiences into the digital realm.&quot; &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out.&quot; Spiegel won&amp;rsquo;t comment on Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s plans to monetize its business, but there&amp;rsquo;s potential in Stories. Imagine a future where Miley Cyrus opens her Story to everyone (since the app allows two settings for who can see your Stories: friends or everyone). At any point in the day, you could check on what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to &amp;mdash; which would provide plenty of opportunities for advertising or brand placement. Spiegel smiles when I suggest the &quot;follow a celebrity&amp;rsquo;s story&quot; idea &amp;mdash; which is already entirely possible with the latest version of Snapchat &amp;mdash; but affirms his pledge to keep any kind of grown-up business ideas out of the app for now. &quot;We don't have Biz Dev boots on the ground trying to make it happen,&quot; Spiegel says, but he won&amp;rsquo;t rule it out either. &quot;We want to find ways to support artists who don't have a lot of reach.&quot; Three such artists will greet Snapchatters worldwide this morning when they open up the app, in three custom videos meant to introduce Stories to users. Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s final pitch is to narrate a day in his own life that seems almost too good to be true. &quot;I spoke at a TechCrunch thing a little while ago,&quot; he says. &quot;I took snaps of me being nervous, and of lots of people, and when I got lunch, and when I met with friend of mine, and then when we announced we do 350 million snaps per day.&quot; Snapchat employees, even though they were busy working out of the company&amp;rsquo;s beachfront office, got a glimpse into each of these moments as Spiegel went about his day, since they had access to his Story. &quot;And at midnight,&quot; he says, &quot;I was with friends at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, and when I ordered I looked down at my receipt and it was number 350.&quot; A new kind of digital communication &quot;It was a great narrative that I could've never captured ... in any other form of content,&quot; he says. &quot;You never know what's gonna happen until it happens.&quot; Spiegel takes a deep breath, leaning forward as if to hear the results of an exam he has just taken. The year of work and high-concept thinking behind Stories may just be &quot;a feature&quot; to his users &amp;mdash; but for Spiegel, it's obviously a lot more than that. Snapchat surprised the world and pushed aside myriad competitors, including Facebook itself . For the 23-year-old Spiegel, the story of Snapchat isn't about a clever and fun app for messaging, but about building a new kind of digital communication where our statuses, chats, photos, and videos don&amp;rsquo;t have to last forever. &quot;Ephemeral messaging&quot; was just the beginning. Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:00:04
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Investment Adviser and Entrepreneur
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        AllThingsD
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://allthingsd.com/20131002/investment-adviser-and-entrepreneur/
      </link>
      <author>
        Voices
      </author>
      <content>
        Ross Ulbricht's Economic Theories - Voices - Voices - AllThingsD WSJ WSJ WSJ Live WSJ Live MarketWatch MarketWatch Barron's Barron's Portfolio Portfolio Product X Product X rt f r&amp;amp;c pe&amp;amp;vc wsj b More All Things Digital WSJ Briefcase BigCharts Financial News Professor Journal SmartMoney Student Journal Virtual Stock Exchange WSJ Classifieds WSJ Classroom WSJ Radio WSJ Wine AllThingsD News Reviews Mobile Media Social Enterprise Commerce Voices Conferences Video Follow Us View by Writer Walt Mossberg &amp;#8211; New Spin on Video Chats Brings More to the Party Voices bio e-mail RSS Recent Posts by Voices Investment Adviser and Entrepreneur October 2, 2013 at 11:59 pm PT Tweet Share Print I want to use economic theory as a means to abolish the use of coercion and agression [sic] amongst mankind&amp;#8230; To that end, I am creating an economic simulation to give people a first-hand experience of what it would be like to live in a world without the systemic use of force. &amp;#8211; From the LinkedIn profile summary of Ross Ulbricht , who was arrested Tuesday as the alleged Silk Road mastermind &amp;#8220;Dread Pirate Roberts&amp;#8221; Tagged with: economic theory, LinkedIn , Ross Ulbricht Powered by Livefyre Must-Reads from other Websites How Google Taught Itself Good Design Farhad Manjoo, Tech Reporter, The Wall Street Journal, in Fast Company Opinion: What the Future of Sports Games Should Look Like Steve McPherson, Contributor, Polygon Shareholder’s Best Interests Ben Horowitz, Partner, Andreessen Horowitz What Inner City Kids Know About Social Media, and Why We Should Listen Jacqui Cheng, Editor, Ars Technica Is Login Data the New Gold? Jack Marshall, Writer, Digiday Quora’s Search for What the Internet Doesn’t Know Tom Simonite, Editor, MIT Technology Review About Must-Reads &amp;raquo; More Inside &amp;raquo; About Voices Along with original content and posts from across the Dow Jones network, this section of AllThingsD includes Must-Reads From Other Websites &amp;#8212; pieces we&amp;#8217;ve read, discussions we&amp;#8217;ve followed, stuff we like. Six posts from external sites are included here each weekday, but we only run the headlines. We link to the original sites for the rest. These posts are explicitly labeled, so it&amp;#8217;s clear that the content comes from other websites, and for clarity&amp;#8217;s sake, all outside posts run against a pink background. We also solicit original full-length posts and accept some unsolicited submissions. Voices is edited by Beth Callaghan. Featured Posts Featured Reviews BlackBerry&amp;#8217;s Latest Filing Paints Grimmest Picture Yet of Company&amp;#8217;s Business Ina Fried in Mobile New Spin on Video Chats Brings More to the Party Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology Kevin Rose Is AngelList&amp;#8217;s Million-Dollar Man Liz Gannes in News View all today&amp;#8217;s news &amp;raquo; Help Wanted: Moonlighters for Mobile Apps Katherine Boehret in The Digital Solution Surface Pro: Hefty Tablet Is a Laptop Lightweight Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology NFC: What You Need to Know Lauren Goode in Product Reviews A Wristwatch Tells When Phone Calls, Emails Arrive Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology How Apple Gets All the Good Apps Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology View all reviews &amp;raquo; AllThingsD by Writer Walt Mossberg Kara Swisher John Paczkowski Katherine Boehret Peter Kafka Ina Fried Liz Gannes Arik Hesseldahl Lauren Goode Mike Isaac Bonnie Cha Jason Del Rey AllThingsD.com is a Web site devoted to news, analysis and opinion on technology, the Internet and media. But it is different from other sites in this space. It is a fusion of different media styles, different topics, different formats and different sources. Read more &amp;raquo; About Us &amp;raquo; Contact Us &amp;raquo; Comments Policy &amp;raquo; Cookies Policy &amp;raquo; Privacy Policy - UPDATED 10/18/2011 &amp;raquo; FAQ &amp;raquo; Terms of Service &amp;raquo; Your Ad Choices &amp;raquo; Advertise With Us &amp;raquo; Send a Tip &amp;raquo; Daily Headlines Email &amp;raquo; Follow AllThingsD Your Way &amp;raquo; Featuring the most influential figures in technology, unscripted and upfront. More &amp;raquo; Conferences: D: All Things Digital. &amp;raquo; D: Dive Into Media &amp;raquo; D: Dive Into Mobile &amp;raquo; Follow us on Twitter: Select Account @allthingsd (All Things Digital) @ATDapple (Apple) @ATDgoogle (Google) @ATDmedia (Media) @ATDmobile (Mobile) @ATDreviews (Reviews) @waltmossberg (Walt Mossberg) @karaswisher (Kara Swisher) @JohnPaczkowski (John Paczkowski) @kabster728 (Katherine Boehret) @pkafka (Peter Kafka) @inafried (Ina Fried) @LizGannes (Liz Gannes) @ahess247 (Arik Hesseldahl) @LaurenGoode (Lauren Goode) @MikeIsaac (Mike Isaac) @BonnieSCha (Bonnie Cha) @DelRey (Jason Del Rey) RSS Feeds Select Feed All Feeds News Reviews Mobile Media Social Enterprise Commerce Voices Personal Technology Mossberg&amp;#8217;s Mailbox The Digital Solution Walt Mossberg Kara Swisher John Paczkowski Katherine Boehret Peter Kafka Ina Fried Liz Gannes Arik Hesseldahl Lauren Goode Mike Isaac Bonnie Cha Jason Del Rey &amp;copy; 2005-2013 Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company Inc. All Rights Reserved. Powered by WordPress.com VIP Mobile Version
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:59:35
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Technology news, comment and analysis | theguardian.com
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.theguardian.com/c/34708/f/663871/s/31ff5f48/sc/21/l/0L0Stheguardian0N0Ctechnology0C20A130Coct0C0A30Calgorithims0Egoogle0Einternet0Esearch0Esecurity0Eonlin/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        Alex Hern
      </author>
      <content>
        From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech | Technology | theguardian.com Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to comments [c] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life &amp;amp; style Data News Technology Programming From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech Algorithms such as those run by Google are the brains of the internet, encrypting data and helping us navigate online Share Tweet this Email Alex Hern theguardian.com , Thursday 3 October 2013 03.05 EDT Jump to comments ( &amp;hellip; ) Algorithms power music discovery, encrypt our personal information and help us navigate through online worlds. Photograph: Google Algorithms, simple functions that hover between mathematical problems and computer programs, are everywhere. Whether dealing with lost packets when using Wi-Fi, or getting your credit-card details securely to an online store, most consumer technology couldn't work without some ingenious solutions to common problems. And when Google decides to change its search algorithm - as it did with Hummingbird last week, it can make or break whole companies . Here are just five which you couldn't live without. Pagerank &amp;ndash; how Google calculates search results The broad strokes of how Google's search algorithm works have been public for over fifteen years, though the exact way it organises search results remains the company's most closely guarded secret. PageRank is the system at the heart of it all, and the key invention behind Google's rapid dominance of internet search. Ten years ago, when competitors relied on human-maintained indexes of webpages, it allowed the company to assess the value of websites automatically - a massive advantage as the web grew exponentially. The algorithm works by looking at every link to and from every page on the internet. A link to a page is, in effect, a vote for that page's validity, because it means that someone thought that whatever was on that page was worth sharing. So the more inbound links a page has, the higher its PageRank is. But then it adds a second measure: links from pages which have a high PageRank themselves confer a higher PageRank. So being linked to by Stanford , the Google creators' alma mater, is significantly more valuable than being linked to by Stanford's , the map shop. On top of PageRank are myriad tweaks and adjustments to improve the results further. Some of those, such as the decision to punish 'link farms', vast networks of sites which link to each other in an effort to boost their PageRank , are directly connected to the core algorithm. Others, like the company's attempts to leverage what it knows about users based on their previous searches to deliver personalised results, were bolted on later. But as the demands we make of search have got ever more intensive, the company has been forced to adapt. The most recent update to the algorithm, Hummingbird is &quot;a new engine built on both existing and new parts&quot;, according to Danny Sullivan of the search blog Search Engine Land . Hummingbird was built to deal with the fact that increasing familiarity with search, as well as the rise of voice control , mean that we now ask Google actual questions, rather than just typing in relevant words. In the future, new problems will require further tweaks, but the position of PageRank at the heart of it all seems secure. Two Enigma machines at the London Science Museum. Photograph: DAVID HOLT/flickr Public key cryptography - keeping credit card data secure Public key cryptography is the name for a broad collection of algorithms which lie at the heart of nearly every form of security online. Using what is perhaps best described as 'magic maths ', public key cryptography lets people encode data with a key which cannot then decode it. If Alice has a piece of information which she needs to get to Bob without anyone else seeing it &amp;ndash; maybe a credit card number which she's using to buy a computer with, or perhaps evidence of state wrongdoing which she's leaking to a national newspaper &amp;ndash; she has to encrypt it. Way back in history, the only way to do this would be to use a shared secret: a cipher which both Alice and Bob know, but no-one else does. That's how encryption all the way up to the second world war worked. But the obvious problem is that Alice and Bob can't use open channels to agree on their cipher. That's fine if they can meet in person to swap codes, but less effective if Alice is a consumer and Bob a multinational corporation. Public key cryptography means that Bob can tell the world his public key, and let them know that anything encoded with that will be readable by him and only him. Alice sees the public key, locks up her credit card data using it, and then sends that packet on the way. Only Bob, using a second, private, key can decrypt the data and read the number. Unfortunately, doing all of this every time is pretty hard on a computer's processor, so another step, where both Alice and Bob use their keys together to generate a shared secret, is frequently added in most practical uses of public key encryption. That shared secret can then be used in old-fashioned symmetrical ciphers. But it all comes back to the public and private keys. Correcting errors CDs are temperamental beasts. When they were introduced, they were hailed as being a resilient replacement for vinyl and cassettes, but as anyone who has tried to play a carelessly preserved album found in their car's glovebox can attest to, that's only half true. Still, it could a lot worse. When you're storing data using microscopic pits on a sheet of metal covered with a thin layer of plastic, it's quite a feat to read every single pit correctly, a feat only compounded by later generations of optical media, which shrink the pits still further. Playback. Photograph: Stockdisc/Getty Images Error correction lies at the heart of that reliability, thanks to the use of a cunning algorithm which lets CDs be readable even with quite a lot of damage to the data stored on them. In hugely simplified form, imagine the data on a CD as a grid of 1s and 0s. Like this: 101 010 000 If there's an error reading the CD, one of those 0s may turn into a 1. Without error correction, there's no way to tell if that's happened, and no way to fix it. The simplest way to correct errors is to add another load of data. Each row and column is counted up, and if there's an even number of 1s, another 1 is added on the end. If there isn't, a 0 is added instead: 101 1 010 0 000 1 000 Now, if one of the 0s is misread, the player can check with the error correction codes, and tell that there's been a mistake &amp;ndash; and even, assuming there's not too much damage, what the real value should be. Suppose the bottom right 0 is read as a 1: by reading the error correction code for that row, the player can tell that there's one too many 1s. It can then cross-check with the error correction codes for each column, and spot that there are also too many 1s in one column as well. Now the player knows where the error is, and can carry on with those sweet tunes. Error correction isn't just used by disc drives, though. Nearly every electronic device which gets data from one place to another will have some error correction on it, from WiFi to DSL. Even ISBN numbers on the back of books have error correction: the final digit serves the role. Protecting passwords Sometimes, it's really important to check that the file you have been given is exactly the one you expected. Maybe you are worried it's been tampered with, or just want to check that a large download finished without corruption. One way to do that is to look at its hash. There isn't really one algorithm which can be used to make 'hashes' of data: any process which can take information and spit out something which fulfils a few criteria will do. A good cryptographic hash function will give the same output every time it's given the same input; the hash will change if the message changes; it would be nearly impossible to work backwards from the hash to the message; and it would be nearly impossible for two messages to have the same hashes. Logging in. Photograph: Jan Miks/Alamy But there's a much more important use for hashing data than just checking files: password protection. As is painfully obvious these days, not many organisations can guarantee they won't lose your data . That's particularly problematic if it's your password they've lost, because &amp;mdash; well, you don't have a different password for every service, do you ? These days, companies shouldn't be keeping passwords in plaintext at all. Instead, when a user types in their password for the first time, the site should hash the password, and only keep that. Every time they come back to log in, it can take another hash, and compare it to the one on file. If they match, the password's correct. But now, if the site's hacked, the only thing which gets lost is a table full of hashes which can't be reverse engineered into passwords, so everyone is happy. (Technically, site owners should be salting their hashes - an oh-so-cute term which means adding a little bit of extra data into the password hash to prevent it being reverse engineered .) Perlin noise: generating landscapes in games Games are just big bags of algorithms. There's art, music, writing, direction, design and playtesting too, but a lot of algorithms. Take procedurally generated terrain, the favoured way of filling in the vast expanses of games like Minecraft or Dwarf Fortress. It's not enough just to generate random noise, and apply it to a landscape, because if you do, you end up with something which is too random: all noise, no pattern. Instead, you want terrain which demonstrates the same fractal nature as the real world, with mountains, hills, boulders and pebbles all having effects on different scales. That's what Perlin noise can do. It's a simple enough algorithm: generate some random noise at a load of different frequencies, smooth it out, and then add them together . But when you do, you go from this: Random noise. Photograph: /http:/freespace.virgin.net/hugo.elias/models/m_perlin.htm To this: Perlin noise Photograph: /http:/freespace.virgin.net/hugo.elias/models/m_perlin.htm Or consider trying to get enemies to take an intelligent route through a map. The obvious way to do it is easy enough: consider every possible route, then take the shortest one from A to B. But that's so computationally intensive that it's unusable in most situations. Instead algorithms like the A* search can be used. How it works is tricky to explain (essentially, it finds a path by always taking the step where the number of steps already taken plus the number of steps in a straight line to the destination is lowest), but it is entrancing in action . &amp;bull; In August 2011, a rogue algorithm lost its owners $440m on the stock market before it was eventually shut down . Sign up for the Guardian Today Our editors' picks for the day's top news and commentary delivered to your inbox each morning. Sign up for the daily email Print this Share Contact us Send to a friend Sender&amp;#39;s name Recipient's email address Your IP address will be logged Share Short link for this page: http://gu.com/p/3j6mf StumbleUpon reddit Tumblr Digg LinkedIn Google Bookmarks del.icio.us livejournal Facebook Twitter Contact us Contact the Technology editor tech@theguardian.com Report errors or inaccuracies: userhelp@theguardian.com Letters for publication should be sent to: letters@theguardian.com If you need help using the site: userhelp@theguardian.com Call the main Guardian and Observer switchboard: +44 (0)20 3353 2000 Advertising guide License/buy our content Technology Programming &amp;middot; Search engines &amp;middot; Internet &amp;middot; Data and computer security &amp;middot; Google &amp;middot; Games Search World news Privacy More blogposts Share Tweet this Email Comments Click here to join the discussion . We can't load the discussion on theguardian.com because you don't have JavaScript enabled . Today's best video Tiger cub born at London Zoo The moment a tiger gives birth to London Zoo's first tiger cub in 17 years is captured by hidden cameras Does the future belong to the Tories? John Harris reports from the Conservative party conference Plane's emergency landing on Florida road A pilot is forced to land his plane on a road Mesut Özil lauded by Arsène Wenger Arsenal manager praises midfielder after 2-0 Champions League win over Napoli Technology Programming &amp;middot; Search engines &amp;middot; Internet &amp;middot; Data and computer security &amp;middot; Google &amp;middot; Games Search World news Privacy More blogposts On the Guardian today World news 'Revenge porn' outlawed in California Technology GTA V Online launches, popularity could cause server issues Technology Rockstar says sorry for Grand Theft Auto Online launch problems Film Mia Farrow: Woody Allen's son Ronan may be Frank Sinatra's World news US shutdown: fruitless talks leave bitter stalemate in place Technology FBI claims largest Bitcoin seizure after arrest of alleged Silk Road founder Sponsored feature Key topics Apple Google Facebook Games blog Game reviews License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US advertising | A - Z index | About us &amp;#169; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) ;
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:05:30
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Register
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://go.theregister.com/feed/www.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/so_i_wouldnt_start_from_here/
      </link>
      <author>
        StorageBod
      </author>
      <content>
        How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy • The Register Skip to content Whitepapers | The Channel Data Center Software Networks Security Policy Business Jobs Hardware Science Bootnotes Columnists Forums Servers HPC Cloud Storage Data Networking Virtualisation BOFH Data Center &gt; Storage How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy Architecture might all look samey, but it's like that for a reason By StorageBod , 3rd October 2013 Post a comment Related stories Storagebod When the SSD came to storage land: How flashy upstarts got their break 5 years in storage: Flash mutants, big data and (WTF is) the cloud Storagebod Those vendor blog sods fog the cogs. Wish they'd slog for user bods Storagebod Storage rage: Like getting a nice steak and being told to only eat 80% of it Supercharge your infrastructure Storagebod We’ve had a few announcements from vendors recently and I've seen all manner of storage roadmaps. If I had one comment to make on all of these, it would be to say that if I were to design an array or a storage product, I probably wouldn’t start from where most of these guys are starting. There appears to be a real fixation on the past, with lots of architectures which are simply re-inventing what has gone before. And although I understand why, I don’t understand why. Stick with me here. Let’s take the legacy vendors. You can’t change things because you will break everything: you will break the existing customer scripts and legacy automation, you will break processes and understanding. So essentially, the vendor can’t build a new architecture because it breaks everything. I get the argument, but I don’t necessarily agree with the result. And then we have the new kids on the block, which want to continue building yesterday’s architecture today. “We’ll build something based on a dual-head filer,” they say, “because everyone knows how to do that and they understand the architecture.” Yet again: I get the argument but I really don’t agree with the result. I’m going to take the new vendors' situation first. If I wished to buy a dual-head filer, I’d probably buy it from one of the leaders of the pack. Certainly if I were a big storage customer, it would be very hard for one of the new vendors get it down to a price that is attractive. Now, you may argue that your new kit is so much better than the legacy vendors that it is worth the extra hassle, but you will almost certainly break my automation and existing processes. Is it really worth that level of disruption? The first situation with the legacy vendors is more interesting. Can I take the new product and make it feel like the old stuff from a management point of view? If storage is truly software (and the management layer is certainly software), I don’t see that it should be beyond the wit of developers to make your new architecture feel like the old stuff. Okay, you might strip out some of the old legacy constructs. You might even fake them ... so if a script creates a LUN utilising a legacy construct, you just fake the responses. There are some more interesting issues around performance and monitoring, but as a whole, the industry is so very poor at it. Breaking this is not such a major issue. Capacity planning and management: well, how many people really do this? The really big customers likely do it, but they might well be the ones who will look at leveraging new technology without a translation layer. So if I were a vendor, I would be looking at ways to make my storage “plug-compatible” with what has gone before – but under the covers, so to speak. I’d be looking for ways to do it a whole lot better and I wouldn’t be afraid to upset some of my legacy engineering teams. I’d build a platform on top of which I could stick &quot;personalities&quot;. And it’s not just about a common look and feel for the GUI, I'd engineer the same for the CLI and the APIs. My advice to the new kids: make the change easy by reducing the friction. ® 5 ways to prepare your advertising infrastructure for disaster Post a comment Previous Story Whitepapers Microsoft’s Cloud OS System Center Virtual Machine manager and how this product allows the level of virtualization abstraction to move from individual physical computers and clusters to unifying the whole Data Centre as an abstraction layer. 5 ways to prepare your advertising infrastructure for disaster Being prepared allows your brand to greatly improve your advertising infrastructure performance and reliability that, in the end, will boost confidence in your brand. Supercharge your infrastructure Fusion­‐io has developed a shared storage solution that provides new performance management capabilities required to maximize flash utilization. High Performance for All While HPC is not new, it has traditionally been seen as a specialist area – is it now geared up to meet more mainstream requirements? Avere FXT with FlashMove and FlashMirror This ESG Lab validation report documents hands-on testing of the Avere FXT Series Edge Filer with the AOS 3.0 operating environment. Search more Resources More from The Register Multipath TCP: Siri's new toy isn't a game-changer This experiment is an alpha and carriers could swat it like a bug 68 Ellison ditches own cloud keynote for billionaires' America's Cup boat race Mass exodus after King Database snubs attendees 42 Barmy Army to get Wi-Fi to the seat for cricket's Ashes Sydney Test Match will offer replays to the smartmobe 14 How many apps does it take to back up your data? Trevor Pott counts the ways 28 Dedupe-dedupe, dedupe-dedupe-dedupe: Flashy clients crowd around Permabit diamond 3 of the top six flash vendors are casing the OEM dedupe tech, claims analyst 8 Seagate to storage bods: You CAN touch this (at last). Stop, HAMR time We've talked about it for a while... next month, you'll actually *see* it 15 Disk-pushers, get reel: Even GOOGLE relies on tape Prepare to be beaten by your old, cheap rival 13 French data cops to Google: RIGHT, you had your chance. PUNISHMENT time Prepare yourself for fines, snarls CNIL 63 Dragons' Den star's biz Outsourcery sends yet more millions up in smoke Telly moneybags went into the cloud and still nobody's making any profit 15 Hong Kong's data centres stay high and dry amid Typhoon Usagi 180 km/h winds kill 25 in China, but the data centres keep humming 9 Most read TUPPERWARE FOUND ON MOON of Saturn Microsoft investors push for Bill Gates defenestration: report GTA V Online hits speed bumps: Short delay before you can rough up that hooker 500 MEELLION PCs still run Windows XP. How did we get here? Review Ubuntu 13.10: Meet the Linux distro with a bizarre Britney Spears fixation Spotlight How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy Oracle muscles way into seat atop the benchmark with hefty ZFS filer How many apps does it take to back up your data? 28 Five reasons why you'll take your storage to the cloud 25 Tracking the history of magnetic tape: A game of noughts and crosses 28 Just how flash is your enterprise storage rig? 11 Gorillas, StorageBeers, sexy flash models: It's all here in Speaking in Tech Got it taped: The business of tape-based disaster recovery 10 Cloud storage: Is the convenience worth the extra expense? 16 Is storage kicking servers in the battle of the bundles? Storage rage: Like getting a nice steak and being told to only eat 80% of it 54 Object storage: The blob creeping from niche to mainstream 12 MORE More from the Register Send us News Tips Week’s Headlines Reg Archive Top 20 Stories eBooks Webcasts The Channel Privacy Advertise with Us Company Info © Copyright 1998–2013
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:02:48
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://news.yahoo.com/calif-man-charged-black-market-drug-scheme-060819404--finance.html
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme - Yahoo News Home Mail News Sports Finance Weather Games Groups Answers Screen Flickr More omg! Shine Movies Music TV Health Shopping Travel Autos Homes Mobile Yahoo News Search News Search Web Sign In Mail Go to Mail.&quot; data-nosubject=&quot;[No Subject]&quot; data-timestamp='short'&gt; Help Account Info Help Suggestions Yahoo News Home U.S. World Politics Tech Science Health Odd News Opinion Local Dear Abby Comics ABC News Yahoo Originals Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme Content preferences Done PAUL ELIAS 12 minutes ago SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — FBI agents found him in the science fiction section of a small branch of the San Francisco public library, chatting online. The man known as Dread Pirate Roberts — 29-year-old Ross William Ulbricht — was on his personal laptop Tuesday afternoon, authorities said, talking about the vast black market bazaar that is believed to have brokered more than $1 billion in transactions for illegal drugs and services. When a half-dozen FBI agents burst into the library in a quiet, blue collar neighborhood they abruptly ended Ulbricht's conversation with a cooperating witness, pinned the Austin, Texas, native to a floor-to-ceiling window and then took him off to jail, law enforcement and library spokeswomen said. Ulbricht was later charged in criminal complaints in federal courts in New York and Maryland. He's accused of making millions of dollars operating the secret Silk Road website and of a failed murder-for-hire scheme, all while living anonymously with two roommates whom he paid $1,000 to rent a room in a modest neighborhood. Federal authorities shut down the website. Ulbricht has not entered pleas to any of his charges. His federal public defender in San Francisco declined comment Wednesday. Ulbricht is due back in San Francisco federal court Friday morning to discuss bail and his transfer to New York, where the bulk of the charges have been filed. He is charged in New York with being the mastermind of Silk Road, where users could browse anonymously through nearly 13,000 listings under categories like &quot;Cannabis,&quot; ''Psychedelics&quot; and &quot;Stimulants.&quot; Ulbricht also is charged in Maryland with ordering first the torture, and then the murder, of an employee from an undercover agent. He feared the employee would expose his alias as Dread Pirate Roberts, a fictional character. Court records say he wired the agent $80,000 after he was shown staged photos of the employee's faked torture. His arrest culminated a two-year-investigation that painstakingly followed a small trail of computer crumbs Ulbricht carelessly left for the FBI to find, according to court documents. Ulbricht first came to the attention of federal agents in 2011 when they figured out he was &quot;altoid,&quot; someone who they say was marketing Silk Road on other drug-related websites the FBI was watching. In October 2011, &quot;altoid&quot; posted an advertisement for a computer expert with experience in Bitcoin, an electronic currency, and gave an email address. From there, investigators began to monitor Ulbricht's online behavior closely, according to the court records. Investigators said Ulbricht was living within 500 feet of a San Francisco Internet cafe on June 3, 2013 when someone &quot;logged into a server used to administer the Silk Road website.&quot; Court documents show investigators slowly connected Ulbricht to Silk Road by monitoring his email and picking up on some slipups, including using his real name to ask a programmers' website a highly technical question about connecting to secret sites like Silk Road. His final mistake, according to the court papers, was ordering fake identification documents from a Silk Road vendor from Canada. One of the nine documents was a California driver's license with Ulbricht's photograph, birthdate but a different name. The package was intercepted at the border during a routine U.S. Customs search. On July 26, Homeland Security investigators visited Ulbricht at his San Francisco residence. He &quot;generally refused to answer questions,&quot; the agents said. The investigators left that day without arresting Ulbricht, who holds a bachelor's of science degree in physics from the University of Texas at Dallas and a master's degree from Penn State. They returned Tuesday and arrested him at the library. He faces the prospect of life in prison if convicted of all the charges. The Silk Road website protected users with an encryption technique called &quot;onion routing,&quot; which is designed to make it &quot;practically impossible to physically locate the computers hosting or accessing websites on the network,&quot; court papers said. One listing for heroin promised buyers &quot;all rock, no powder, vacuum sealed and stealth shipping,&quot; and had a community forum below where one person commented, &quot;Quality is superb.&quot; The defendant announced in a website forum in 2012 that to avoid confusion he needed to change his Silk Road username, according to court papers released Wednesday. He wrote, &quot;drum roll please ... my new name is: Dread Pirate Roberts,&quot; an apparent reference to a swashbuckling character in &quot;The Princess Bride,&quot; the 1987 comedy film based on a novel of the same name. As of July, there were nearly 1 million registered users of the site from the United States, Germany, Russia, Australia and elsewhere around the globe, the court papers said. The site generated an estimated $1.2 billion since it started in 2011 and collected $80 million by charging 8 to 15 percent commission on each sale, they said. ___ Associated Press writer Tom Hays and AP researcher Barbara Sambriski in New York contributed to this report. Crime &amp; Justice Society &amp; Culture Dread Pirate Roberts San Francisco Click to view comments View Comments Share this Recommended for You Obama stressed to congressional leaders he will not negotiate over shutdown, debt limit WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Barack Obama stressed to congressional leaders on Wednesday in White House talks that he will not negotiate with Republicans over a government shutdown or raising the U.S. debt limit, the White House said. After more than an hour of talks that did not lead to a… Reuters Save More like this Remove Rouhani: Iran to discuss nuke details, not rights TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — President Hassan Rouhani said Wednesday that Iran is open to discussing &amp;quot;details&amp;quot; of nuclear activities including the enrichment of uranium, hinting that the Islamic Republic is willing to broaden the terms of negotiations with world powers. He spoke shortly after receiving… Associated Press Save More like this Remove Stream TV Shows and Movies Anywhere Any Time Take Netflix anywhere you go. Unlimited streaming from your favorite device for only $7.99/month. AdChoices Netflix Sponsored Suspect arraigned in motorcycle-SUV brawl in NYC NEW YORK (AP) — A motorcyclist was charged Wednesday with reckless driving after prosecutors said he touched off a tense encounter with the driver of an SUV and a throng of other bikers that ended with blood and broken bones on a Manhattan street. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Mia Farrow: &amp;#39;Possible&amp;#39; son is Sinatra&amp;#39;s NEW YORK (AP) — Mia Farrow says in an interview with Vanity Fair that it&amp;#39;s possible her son with Woody Allen is instead Frank Sinatra&amp;#39;s. Associated Press Save More like this Remove China&amp;#39;s Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes By Kanupriya Kapoor JAKARTA (Reuters) - Chinese President Xi Jinping showed no sign of bending to Southeast Asian pressure to resolve increasingly irascible territorial disputes over the South China Sea on Thursday, simply repeating past calls for dialogue. Xi, in the first address by a foreign… Reuters 45 mins ago Save More like this Remove View In the wild photo competition (9 photos) In The Wild Photo Competition via ZUMA Press   All creatures great and small are depicted in these wonderful images from a top wildlife competition. From a leopard hauling a wildebeest kill into a tree to a jackdaw picking parasites off a deer in Bushy Park, these were just some of the hundreds of… Save More like this Remove Wife: Biker husband is victim in NYC altercation NEW YORK (AP) — Shaky camera footage depicts the gory scene: A driver who police say was frightened when a group of motorcyclists swarmed his Range Rover plowed through them, striking a rider in a purple T-shirt and black helmet. Associated Press Save More like this Remove EPIC FAIL: Los Angeles high schools now confiscate all free iPads they gave students Hilariously, officials at high schools in the Los Angeles Unified School District are now taking back a couple thousand iPads a week or so after giving them to students as part of a 47-school pilot program. The Daily Caller Save More like this Remove The Hidden Costs of &amp;#39;Affordable&amp;#39; Health Insurance Plans The Affordable Care Act promises to expand access to health care by providing affordable coverage to millions of Americans. But finding a policy that meets your health care needs and your budget requirements can be daunting. U.S.News &amp; World Report LP Save More like this Remove With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) recently released this stunning photo of an estimated 10,000 walruses crammed onto a tiny Alaskan beach. The Sideshow Save More like this Remove Dazzling Bayern Munich can improve, warns Guardiola Manchester (United Kingdom) (AFP) - Manager Pep Guardiola watched his Bayern Munich team outclass Manchester City 3-1 and then warned the rest of Europe that the Champions League holders can get even better. AFP Save More like this Remove Video reveals final design of Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia Madrid (AFP) - It has been under construction for more than 130 years and there is another 13 to go, but the world has been given a glimpse of what Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia will look like when finally completed. AFP Save More like this Remove Play Hundreds of Students Involved in Violent Hazing Incident More than one hundred students at a Seattle high school were caught taking part in a dangerous hazing incident. Tribune Save More like this Remove Tesla Says Car Fire Began in Battery APNewsBreak: Tesla Model S car fire began in battery; stock falls after video goes online         ABC News Save More like this Remove Auto Dealers Cut Prices on New Cars &amp;amp; Trucks Local auto dealers are cutting their prices on all vehicle types. If you're looking for a new car this month, buy now and save as much as ... AdChoices Auto-Price-Finder.com Sponsored House Dems offer immigration bill, fate uncertain WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Wednesday unveiled an immigration bill that provides a path to citizenship for the 11 million immigrants living here illegally and tightens border security, and they warned of political fallout if House Republicans fail to act. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Shutdown Hampers Search for Missing Woman in Idaho National Park Ten Park Service rangers furloughed as a result of the government shutdown are volunteering their time to scour a national park in Idaho for a missing physician, whose search has been complicated by federal closures. Jo Elliott-Blakeslee, 63, was last seen in Craters of the... ABC News Save More like this Remove South Carolina drops extradition order for Baby Veronica&amp;#39;s biological father By Brendan O&amp;#39;Brien (Reuters) - The biological father of &amp;quot;Baby Veronica,&amp;quot; a Native American girl who was at the heart of a protracted custody battle, will not be extradited to South Carolina to face felony charges for interfering with her adoption, Oklahoma Governor Mary Fallin said on Wednesday.… Reuters Save More like this Remove 22 dogs will get lucky on new CBS television show LOS ANGELES (AP) — Brandon McMillan has trained as many as 10,000 dogs for television, movies, commercials, videos and people. Then he started saving dogs from animal shelters, training them and finding homes for them. Associated Press Save More like this Remove iPhone 5s Review: A Great Phone With Some More Forward Thinking Needed Is Apple&amp;#39;s Latest Really the &amp;#39;Forward Thinking&amp;#39; Phone it Promises? Good Morning America Save More like this Remove LA Coroner&amp;#39;s office IDing 4 bodies found in jet LOS ANGELES (AP) — Just as he had so many times before, Mark Benjamin rode his small jet from a town in the Idaho wilderness he loved to the Southern California airport he knew so well. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Load more stories Top Stories Meeting yields no breakthrough in shutdown Service academy football games will go on Tesla car fire involved battery pack Latest Videos Obama: Shutdown Result of Ideological Crusade 01:34 Vets Cross Barricades Despite Shutdown 01:15 Shutdown Ripple Effect Felt Across Country 00:02 Government shutdown: 15,000 FAA employees furloughed 01:59 Obama cancels stops on overseas trip in wake of shutdown 01:55 Latest Slideshows Sectarian violence between Rohingyas and Buddhists Photos of the day - October 2, 2013 In the wild photo competition Government shutdown begins US-Mexico border helicopter patrol continues through &amp;hellip; Yahoo News Originals Lottery Luck: Learn the recipe for winning the lottery (Video) Shutdown stories: How congressional quarreling is affecting us Veterans swarm ‘closed’ WWII memorial, knock politicians Awesome Magic Trick Prank Gives Pizza Deliverymen Surprise Tips Our Very Own Lip Sync Battle - Vote Now! Skeletons get hungry, too The biggest complaints about iOS 7 so far Obama, lawmakers huddle but no shutdown breakthrough The Last Word on...the Kindle Fire HDX With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach Copyright 2013 The Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten or redistributed. Yahoo - ABC News Network Help / Suggestions Privacy About Our Ads Terms
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:01:02
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4791934/snapchats-next-big-thing-stories-that-dont-just-disappear
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 19 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Apps Exclusive Report Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear The app that introduced ephemeral messages sets its sights on Facebook By Ellis Hamburger on October 3, 2013 03:00 am @hamburger 1 Comments Jump To up Top Comments down Close Snapchat CEO Evan Spiegel's hands are shaking as he points to his iPhone. He's unmistakably nervous, and not in a sweaty, early-Mark Zuckerberg kind of way. There must be a lot on his mind as the young CEO of a company bounding toward a $1 billion valuation — a company that has changed the course of being a teenager in the year 2013. Spiegel brushes off Snapchat’s latest bragging right: the service sees 350 million snaps sent per day. He seems anxious, as if he's about to interview for a job or deliver a commencement speech to his graduating class. Instead, he tells me about Stories, his team’s latest invention : a rolling compilation of snaps from the last 24 hours that your friends can see. You create your Story as you go about your day by tapping &quot;My Story&quot; above the friends you want to send a snap to. Or, you can tap a new shortcut button in the app's camera screen to instantly post a snap to your Story. But unlike conventional snaps, Stories don't disappear in a puff of ephemeral smoke after you've watched them. You can watch a friend’s (or your own) Story over and over. Each Story is the sum of all the snaps you’ve added over the last 24 hours, which means its size is always fluctuating. What doesn’t change is that every piece of the Story is less than a day old, so viewing one might be the fastest way to see what a friend's been up to. Snapchat may not look much like Facebook, but with Stories, the company is taking its first steps toward competing with Facebook’s most important product: News Feed. Behind Stories is a deep understanding, or perhaps loathing, of the way social apps work today. Spiegel claims to have no special knowledge of the way we work as social organisms aside from what he learned as a college student, but has thus far proven himself and his colleagues to be surprisingly thoughtful about our hidden social behaviors and desires. Stories is the next big piece of how Snapchat thinks social media should work, and everybody’s watching. No wonder Spiegel’s a little nervous. Stories, one of Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s most visible feature additions in its two-year lifespan, was first conceived as a way to address perhaps the most common request from users: a way to send a snap to your entire friends list. Spiegel and his team thought that a &quot;Send All&quot; button could destroy Snapchat, and instead sought a more passive means of sharing an image or video with everyone you know. Over the next year they built Stories, which live inside Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s &quot;My Friends&quot; page &amp;mdash; one of just four screens in the entire app. The final result recalls the early days of Facebook, where the quickest way to catch up with a friend was to visit their profile. Each person in your friend list is now flanked by a circular thumbnail of the most recent moment in their daily Story. Holding your finger on a friend&amp;rsquo;s name starts a stream of every snap they&amp;rsquo;ve shared to their Story within the last 24 hours. &quot;When you have a minute in your day and are curious about what your friends are up to, you can jump into their experience,&quot; says Spiegel. If you&amp;rsquo;re bored, you can skip ahead by tapping with a second finger. Unlike most forms of social media updates, Spiegel stresses, Stories play back in the order they occurred, and not in reverse chronological order. There&amp;rsquo;s also no algorithm to decide which stories are more important than others. &quot;The last snap today will also be the beginning of tomorrow,&quot; says Spiegel, &quot;so there&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Without naming any rivals, Spiegel digs at the Facebooks, Twitters, and Pinterests of the world that implicitly ask you to build an identity online. &quot;There's this weird thing that happens when you contribute something to a static profile,&quot; he says. &quot;You have to worry about how this new content fits in with your online persona that&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be you . It's uncomfortable and unfortunate.&quot; He seems to say that when Facebook released Timeline , a simple way to pore through years of updates and photos, it inadvertently cursed itself. By providing users with an enormous degree of transparency into their posts, Facebook may have also given its users anxiety about posting new content. Stories operates on the opposite principle. By providing users with fleeting, pocket-sized &quot;live profiles&quot; that last at most 24 hours, Spiegel hopes that users will feel free to act more like their true selves. He cites the practice of &quot;white-walling&quot; as evidence: where social media users on Facebook or Twitter post updates, only to delete the posts a short time later. The term was coined by one of Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s role models, researcher danah boyd , who describes it as a &quot;Risk Reduction Strategy&quot; on sites like Facebook. &quot;The internet is a timeless void &amp;mdash; you put something in there and it's there forever and loses a lot of context,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;There&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Snapchat actually has its own sociology researcher on staff, Nathan Jurgenson, made famous for &quot;The IRL Fetish,&quot; an essay on the augmented reality of our digital lives. &quot;He invented a concept called &amp;lsquo;digital dualism&amp;rsquo; &amp;mdash; something our company is fascinated by,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;It&amp;rsquo;s the notion that people conceptualize the world into online and offline, which makes for a lot of very awkward experiences.&quot; Spiegel doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly say that Snapchat is meant to emulate our real-life relationships, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t shy about saying that his app is doing a better job at it than competitors. &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out,&quot; he says. &quot;We believe that the next generation of powerful mobile companies have a deep understanding of the world as a unified whole,&quot; Spiegel argues, with the kind of hubristic, starry-eyed optimism only possible in the insular world of startups, &quot;where digital and analog experiences affect each other, rather than transporting analog experiences into the digital realm.&quot; &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out.&quot; Spiegel won&amp;rsquo;t comment on Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s plans to monetize its business, but there&amp;rsquo;s potential in Stories. Imagine a future where Miley Cyrus opens her Story to everyone (since the app allows two settings for who can see your Stories: friends or everyone). At any point in the day, you could check on what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to &amp;mdash; which would provide plenty of opportunities for advertising or brand placement. Spiegel smiles when I suggest the &quot;follow a celebrity&amp;rsquo;s story&quot; idea &amp;mdash; which is already entirely possible with the latest version of Snapchat &amp;mdash; but affirms his pledge to keep any kind of grown-up business ideas out of the app for now. &quot;We don't have Biz Dev boots on the ground trying to make it happen,&quot; Spiegel says, but he won&amp;rsquo;t rule it out either. &quot;We want to find ways to support artists who don't have a lot of reach.&quot; Three such artists will greet Snapchatters worldwide this morning when they open up the app, in three custom videos meant to introduce Stories to users. Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s final pitch is to narrate a day in his own life that seems almost too good to be true. &quot;I spoke at a TechCrunch thing a little while ago,&quot; he says. &quot;I took snaps of me being nervous, and of lots of people, and when I got lunch, and when I met with friend of mine, and then when we announced we do 350 million snaps per day.&quot; Snapchat employees, even though they were busy working out of the company&amp;rsquo;s beachfront office, got a glimpse into each of these moments as Spiegel went about his day, since they had access to his Story. &quot;And at midnight,&quot; he says, &quot;I was with friends at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, and when I ordered I looked down at my receipt and it was number 350.&quot; A new kind of digital communication &quot;It was a great narrative that I could've never captured ... in any other form of content,&quot; he says. &quot;You never know what's gonna happen until it happens.&quot; Spiegel takes a deep breath, leaning forward as if to hear the results of an exam he has just taken. The year of work and high-concept thinking behind Stories may just be &quot;a feature&quot; to his users &amp;mdash; but for Spiegel, it's obviously a lot more than that. Snapchat surprised the world and pushed aside myriad competitors, including Facebook itself . For the 23-year-old Spiegel, the story of Snapchat isn't about a clever and fun app for messaging, but about building a new kind of digital communication where our statuses, chats, photos, and videos don&amp;rsquo;t have to last forever. &quot;Ephemeral messaging&quot; was just the beginning. Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:00:04
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Microsoft explains how it built a better Kinect, boosted accuracy without sacrificing performance (video)
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.engadget.com/2013/10/03/xbox-one-kinect-design?ncid=txtlnkusaolp00000589
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Microsoft explains how it built a better Kinect, boosted accuracy without sacrificing performance (video) Engadget Menu News Reviews Features Galleries Videos Events Podcasts Engadget Show Topics Buyers Guides Sagas Store HD Mobile Alt Announcements Cameras Cellphones Desktops Displays Gaming GPS Handhelds Home Entertainment Household Internet Laptops Meta Misc Networking Peripherals Podcasts Robots Portable Audio/Video Science Software Storage Tablets Transportation Wearables Wireless Acer Amazon AMD Apple ASUS AT&amp;T Blackberry Canon Dell Facebook Google HP HTC Intel Lenovo LG Microsoft Nikon Nintendo Nokia NVIDIA Samsung Sony Sprint T-Mobile Verizon About Us Subscribe Like Engadget @engadget tip us Microsoft explains how it built a better Kinect, boosted accuracy without sacrificing performance (video) HD By Timothy J. Seppala posted Oct 3rd, 2013 at 2:08 AM 0 The Xbox One's improved Kinect device is looking like an enormous leap ahead of its predecessor, but getting it there wasn't easy. Designing it took a joint-effort between Microsoft's research division and the Architecture and Silicon Management (ASM) shop, according to Redmond's TechNet blog . It wasn't enough that the designers had to address the original Kinect's shortcomings either, adding new features presented plenty of new hurdles to overcome. Take the new sensor's HD camera upgrade, for example. That wider field of view may make using Kinect in a real living room more feasible, but the enhanced fidelity made it harder for engineers to keep smaller objects (like fingers) from disappearing into the background. The team has outlined some of the camera's new tricks, like ambient light canceling and an improved color camera, in a pair of demo videos. You'll find both of those, plus a look at how the Kinect processes 6.5 million pixels per second without the Xbox One missing a beat, at the source link below. Source: TechNet (Microsoft) Tags: gaming , hd , hdpostcross , kinect , microsoft , sensor , XboxOne Previous Netflix brings HD video and AirPlay streaming to iPhone, iPad &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/microsoft/xbox/one/kinect/&quot;&amp;gt; Microsoft Xbox One Kinect &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Microsoft Xbox One Kinect powered by gdgt Key specs &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/microsoft/xbox/one/kinect/&quot; title=&quot;Microsoft Xbox One Kinect reviews&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&amp;gt; Reviews &amp;bull; 0 &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Prices Type Other Connection Wired Console compatibility Microsoft Released 2013-11-22 see all specs &amp;rarr; There are not any reviews for this product yet. Why not be the first to write one? Get better reviews from people who actually have this product! write a review see all reviews &amp;rarr; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/microsoft/xbox/one/&quot;&amp;gt; Microsoft Xbox One &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Microsoft Xbox One Standard Day One Edition Buy from $ 499 powered by gdgt Key specs &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/microsoft/xbox/one/&quot; title=&quot;Microsoft Xbox One reviews&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&amp;gt; Reviews &amp;bull; 0 &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Prices Game format Optical disc, Downloadable Online features Multiplayer, Voice chat, Video chat, Store, Browser Drive capacity 500 GB Controller type Wired, Wireless Motion controls Camera / optical Video outputs HDMI Released 2013-11-22 see all specs &amp;rarr; There are not any reviews for this product yet. Why not be the first to write one? Get better reviews from people who actually have this product! write a review see all reviews &amp;rarr; Displaying prices for model: Standard-Black $499.96 + tax &amp;amp; shipping Buy now Sites We Like Tech Apple News gdgt Boing Boing Slashdot MAKE Ars Technica TechMeme Phone Scoop Design FFFFOUND! Core77 Popcorn Shower MoCo Loco Design*Sponge The Sartorialist News HuffPost Politics The Daily Beast Huffington Post Tech News Business News Investing News Lifestyle Lifehacker HuffPost Women Stylelist Automotive Translogic Gadling Environmental Inhabitat Good Autoblog Green Huffpost Green Entertainment Joystiq Massively The Onion i09 HuffPost Celebrity Spinner Moviefone About Us Subscribe via RSS Like Engadget on Facebook @engadget on Twitter Español 繁體中文 简体中文 日本版 Deutschland Joystiq Stealth Inc bringing its sneaky platforming to iOS All nominated IndieCade games offered Desura distribution and promotion Namco Bandai trademarks 'Soulcalibur: Unbreakable Soul' Tuaw Daily Deals for October 2, 2013, featuring the Call of Duty Bundle for Mac In contrast to Android OEMs, Apple and Motorola don't fudge their benchmarking results eleMount iPhone/iPad mount Kickstarts its way into production TechCrunch Cue, The Startup Formerly Known As Greplin, Shuts Down Its App Quantopian, A Community Of Quants, Picks Up $6.7M From Khosla, Spark Penn Jillette Turns To FundAnything To Become A Bad Guy HuffPost Tech A TALE OF TWO FACEBOOKS Here's The Seemingly Ordinary Man Who Ran The Internet's Biggest Black Market MORE : FBI Shutters 'Silk Road' AOL Tech. &amp;copy; 2013 AOL Inc. All rights reserved. Reprints and Permissions Privacy Policy Terms of Use Trademarks AOL A-Z Help Advertise with Us
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:59:31
      </updated_at>
    </item>
  </body>
</opml>
