<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<opml version="1.0">
  <!--Generated by FeedDigger-->
  <head>
    <title>
      grep last 60 minutes 201310030712
    </title>
    <dateCreated>
      2013-10-03 07:12:19.729592
    </dateCreated>
    <dateModified>
      2013-10-03 07:12:19.729592
    </dateModified>
  </head>
  <body>
    <item>
      <title>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Verge -  All Posts
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4791934/snapchats-next-big-thing-stories-that-dont-just-disappear
      </link>
      <author>
        Ellis Hamburger
      </author>
      <content>
        Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 19 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Apps Exclusive Report Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear The app that introduced ephemeral messages sets its sights on Facebook By Ellis Hamburger on October 3, 2013 03:00 am @hamburger 1 Comments Jump To up Top Comments down Close Snapchat CEO Evan Spiegel's hands are shaking as he points to his iPhone. He's unmistakably nervous, and not in a sweaty, early-Mark Zuckerberg kind of way. There must be a lot on his mind as the young CEO of a company bounding toward a $1 billion valuation — a company that has changed the course of being a teenager in the year 2013. Spiegel brushes off Snapchat’s latest bragging right: the service sees 350 million snaps sent per day. He seems anxious, as if he's about to interview for a job or deliver a commencement speech to his graduating class. Instead, he tells me about Stories, his team’s latest invention : a rolling compilation of snaps from the last 24 hours that your friends can see. You create your Story as you go about your day by tapping &quot;My Story&quot; above the friends you want to send a snap to. Or, you can tap a new shortcut button in the app's camera screen to instantly post a snap to your Story. But unlike conventional snaps, Stories don't disappear in a puff of ephemeral smoke after you've watched them. You can watch a friend’s (or your own) Story over and over. Each Story is the sum of all the snaps you’ve added over the last 24 hours, which means its size is always fluctuating. What doesn’t change is that every piece of the Story is less than a day old, so viewing one might be the fastest way to see what a friend's been up to. Snapchat may not look much like Facebook, but with Stories, the company is taking its first steps toward competing with Facebook’s most important product: News Feed. Behind Stories is a deep understanding, or perhaps loathing, of the way social apps work today. Spiegel claims to have no special knowledge of the way we work as social organisms aside from what he learned as a college student, but has thus far proven himself and his colleagues to be surprisingly thoughtful about our hidden social behaviors and desires. Stories is the next big piece of how Snapchat thinks social media should work, and everybody’s watching. No wonder Spiegel’s a little nervous. Stories, one of Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s most visible feature additions in its two-year lifespan, was first conceived as a way to address perhaps the most common request from users: a way to send a snap to your entire friends list. Spiegel and his team thought that a &quot;Send All&quot; button could destroy Snapchat, and instead sought a more passive means of sharing an image or video with everyone you know. Over the next year they built Stories, which live inside Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s &quot;My Friends&quot; page &amp;mdash; one of just four screens in the entire app. The final result recalls the early days of Facebook, where the quickest way to catch up with a friend was to visit their profile. Each person in your friend list is now flanked by a circular thumbnail of the most recent moment in their daily Story. Holding your finger on a friend&amp;rsquo;s name starts a stream of every snap they&amp;rsquo;ve shared to their Story within the last 24 hours. &quot;When you have a minute in your day and are curious about what your friends are up to, you can jump into their experience,&quot; says Spiegel. If you&amp;rsquo;re bored, you can skip ahead by tapping with a second finger. Unlike most forms of social media updates, Spiegel stresses, Stories play back in the order they occurred, and not in reverse chronological order. There&amp;rsquo;s also no algorithm to decide which stories are more important than others. &quot;The last snap today will also be the beginning of tomorrow,&quot; says Spiegel, &quot;so there&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Without naming any rivals, Spiegel digs at the Facebooks, Twitters, and Pinterests of the world that implicitly ask you to build an identity online. &quot;There's this weird thing that happens when you contribute something to a static profile,&quot; he says. &quot;You have to worry about how this new content fits in with your online persona that&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be you . It's uncomfortable and unfortunate.&quot; He seems to say that when Facebook released Timeline , a simple way to pore through years of updates and photos, it inadvertently cursed itself. By providing users with an enormous degree of transparency into their posts, Facebook may have also given its users anxiety about posting new content. Stories operates on the opposite principle. By providing users with fleeting, pocket-sized &quot;live profiles&quot; that last at most 24 hours, Spiegel hopes that users will feel free to act more like their true selves. He cites the practice of &quot;white-walling&quot; as evidence: where social media users on Facebook or Twitter post updates, only to delete the posts a short time later. The term was coined by one of Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s role models, researcher danah boyd , who describes it as a &quot;Risk Reduction Strategy&quot; on sites like Facebook. &quot;The internet is a timeless void &amp;mdash; you put something in there and it's there forever and loses a lot of context,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;There&amp;rsquo;s no pressure to compose a narrative.&quot; Snapchat actually has its own sociology researcher on staff, Nathan Jurgenson, made famous for &quot;The IRL Fetish,&quot; an essay on the augmented reality of our digital lives. &quot;He invented a concept called &amp;lsquo;digital dualism&amp;rsquo; &amp;mdash; something our company is fascinated by,&quot; says Spiegel. &quot;It&amp;rsquo;s the notion that people conceptualize the world into online and offline, which makes for a lot of very awkward experiences.&quot; Spiegel doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly say that Snapchat is meant to emulate our real-life relationships, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t shy about saying that his app is doing a better job at it than competitors. &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out,&quot; he says. &quot;We believe that the next generation of powerful mobile companies have a deep understanding of the world as a unified whole,&quot; Spiegel argues, with the kind of hubristic, starry-eyed optimism only possible in the insular world of startups, &quot;where digital and analog experiences affect each other, rather than transporting analog experiences into the digital realm.&quot; &quot;We never saw Google+ Circles or Facebook Lists as reflective of the way our friendships play out.&quot; Spiegel won&amp;rsquo;t comment on Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s plans to monetize its business, but there&amp;rsquo;s potential in Stories. Imagine a future where Miley Cyrus opens her Story to everyone (since the app allows two settings for who can see your Stories: friends or everyone). At any point in the day, you could check on what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to &amp;mdash; which would provide plenty of opportunities for advertising or brand placement. Spiegel smiles when I suggest the &quot;follow a celebrity&amp;rsquo;s story&quot; idea &amp;mdash; which is already entirely possible with the latest version of Snapchat &amp;mdash; but affirms his pledge to keep any kind of grown-up business ideas out of the app for now. &quot;We don't have Biz Dev boots on the ground trying to make it happen,&quot; Spiegel says, but he won&amp;rsquo;t rule it out either. &quot;We want to find ways to support artists who don't have a lot of reach.&quot; Three such artists will greet Snapchatters worldwide this morning when they open up the app, in three custom videos meant to introduce Stories to users. Spiegel&amp;rsquo;s final pitch is to narrate a day in his own life that seems almost too good to be true. &quot;I spoke at a TechCrunch thing a little while ago,&quot; he says. &quot;I took snaps of me being nervous, and of lots of people, and when I got lunch, and when I met with friend of mine, and then when we announced we do 350 million snaps per day.&quot; Snapchat employees, even though they were busy working out of the company&amp;rsquo;s beachfront office, got a glimpse into each of these moments as Spiegel went about his day, since they had access to his Story. &quot;And at midnight,&quot; he says, &quot;I was with friends at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, and when I ordered I looked down at my receipt and it was number 350.&quot; A new kind of digital communication &quot;It was a great narrative that I could've never captured ... in any other form of content,&quot; he says. &quot;You never know what's gonna happen until it happens.&quot; Spiegel takes a deep breath, leaning forward as if to hear the results of an exam he has just taken. The year of work and high-concept thinking behind Stories may just be &quot;a feature&quot; to his users &amp;mdash; but for Spiegel, it's obviously a lot more than that. Snapchat surprised the world and pushed aside myriad competitors, including Facebook itself . For the 23-year-old Spiegel, the story of Snapchat isn't about a clever and fun app for messaging, but about building a new kind of digital communication where our statuses, chats, photos, and videos don&amp;rsquo;t have to last forever. &quot;Ephemeral messaging&quot; was just the beginning. Previous Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:00:04
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Verge -  All Posts
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4797598/lg-g-flex-curved-oled-display-smartphone-rumor
      </link>
      <author>
        Aaron Souppouris
      </author>
      <content>
        LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 19 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Next Story Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just disappear Google Mobile LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month By Aaron Souppouris on October 3, 2013 02:55 am @AaronIsSocial 2 Comments Don't miss stories Follow The Verge Follow LG is planning to introduce a curved-screen smartphone called the G Flex this November. CNET reports that the Korean manufacturer will match Samsung's plan to sell a highly-curved handset, with the G Flex apparently set to feature a six-inch concave display. Although the phone could be one of the first to feature a long-awaited flexible OLED display , it won't be flexible itself. Instead, the OLED tech will enable a more dramatic curve than previously possible with conventional methods. Samsung has already created OLED-based devices with a slight curve, namely the Nexus S and Galaxy Nexus Google phones. The news comes just a week after Samsung announced it was ready to &quot; introduce a curved display smartphone in October .&quot; Both companies are heavily invested in OLED technologies, and have a history of one-upping and aping each other's products. The pair are already producing curved OLED televisions, so the idea of introducing such displays into smartphones isn't be a huge leap. CNET has a highly-pixelated sketch of what LG's new handset might look like on its site, but doesn't offer up any details as to the specs or price of the rumored smartphone. Source CNET Related Items oled flexible oled curved display smartphone android g flex curved oled television Nexus S Galaxy Nexus (Verizon) Samsung LG Cellphones In The Article Previous Samsung Nexus S Available: Dec. 16, 2010 8.7 Verge Score Samsung Galaxy Nexus (Verizon) Available: Dec. 15, 2011 Next Headlines Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to avoid a ruling on its claims This video game photographer creates art out of virtual worlds Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and analyst downgrade Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It On' claims bogus Latest Media Video Silk Road, Apple TV, and Tom Clancy: 90 Seconds on The Verge about 8 hours ago 2 comments Gallery August smart lock promo photos about 13 hours ago 1 comments Video Detours: Detroit-area firefighters battle a plague of burning buildings about 14 hours ago 4 comments Gallery Dell Venue 8 Pro, Venue 11 Pro, Venue 7 and Venue 8 about 15 hours ago Gallery Dell Venue tablet lineup press pictures about 15 hours ago 1 comments Discussions Meta Guys, stop using numerical scores. 30 minutes ago by ryallen23 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Has Microsoft been neglecting the desktop and not keeping pace with competition? about 1 hour ago by MetroPedro 9 comments Science NASA To Announce Alien Life On November 13th, 2013?! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 5 comments Web &amp; Social NASA &quot;Earth Shaking&quot; Announcement Going Viral! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 3 comments Meta I chatted with Netflix customer service just to give them a hard time. Turns out they are super helpful. about 2 hours ago by Ceveret3 2 comments Microsoft Tribe Dell Venue 8 Pro - HDMI? about 3 hours ago by debacle 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Can Surface RT Appeal to the Masses? about 3 hours ago by 1Rahtid 18 comments Microsoft Tribe Devil's Advocate on Venue 11 Pro about 3 hours ago by meelahi 8 comments Apps &amp; Software Best way to read The Verge articles on Kindle? about 4 hours ago by Soorms Googleplex I'm thinking about buying the Moto X. A few Questions... about 5 hours ago by mrusert 9 comments All Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:55:14
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Verge -  All Posts
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4797506/netflix-updates-ios-app-for-hd-streaming-and-airplay
      </link>
      <author>
        Aaron Souppouris
      </author>
      <content>
        Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 20 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to avoid a ruling on... Next Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Apple Apps Mobile Tech Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay By Aaron Souppouris on October 3, 2013 02:33 am @AaronIsSocial 4 Comments Don't miss stories Follow The Verge Follow Netflix has updated its iOS app to support HD streaming and AirPlay. After noting that HD streaming was coming well over a year ago , today's update apparently brings high-quality video to iOS devices for the first time. We've been unable to get the feature working in either the UK or the US. We had similar issues with AirPlay. The update claims to enable AirPlay streaming for iOS 7, so long as you disable AirPlay mirroring. We've been unable to stream anything but audio to an Apple TV, however, and also don't see the dedicated AirPlay button within the new app as depicted in Netflix's promotional imagery. It's not clear why the new functions aren't working right now, but it could be a case of Apple offering up the app update before Netflix's web-based interface is ready. We've reached out to Netflix for clarification on the new features, and will update this article when we hear back. Source Netflix (App Store) Related Items update hd streaming iphone netflix apple ipad video on demand ios airplay hd streaming ios 7 Headlines LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to avoid a ruling on its claims This video game photographer creates art out of virtual worlds Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and analyst downgrade Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It On' claims bogus Latest Media Video Silk Road, Apple TV, and Tom Clancy: 90 Seconds on The Verge about 8 hours ago 2 comments Gallery August smart lock promo photos about 13 hours ago 1 comments Video Detours: Detroit-area firefighters battle a plague of burning buildings about 14 hours ago 4 comments Gallery Dell Venue 8 Pro, Venue 11 Pro, Venue 7 and Venue 8 about 15 hours ago Gallery Dell Venue tablet lineup press pictures about 15 hours ago 1 comments Discussions Meta Guys, stop using numerical scores. 30 minutes ago by ryallen23 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Has Microsoft been neglecting the desktop and not keeping pace with competition? about 1 hour ago by MetroPedro 9 comments Science NASA To Announce Alien Life On November 13th, 2013?! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 5 comments Web &amp; Social NASA &quot;Earth Shaking&quot; Announcement Going Viral! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 3 comments Meta I chatted with Netflix customer service just to give them a hard time. Turns out they are super helpful. about 2 hours ago by Ceveret3 2 comments Microsoft Tribe Dell Venue 8 Pro - HDMI? about 3 hours ago by debacle 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Can Surface RT Appeal to the Masses? about 3 hours ago by 1Rahtid 18 comments Microsoft Tribe Devil's Advocate on Venue 11 Pro about 3 hours ago by meelahi 8 comments Apps &amp; Software Best way to read The Verge articles on Kindle? about 4 hours ago by Soorms Googleplex I'm thinking about buying the Moto X. A few Questions... about 5 hours ago by mrusert 9 comments All Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:33:40
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Investment Adviser and Entrepreneur
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        AllThingsD
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://allthingsd.com/20131002/investment-adviser-and-entrepreneur/
      </link>
      <author>
        Voices
      </author>
      <content>
        Ross Ulbricht's Economic Theories - Voices - Voices - AllThingsD WSJ WSJ WSJ Live WSJ Live MarketWatch MarketWatch Barron's Barron's Portfolio Portfolio Product X Product X rt f r&amp;amp;c pe&amp;amp;vc wsj b More All Things Digital WSJ Briefcase BigCharts Financial News Professor Journal SmartMoney Student Journal Virtual Stock Exchange WSJ Classifieds WSJ Classroom WSJ Radio WSJ Wine AllThingsD News Reviews Mobile Media Social Enterprise Commerce Voices Conferences Video Follow Us View by Writer Walt Mossberg &amp;#8211; New Spin on Video Chats Brings More to the Party Voices bio e-mail RSS Recent Posts by Voices Investment Adviser and Entrepreneur October 2, 2013 at 11:59 pm PT Tweet Share Print I want to use economic theory as a means to abolish the use of coercion and agression [sic] amongst mankind&amp;#8230; To that end, I am creating an economic simulation to give people a first-hand experience of what it would be like to live in a world without the systemic use of force. &amp;#8211; From the LinkedIn profile summary of Ross Ulbricht , who was arrested Tuesday as the alleged Silk Road mastermind &amp;#8220;Dread Pirate Roberts&amp;#8221; Tagged with: economic theory, LinkedIn , Ross Ulbricht Powered by Livefyre Must-Reads from other Websites How Google Taught Itself Good Design Farhad Manjoo, Tech Reporter, The Wall Street Journal, in Fast Company Opinion: What the Future of Sports Games Should Look Like Steve McPherson, Contributor, Polygon Shareholder’s Best Interests Ben Horowitz, Partner, Andreessen Horowitz What Inner City Kids Know About Social Media, and Why We Should Listen Jacqui Cheng, Editor, Ars Technica Is Login Data the New Gold? Jack Marshall, Writer, Digiday Quora’s Search for What the Internet Doesn’t Know Tom Simonite, Editor, MIT Technology Review About Must-Reads &amp;raquo; More Inside &amp;raquo; About Voices Along with original content and posts from across the Dow Jones network, this section of AllThingsD includes Must-Reads From Other Websites &amp;#8212; pieces we&amp;#8217;ve read, discussions we&amp;#8217;ve followed, stuff we like. Six posts from external sites are included here each weekday, but we only run the headlines. We link to the original sites for the rest. These posts are explicitly labeled, so it&amp;#8217;s clear that the content comes from other websites, and for clarity&amp;#8217;s sake, all outside posts run against a pink background. We also solicit original full-length posts and accept some unsolicited submissions. Voices is edited by Beth Callaghan. Featured Posts Featured Reviews BlackBerry&amp;#8217;s Latest Filing Paints Grimmest Picture Yet of Company&amp;#8217;s Business Ina Fried in Mobile New Spin on Video Chats Brings More to the Party Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology Kevin Rose Is AngelList&amp;#8217;s Million-Dollar Man Liz Gannes in News View all today&amp;#8217;s news &amp;raquo; Help Wanted: Moonlighters for Mobile Apps Katherine Boehret in The Digital Solution Surface Pro: Hefty Tablet Is a Laptop Lightweight Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology NFC: What You Need to Know Lauren Goode in Product Reviews A Wristwatch Tells When Phone Calls, Emails Arrive Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology How Apple Gets All the Good Apps Walt Mossberg in Personal Technology View all reviews &amp;raquo; AllThingsD by Writer Walt Mossberg Kara Swisher John Paczkowski Katherine Boehret Peter Kafka Ina Fried Liz Gannes Arik Hesseldahl Lauren Goode Mike Isaac Bonnie Cha Jason Del Rey AllThingsD.com is a Web site devoted to news, analysis and opinion on technology, the Internet and media. But it is different from other sites in this space. It is a fusion of different media styles, different topics, different formats and different sources. Read more &amp;raquo; About Us &amp;raquo; Contact Us &amp;raquo; Comments Policy &amp;raquo; Cookies Policy &amp;raquo; Privacy Policy - UPDATED 10/18/2011 &amp;raquo; FAQ &amp;raquo; Terms of Service &amp;raquo; Your Ad Choices &amp;raquo; Advertise With Us &amp;raquo; Send a Tip &amp;raquo; Daily Headlines Email &amp;raquo; Follow AllThingsD Your Way &amp;raquo; Featuring the most influential figures in technology, unscripted and upfront. More &amp;raquo; Conferences: D: All Things Digital. &amp;raquo; D: Dive Into Media &amp;raquo; D: Dive Into Mobile &amp;raquo; Follow us on Twitter: Select Account @allthingsd (All Things Digital) @ATDapple (Apple) @ATDgoogle (Google) @ATDmedia (Media) @ATDmobile (Mobile) @ATDreviews (Reviews) @waltmossberg (Walt Mossberg) @karaswisher (Kara Swisher) @JohnPaczkowski (John Paczkowski) @kabster728 (Katherine Boehret) @pkafka (Peter Kafka) @inafried (Ina Fried) @LizGannes (Liz Gannes) @ahess247 (Arik Hesseldahl) @LaurenGoode (Lauren Goode) @MikeIsaac (Mike Isaac) @BonnieSCha (Bonnie Cha) @DelRey (Jason Del Rey) RSS Feeds Select Feed All Feeds News Reviews Mobile Media Social Enterprise Commerce Voices Personal Technology Mossberg&amp;#8217;s Mailbox The Digital Solution Walt Mossberg Kara Swisher John Paczkowski Katherine Boehret Peter Kafka Ina Fried Liz Gannes Arik Hesseldahl Lauren Goode Mike Isaac Bonnie Cha Jason Del Rey &amp;copy; 2005-2013 Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company Inc. All Rights Reserved. Powered by WordPress.com VIP Mobile Version
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:59:35
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        China's Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Reuters: Top News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/topNews/~3/KlGzCwee0_U/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        China's Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes | Reuters Edition: U.S. Arabic Argentina Brazil Canada China France Germany India Italy Japan Latin America Mexico Russia Spain United Kingdom Home Business Business Home Economy Media Small Business Legal Deals Earnings Business Video The Freeland File Aerospace &amp; Defense Summits Markets Markets Home U.S. Markets European Markets Asian Markets Global Market Data Indices M&amp;A Stocks Bonds Currencies Commodities Futures Funds peHUB Dividends World World Home U.S. Brazil China Euro Zone Japan Africa Mexico Russia India Insight World Video Reuters Investigates Decoder Global Innovations Politics Politics Home Supreme Court Politics Video Tech Technology Home MediaFile Science Tech Video Tech Tonic Opinion Opinion Home John Lloyd Felix Salmon Jack Shafer David Rohde Nader Mousavizadeh Nicholas Wapshott Bethany McLean Anatole Kaletsky Zachary Karabell Edward Hadas Hugo Dixon Ian Bremmer Lawrence Summers The Great Debate Reihan Salam Mark Leonard Steven Brill Alison Frankel Breakingviews Equities Credit Private Equity M&amp;A Macro &amp; Markets Politics Breakingviews Video Money Money Home Tax Break Lipper Awards Global Investing MuniLand Unstructured Finance Linda Stern Mark Miller John Wasik James Saft Analyst Research Alerts Watchlist Portfolio Stock Screener Fund Screener Personal Finance Video Money Clip Investing 201 Life Health Sports Arts Faithworld Entertainment Oddly Enough Cancer in Context Lifestyle Video Pictures Pictures Home Reuters Photographers Full Focus Video Reuters TV Reuters News Article Comments (2) Full Focus Editor's choice Our top photos from the last 24 hours. Slideshow Images of August Download our Wider Image iPad app Follow Reuters Facebook Twitter RSS YouTube Read FBI shuts alleged online drug marketplace, Silk Road 02 Oct 2013 Obama, congressional leaders still deadlocked on shutdown | 02 Oct 2013 Japan's Fukushima nuclear plant operator says another tank leaked toxic water 12:07am EDT Exclusive: Microsoft investors push for chairman Gates to step down 01 Oct 2013 FBI raids alleged online drug market Silk Road, arrests owner 02 Oct 2013 Discussed 249 Deadlocked Congress takes U.S. government to brink of shutdown 174 White House rejects latest Republican offer to end shutdown 169 Capitol quiet as federal government shutdown nears Pictures Reuters Photojournalism Our day's top images, in-depth photo essays and offbeat slices of life. See the best of Reuters photography. See more | Photo caption Scenes from the shutdown Images from the U.S. government shutdown. Slideshow The elderly boom A United Nations report says the world may not be ready to support its growing elderly population. By 2050, estimates say seniors over 60 will outnumber children under 15. Slideshow Sponsored Links China's Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes Tweet Share this Email Print Related Topics World &amp;#187; China &amp;#187; China's President Xi Jinping walks during a welcoming ceremony at the Presidential Palace in Jakarta October 2, 2013. Credit: Reuters/Supri By Kanupriya Kapoor JAKARTA | Thu Oct 3, 2013 2:29am EDT JAKARTA (Reuters) - Chinese President Xi Jinping showed no sign of bending to Southeast Asian pressure to resolve increasingly irascible territorial disputes over the South China Sea on Thursday, simply repeating past calls for dialogue. Xi, in the first address by a foreign leader to Indonesian MPs, made no reference to regional demands, echoed in Washington, that Beijing deal with the rival claims through multilateral talks rather than with individual negotiations. The issue is certain to overshadow two regional summits next week which Xi will attend. U.S. President Barack Obama's planned attendance is in doubt because of the U.S. government shutdown. &quot;As for the disagreements and disputes between China and certain Southeast Asian nations on territorial sovereignty and maritime rights, both sides must always uphold the use of peaceful methods ...to maintain the broad picture of bilateral relations and regional stability,&quot; he told MPs on the second and last day of his visit to Southeast Asia's largest country. &quot;China's development is a force for peace and friendship in the world, bringing development opportunities for Asia and the world and not threats.&quot; Last month, the Philippines accused China of violating an informal code of conduct in the South China Sea, home to some of the world's most vital trade routes, by planning new structures on a disputed shoals. The disputes have centred on concerns that China's use of its growing naval might to back claims to much of the oil- and gas-rich sea could spark a military clash. Four of the 10 members of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), including Vietnam and the Philippines, have overlapping claims with China. Indonesia, which does not, has offered to mediate but has in the past criticized China for not showing more restraint over the disputes. Next Tuesday sees the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit in the Indonesian resort island of Bali. After that, Xi and several other leaders will head to Brunei for the East Asia summit. &quot;What we wanted to hear from President Xi Jinping was whether China has the goodwill to resolve the South China Sea issue ... But he didn't address the issue at all, so I'm disappointed,&quot; legislator Tantowi Yahya told Reuters. Xi has used his visit try to lift relations in the region, saying China hoped trade with ASEAN would reach $1 trillion by 2020. He flies later in the day to Malaysia. China is already Indonesia's biggest trading partner after Japan. The two were expected to finalize a raft of deals, mainly in the mining sector, worth more than $30 billion during Xi's visit. Only about a third of the members of the combined houses attended the speech, the first such address by a foreign leader. (Addtional reporting by Ben Blanchard in Beijing; Writing by Jonathan Thatcher; Editing by Nick Macfie) World China Tweet this Link this Share this Digg this Email Reprints We welcome comments that advance the story through relevant opinion, anecdotes, links and data. If you see a comment that you believe is irrelevant or inappropriate, you can flag it to our editors by using the report abuse links. Views expressed in the comments do not represent those of Reuters. For more information on our comment policy, see http://blogs.reuters.com/fulldisclosure/2010/09/27/toward-a-more-thoughtful-conversation-on-stories/ Comments (2) yoong wrote: Response to nike_sky: China is not a wannabe. It will be !! 2020. Can&amp;#8217;t live with it ? Use your brains instead of your dick. Oct 03, 2013 1:02am EDT -- Report as abuse Free_Pacific wrote: &amp;#8220;What we wanted to hear from President Xi Jinping was whether China has the goodwill to resolve the South China Sea issue &amp;#8230; But he didn&amp;#8217;t address the issue at all, so I&amp;#8217;m disappointed,&amp;#8221; legislator Tantowi Yahya told Reuters. China has no goodwill. Only belligerence and creeping colonial expansion. The thief, robber and bully of the Asia-pacific. Oct 03, 2013 3:03am EDT -- Report as abuse See All Comments &amp;#187; Add Your Comment Edition: U.S. Arabic Argentina Brazil Canada China France Germany India Italy Japan Latin America Mexico Russia Spain United Kingdom Back to top Reuters.com Business Markets World Politics Technology Opinion Money Pictures Videos Site Index Legal Bankruptcy Law California Legal New York Legal Securities Law Support &amp; Contact Support Corrections Connect with Reuters Twitter Facebook LinkedIn RSS Podcast Newsletters Mobile About Privacy Policy Terms of Use Advertise With Us AdChoices Copyright Our Flagship financial information platform incorporating Reuters Insider An ultra-low latency infrastructure for electronic trading and data distribution A connected approach to governance, risk and compliance Our next generation legal research platform Our global tax workstation Thomsonreuters.com About Thomson Reuters Investor Relations Careers Contact Us Thomson Reuters is the world's largest international multimedia news agency, providing investing news , world news , business news , technology news , headline news, small business news , news alerts, personal finance , stock market , and mutual funds information available on Reuters.com, video , mobile , and interactive television platforms. Thomson Reuters journalists are subject to an Editorial Handbook which requires fair presentation and disclosure of relevant interests. NYSE and AMEX quotes delayed by at least 20 minutes. Nasdaq delayed by at least 15 minutes. For a complete list of exchanges and delays, please click here .
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:29:33
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        15 dead in attack on leader of Pakistani anti-Taliban militia
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Reuters: Top News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/topNews/~3/Q1bStNBoqpk/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        15 dead in attack on leader of Pakistani anti-Taliban militia | Reuters Edition: U.S. Arabic Argentina Brazil Canada China France Germany India Italy Japan Latin America Mexico Russia Spain United Kingdom Home Business Business Home Economy Media Small Business Legal Deals Earnings Business Video The Freeland File Aerospace &amp; Defense Summits Markets Markets Home U.S. Markets European Markets Asian Markets Global Market Data Indices M&amp;A Stocks Bonds Currencies Commodities Futures Funds peHUB Dividends World World Home U.S. Brazil China Euro Zone Japan Africa Mexico Russia India Insight World Video Reuters Investigates Decoder Global Innovations Politics Politics Home Supreme Court Politics Video Tech Technology Home MediaFile Science Tech Video Tech Tonic Opinion Opinion Home John Lloyd Felix Salmon Jack Shafer David Rohde Nader Mousavizadeh Nicholas Wapshott Bethany McLean Anatole Kaletsky Zachary Karabell Edward Hadas Hugo Dixon Ian Bremmer Lawrence Summers The Great Debate Reihan Salam Mark Leonard Steven Brill Alison Frankel Breakingviews Equities Credit Private Equity M&amp;A Macro &amp; Markets Politics Breakingviews Video Money Money Home Tax Break Lipper Awards Global Investing MuniLand Unstructured Finance Linda Stern Mark Miller John Wasik James Saft Analyst Research Alerts Watchlist Portfolio Stock Screener Fund Screener Personal Finance Video Money Clip Investing 201 Life Health Sports Arts Faithworld Entertainment Oddly Enough Cancer in Context Lifestyle Video Pictures Pictures Home Reuters Photographers Full Focus Video Reuters TV Reuters News Article Comments (0) Full Focus Editor's choice Our top photos from the last 24 hours. Slideshow Images of August Download our Wider Image iPad app Follow Reuters Facebook Twitter RSS YouTube Read FBI shuts alleged online drug marketplace, Silk Road 02 Oct 2013 Obama, congressional leaders still deadlocked on shutdown | 02 Oct 2013 Japan's Fukushima nuclear plant operator says another tank leaked toxic water 12:07am EDT Exclusive: Microsoft investors push for chairman Gates to step down 01 Oct 2013 FBI raids alleged online drug market Silk Road, arrests owner 02 Oct 2013 Discussed 249 Deadlocked Congress takes U.S. government to brink of shutdown 174 White House rejects latest Republican offer to end shutdown 169 Capitol quiet as federal government shutdown nears Pictures Reuters Photojournalism Our day's top images, in-depth photo essays and offbeat slices of life. See the best of Reuters photography. See more | Photo caption Scenes from the shutdown Images from the U.S. government shutdown. Slideshow The elderly boom A United Nations report says the world may not be ready to support its growing elderly population. By 2050, estimates say seniors over 60 will outnumber children under 15. Slideshow Sponsored Links 15 dead in attack on leader of Pakistani anti-Taliban militia Tweet Share this Email Print Related Topics World &amp;#187; By Javed Hussain Parachinar, PAKISTAN | Thu Oct 3, 2013 2:27am EDT Parachinar, PAKISTAN (Reuters) - At least 15 people were killed in an attack on a pro-government militia commander in Pakistan's lawless northwestern tribal area on Thursday morning, security forces said. The attack comes as Pakistan's government is mulling peace talks with the Taliban, although no conditions have yet been set, and previous deals with the Taliban have always collapsed. A car bomb rammed into the compound of Mullah Nabi Hanfi, the leader of an anti-Taliban militia he formed after breaking away from the Taliban in 2009. Two suicide bombers launched a second attack but were killed in the shootout by Hanfi's men, sources in the security forces said. Hanfi was among the ten men wounded in the attack and taken to a district hospital. He survived a similar attack on his compound last year that killed 10 people. He lives in the Spin Tal region of Hangu district, bordering North Waziristan, considered a hub of Taliban militants. (Writing by Syed Raza Hassan; Editing by Clarence Fernandez) World Tweet this Link this Share this Digg this Email Reprints We welcome comments that advance the story through relevant opinion, anecdotes, links and data. If you see a comment that you believe is irrelevant or inappropriate, you can flag it to our editors by using the report abuse links. Views expressed in the comments do not represent those of Reuters. For more information on our comment policy, see http://blogs.reuters.com/fulldisclosure/2010/09/27/toward-a-more-thoughtful-conversation-on-stories/ Comments (0) Be the first to comment on reuters.com. Add yours using the box above. Edition: U.S. Arabic Argentina Brazil Canada China France Germany India Italy Japan Latin America Mexico Russia Spain United Kingdom Back to top Reuters.com Business Markets World Politics Technology Opinion Money Pictures Videos Site Index Legal Bankruptcy Law California Legal New York Legal Securities Law Support &amp; Contact Support Corrections Connect with Reuters Twitter Facebook LinkedIn RSS Podcast Newsletters Mobile About Privacy Policy Terms of Use Advertise With Us AdChoices Copyright Our Flagship financial information platform incorporating Reuters Insider An ultra-low latency infrastructure for electronic trading and data distribution A connected approach to governance, risk and compliance Our next generation legal research platform Our global tax workstation Thomsonreuters.com About Thomson Reuters Investor Relations Careers Contact Us Thomson Reuters is the world's largest international multimedia news agency, providing investing news , world news , business news , technology news , headline news, small business news , news alerts, personal finance , stock market , and mutual funds information available on Reuters.com, video , mobile , and interactive television platforms. Thomson Reuters journalists are subject to an Editorial Handbook which requires fair presentation and disclosure of relevant interests. NYSE and AMEX quotes delayed by at least 20 minutes. Nasdaq delayed by at least 15 minutes. For a complete list of exchanges and delays, please click here .
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:27:30
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Google acquiring gesture recognition tech startup Flutter
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Top Headlines
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.zdnet.com/google-acquiring-gesture-recognition-tech-startup-flutter-7000021484/
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        ﻿ Google acquiring gesture recognition tech startup Flutter | ZDNet ZDNet Log In | Join ZDNet Home White Papers Hot Topics Downloads Reviews Newsletters US Edition ZDNet.com is available in the following editions: Asia Australia Europe India United Kingdom United States ZDNet around the globe: ZDNet Benelux ZDNet China ZDNet France ZDNet Germany ZDNet Korea ZDNet Japan ZDNet Netherlands Topics IaaS BYOD SMB Virtualization Big Data Apple CXO Windows 8 Tablets All Writers Log In Log In Join ZDNet JUST IN: Dell launches new Android, Windows-powered Venue tablets, XPS ultrabooks Topic: Start-Ups Discover Follow via: RSS Email Alert Google acquiring gesture recognition tech startup Flutter Summary: Naturally, Google's new purchase has everyone buzzing about whether or not the new tech is going into everything from the Nexus 5 to Glass. By Rachel King for Between the Lines | October 2, 2013 -- 23:30 GMT (16:30 PDT) Follow @rachelking Google has bought a startup that produces gesture recognition technology that controls popular apps via webcam. Read this Nuance intros Voice Ads to engage consumers through mobile ads Nuance has introduced what it is framing as a &quot;game changer&quot; for mobile advertising — and that could be accurate. Read more Flutter, a San Francisco-based startup backed by the likes of Andreessen Horowitz and Y Combinator, launched approximately 18 months ago to develop gesture recognition technology for Mac and Windows apps. Some of the apps that can be controlled by Flutter's solutions include YouTube, Pandora, Grooveshark, and Netflix. With Google as the new owner, presumably some sort of Android and/or Chrome support is on the agenda. Flutter CEO Navneet Dalal confirmed the news in a blog post on Wednesday, remarking that his team &quot;will be continuing our research at Google.&quot; Naturally, Google's new purchase has everyone buzzing about whether or not the new tech is going into everything from the Nexus 5 to Glass. But neither Flutter leadership nor the Internet giant itself have revealed how or where the Flutter portfolio will be integrated. Financial terms of the deal have also not been disclosed. Screenshot via Flutter Topics: Start-Ups , Google , Mobility , Software , Tech Industry About Rachel King Rachel King is a staff writer for ZDNet based in San Francisco. Google+ Follow @rachelking Contact Disclosure Kick off your day with ZDNet's daily email newsletter . It's the freshest tech news and opinion, served hot. Get it. Talkback 1 comment Log in or register to join the discussion Talk to the hand, Rachel. Based on your included &amp;quot;How Flutter Works&amp;quot; graphics, I just couldn&amp;#039;t resist. Grin. kenosha77a 3 October, 2013 00:42 Reply Vote Related Stories Google: Who wants to be a startup billionare? Coinbase drops merchant fees for first $1 million Bitcoin orders Rogue Wave buying open source software provider OpenLogic And now, 231 words on entrepreneurship (and more) from Jack Dorsey The best of ZDNet, delivered ZDNet Newsletters Get the best of ZDNet delivered straight to your inbox We're temporarily in maintenance mode, which means you won't be able to sign up for a newsletter. Please check back shortly to resume the subscription process. Thanks for your patience. ZDNet Must Read News Alerts - US: Major news is breaking. Are you ready? This newsletter has only the most important tech news nothing else. Facebook Twitter LinkedIn Google+ RSS Android iPhone Facebook Activity Events Calendar White Papers, Webcasts, &amp;amp; Resources Top Five Reasons Why EMC VNX is Simple The EMC VNX family offers automated and economical unified storage . Check out this white paper for the top five simple benefits of EMC VNX. Control Your IT Universe with DameWare DameWare Remote Support ( DRS ) helps you remotely manage the Windows &amp;#174; desktops and laptops in your IT universe. Download a FREE 14-day trial of DameWare Remote Support today! An Inside Look at the New NetApp FAS2240 This article takes an inside look at the unique design features of the NetApp FAS2240, including integration of controllers within NetApp SAS disk shelves, I/O and performance enhancements, and new resiliency and availability features. Download this white paper now . CNET Join | Log In | Privacy | Cookies Close Featured Articles Kaspersky Lab calls Lodsys out on patent trolling and wins The death of Microsoft Nokia Lumia 1020 review: A photographer&amp;#039;s smartphone Microsoft&amp;#039;s next CEO: Is an insider Redmond&amp;#039;s best bet? Around ZDNet Topics Broadband Speed Test Events Calendar Meet the Team About ZDNet Site Map Services Log In | Join ZDNet Membership Newsletters RSS Feeds ZDNet Mobile Site Assistance &amp;copy; 2013 CBS Interactive. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy | Cookies | Ad Choice | Advertise | Terms of Use Visit other CBS Interactive sites Select Site CBS Cares CBS Films CBS Radio CBS.com CBSInteractive CBSNews.com CBSSports.com CHOW Clicker CNET College Network GameSpot Help.com Last.fm MaxPreps Metacritic.com Moneywatch mySimon Radio.com Search.com Shopper.com Showtime SmartPlanet TechRepublic The Insider TV.com UrbanBaby.com ZDNet
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:30:05
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        US federal agents shut down Silk Road website
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Top Headlines
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.zdnet.com/us-federal-agents-shut-down-silk-road-website-7000021483/
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        ﻿ US federal agents shut down Silk Road website | ZDNet ZDNet Log In | Join ZDNet Home White Papers Hot Topics Downloads Reviews Newsletters US Edition ZDNet.com is available in the following editions: Asia Australia Europe India United Kingdom United States ZDNet around the globe: ZDNet Benelux ZDNet China ZDNet France ZDNet Germany ZDNet Korea ZDNet Japan ZDNet Netherlands Topics IaaS BYOD SMB Virtualization Big Data Apple CXO Windows 8 Tablets All Writers Log In Log In Join ZDNet JUST IN: Dell launches new Android, Windows-powered Venue tablets, XPS ultrabooks Topic: Privacy Discover Follow via: RSS Email Alert US federal agents shut down Silk Road website Summary: American authorities say they have busted an online black market for drugs, hitmen, hacker tools, and more, arresting the suspected mastermind of a nefarious bazaar called Silk Road. By AAP | October 2, 2013 -- 23:28 GMT (16:28 PDT) US federal agents have shut down the Silk Road website, which used the privacy-protecting Tor network and Bitcoin digital currency to shield the identities of buyers and sellers around the world. Ross William Ulbricht, also known as &quot;Dread Pirate Roberts&quot;, was arrested in San Francisco after the website was shut down, the Justice Department said in a statement on Wednesday. His online moniker appeared to be taken from a character in the film The Princess Bride. Prosecutors said they seized approximately $3.6 million worth of Bitcoins in the largest ever seizure of the digital currency. &quot;The Silk Road website has served as a sprawling black market bazaar where illegal drugs and other illicit goods and services have been regularly bought and sold by the site's users,&quot; FBI Special Agent Christopher Tarbell said in a criminal complaint filed in Federal Court. From about January 2011, Ulbricht ran a marketplace that hawked heroin, cocaine, LSD, and methamphetamine, as well as hacker tools such as software for stealing passwords or logging keystrokes on people's machines, according to court documents. Prosecutors also charged that in March, Ulbricht tried to hire someone to kill a Silk Road user who threatened to expose the identities of others using the website. &quot;The defendant deliberately set out to establish an online criminal marketplace outside the reach of law enforcement and government regulation,&quot; Tarbell said in the legal filing. Ulbricht, 29, anonymised Silk Road transactions by using a Tor computer network designed to make it almost impossible to locate computers used to host or access websites. He also added a Bitcoin &quot;tumbler&quot; to the Silk Road payment system to foil efforts to trace digital currency back to buyers, according to the criminal complaint. &quot;Silk Road has emerged as the most sophisticated and extensive criminal marketplace on the internet today,&quot; the criminal complaint contended. &quot;The site has sought to make conducting illegal transactions as easy and frictionless as shopping online at mainstream ecommerce websites.&quot; Prosecutors maintained that Silk Road has been used by thousands of drug dealers to distribute hundreds of kilograms of illegal wares to more than 100,000 buyers, and to launder hundreds of millions of dollars in ill-gotten profits. Topics: Privacy , Security Kick off your day with ZDNet's daily email newsletter . It's the freshest tech news and opinion, served hot. Get it. Talkback 0 comments Log in or register to start the discussion Related Stories Greens propose to force IT companies to disclose govt agreements Inside the Tor exploit Verizon exec slams Google, Microsoft, Yahoo for NSA lawsuit grandstanding Data-driven analysis debunks claims that NSA is out of control (Special Report) The best of ZDNet, delivered ZDNet Newsletters Get the best of ZDNet delivered straight to your inbox We're temporarily in maintenance mode, which means you won't be able to sign up for a newsletter. Please check back shortly to resume the subscription process. Thanks for your patience. ZDNet Must Read News Alerts - US: Major news is breaking. Are you ready? This newsletter has only the most important tech news nothing else. Facebook Twitter LinkedIn Google+ RSS Android iPhone Facebook Activity Events Calendar White Papers, Webcasts, &amp;amp; Resources Aerospec and EMC VNXe In this case study , learn how Aerospec , a system engineering and manufacturing company, leveraged VNXe and VMware to cut operating costs and increase reliability . Control Your IT Universe with DameWare DameWare Remote Support ( DRS ) helps you remotely manage the Windows &amp;#174; desktops and laptops in your IT universe. Download a FREE 14-day trial of DameWare Remote Support today! Denver Broncos Success Story To carry the organization forward, the The Denver Broncos IT staff needed to upgrade the storage environment . Learn how efficient NetApp IT empowered the Denver Broncos to invest in the future by providing asychronous disaster recovery and data protection. Read more now ! CNET Join | Log In | Privacy | Cookies Close Featured Articles Kaspersky Lab calls Lodsys out on patent trolling and wins The death of Microsoft Nokia Lumia 1020 review: A photographer&amp;#039;s smartphone Microsoft&amp;#039;s next CEO: Is an insider Redmond&amp;#039;s best bet? Around ZDNet Topics Broadband Speed Test Events Calendar Meet the Team About ZDNet Site Map Services Log In | Join ZDNet Membership Newsletters RSS Feeds ZDNet Mobile Site Assistance &amp;copy; 2013 CBS Interactive. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy | Cookies | Ad Choice | Advertise | Terms of Use Visit other CBS Interactive sites Select Site CBS Cares CBS Films CBS Radio CBS.com CBSInteractive CBSNews.com CBSSports.com CHOW Clicker CNET College Network GameSpot Help.com Last.fm MaxPreps Metacritic.com Moneywatch mySimon Radio.com Search.com Shopper.com Showtime SmartPlanet TechRepublic The Insider TV.com UrbanBaby.com ZDNet
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:28:05
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Ziggy Switkowski appointed chairman of NBN Co
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Technology news, comment and analysis | theguardian.com
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.theguardian.com/c/34708/f/663871/s/31ff5891/sc/25/l/0L0Stheguardian0N0Ctechnology0C20A130Coct0C0A30Cziggy0Eswitkowski0Echairman0Enbn0Eco/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        Gabrielle Chan
      </author>
      <content>
        Ziggy Switkowski appointed chairman of NBN Co | Technology | theguardian.com Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life &amp;amp; style Data News Technology National Broadband Network (NBN) Ziggy Switkowski appointed chairman of NBN Co Malcolm Turnbull announces that former Telstra chief will chair board overseeing national broadband network Share Tweet this Email Gabrielle Chan , political correspondent theguardian.com , Thursday 3 October 2013 02.41 EDT Link to video: Malcolm Turnbull announces the appointment of Ziggy Switkowski as NBN Co chair Ziggy Switkowski has been appointed chairman of NBN Co, but only two directors out of Labor's seven existing board members survived the change of government. Switkowski has also been appointed interim executive chair to replace outgoing boss Mike Quigley, while Kerry Schott and Alison Lansley will remain as directors. The communications minister, Malcolm Turnbull , announced the decision after Tony Abbott's second cabinet meeting on Thursday. Turnbull also ordered NBN Co to conduct a strategic review to give the government a clearer indication of the progress and cost of the network, including the &quot;economic viability&quot; of &quot;alternative strategies&quot;. More details soon ... Print this Share Contact us Send to a friend Sender&amp;#39;s name Recipient's email address Your IP address will be logged Share Short link for this page: http://gu.com/p/3j8pp StumbleUpon reddit Tumblr Digg LinkedIn Google Bookmarks del.icio.us livejournal Facebook Twitter Contact us Contact the Technology editor tech@theguardian.com Report errors or inaccuracies: userhelp@theguardian.com Letters for publication should be sent to: letters@theguardian.com If you need help using the site: userhelp@theguardian.com Call the main Guardian and Observer switchboard: +44 (0)20 3353 2000 Advertising guide License/buy our content Article history About this article Ziggy Switkowski appointed chairman of NBN Co This article was published on the Guardian website at 02.41 EDT on Thursday 3 October 2013 . It was last modified at 02.44 EDT on Thursday 3 October 2013 . Technology National Broadband Network (NBN) World news Malcolm Turnbull &amp;middot; Australia &amp;middot; Coalition &amp;middot; Australian politics More news Share Tweet this Email Today's best video Tiger cub born at London Zoo The moment a tiger gives birth to London Zoo's first tiger cub in 17 years is captured by hidden cameras Does the future belong to the Tories? John Harris reports from the Conservative party conference Plane's emergency landing on Florida road A pilot is forced to land his plane on a road Mesut Özil lauded by Arsène Wenger Arsenal manager praises midfielder after 2-0 Champions League win over Napoli On the Guardian today World news 'Revenge porn' outlawed in California Technology GTA V Online launches, popularity could cause server issues Technology Rockstar says sorry for Grand Theft Auto Online launch problems Film Mia Farrow: Woody Allen's son Ronan may be Frank Sinatra's World news US shutdown: fruitless talks leave bitter stalemate in place Technology FBI claims largest Bitcoin seizure after arrest of alleged Silk Road founder Sponsored feature Today in pictures BBC Sports Personality of the Year – in pictures Bradley Wiggins capped his remarkable sporting year by taking home the big prize at the ceremony in London Dinner, dusk and dancing Russians: my best winter shot A glass of wine with a rough sleeper, Santa in trunks, a thousand partying Muscovites … in a My Best Shot special, top photographers pick the image that sums up winter for them Monkey adopts kitten – in pictures Kimon, an eight-year-old pet female long-tailed monkey, treats a kitten as her baby in Bintan Island, Indonesia Key topics Apple Google Facebook Games blog Game reviews License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US advertising | A - Z index | About us &amp;#169; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) Share Tweet this ;
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:44:58
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Malcolm Turnbull announces the appointment of Ziggy Switkowski as NBN Co chair – video
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Technology news, comment and analysis | theguardian.com
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.theguardian.com/c/34708/f/663871/s/31ff433f/sc/25/l/0L0Stheguardian0N0Ctechnology0Cvideo0C20A130Coct0C0A30Cturnbull0Eannounces0Eziggy0Eswitkowski0Enbn0Evideo/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author/>
      <content>
        Malcolm Turnbull announces the appointment of Ziggy Switkowski as NBN Co chair – video | Technology | theguardian.com Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life &amp;amp; style Data News Technology National Broadband Network (NBN) Malcolm Turnbull announces the appointment of Ziggy Switkowski as NBN Co chair – video Former Telstra boss and nuclear physicist Dr Ziggy Switkowski will lead a three-person board overseeing the national broadband network, the biggest infrastructure project in Australia. Switkowski replaces Siohban McKenna as NBN chair and will be joined by the only two survivors of the former NBN Co board, Kerry Schott and Alison Lansley Source: Parlview Length: 1min 30sec theguardian.com Thursday 3 October 2013 Share Tweet this Email Share Embed Autoplay settings Send to a friend Sender&amp;#39;s name Recipient's email address Your IP address will be logged Video play settings Autoplay is on | Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on | Autoplay is off When autoplay is on, videos on these pages will autoplay More about our videos Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off More about our videos Share Short link for this page: http://gu.com/p/3j8py StumbleUpon reddit Tumblr Digg LinkedIn Google Bookmarks del.icio.us livejournal Facebook Twitter Embed video Copy and paste the embed code below Terms and conditions of use Technology videos Malcolm Turnbull announces the appointment of Ziggy Switkowski as NBN Co chair 03 Oct 2013 1:30 Forza Motorsport 5: new gameplay trailer 02 Oct 2013 2:02 Google Glass: video user guide released 01 May 2013 1:21 Skylanders Swap Force: announcement trailer 08 Feb 2013 2:18 Xbox One hands-on preview event 26 Sep 2013 3:48 Tesco Hudl tablet first look 23 Sep 2013 3:07 GTA V: first heist playthrough 17 Sep 2013 16:39 Ceatec 2013: Japan's biggest consumer technology show 01 Oct 2013 1:49 Most popular Tiger cub born at London zoo 02 Oct 2013 1:08 Plane conducts emergency landing on Florida highway 02 Oct 2013 1:08 South Park spoofs the NSA and social networking 02 Oct 2013 0:42 Sir Alex Ferguson: Manchester United is ‘my team, my club’ 02 Oct 2013 1:35 Conservative conference: does the future belong to them? 02 Oct 2013 7:47 Mesut Özil lauded by Arsène Wenger after Arsenal beat Napoli in Champions League 02 Oct 2013 1:23 How will the US government shutdown affect the global economy? 01 Oct 2013 3:57 Brazil: teachers' pay protest in Rio erupts into violence 02 Oct 2013 1:27 Related video Malcolm Turnbull defends original internet filter plan on ABC's Triple J - audio 06 Sep 2013 1:49 Election 2013: Day 4 campaign video roundup 08 Aug 2013 2:11 GCSE results: exams have been marked fairly, say Edexcel 23 Aug 2012 0:42 Kevin Rudd on Rupert Murdoch, interest rates and the economy 06 Aug 2013 5:10 Kevin Rudd on 7:30: Murdoch and the NBN 08 Aug 2013 1:35 Tony Abbott on Murdoch, NBN and Rudd 08 Aug 2013 1:02 Danny Alexander: building projects could boost UK economy by £50bn 18 Jul 2012 1:33 Brian Cox explains the forces of nature 04 Mar 2011 12:34 Related topics Technology National Broadband Network (NBN) World news Malcolm Turnbull &amp;middot; Australia &amp;middot; Australian Capital Territory (ACT) &amp;middot; Australian politics More video Sponsored feature Key topics Apple Google Facebook Games blog Game reviews License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US advertising | A - Z index | About us &amp;#169; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) ;
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:33:18
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Boot up: benchmark cheats, HTC v Nokia, M7 monitored and more
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Technology news, comment and analysis | theguardian.com
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.theguardian.com/c/34708/f/663871/s/31ff4340/sc/5/l/0L0Stheguardian0N0Ctechnology0Cblog0C20A130Coct0C0A30Csamsung0Egear0Ebenchmarks0Em7/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        Charles Arthur
      </author>
      <content>
        Boot up: benchmark cheats, HTC v Nokia, M7 monitored and more | Technology | theguardian.com Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to comments [c] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life &amp;amp; style Data News Technology Technology blog Previous Blog home Boot up: benchmark cheats, HTC v Nokia, M7 monitored and more Plus how Microsoft plans to sell more Surfaces, inside story of the Galaxy Gear, Note 10.1 review roundup, and more Share Tweet this Email Climbing a spiral staircase: will your gadget monitor your steps? Photograph: Robert Frerck/Getty Images A burst of 8 links for you to chew over, as picked by the Technology team HTC works with Qualcomm to avoid US ban on phones &amp;gt;&amp;gt; WSJ.com A US International Trade Commission judge last week issued a preliminary ruling that HTC infringed on two Nokia patents that enhance transmission and reception of phone calls. Nokia's filings with the commission said that the chip covered by the patents was made by Qualcomm. Only older HTC phone models were listed in the case. But the HTC One smartphone and other new devices use the same technology that would be banned if the commission decides in January to uphold its initial ruling, two people familiar with the matter said. Nokia said it believed that the One also violated the Finnish company's patents and would be included under any ban. Things are going from bad to worse for HTC. Galaxy Note 10.1 2014 Edition review roundup: Is this a 10.1 inch Android tablet worth buying? &amp;gt;&amp;gt; Android Beat Let an Android site tell you. More M7 details: data storage, battery life, Android motion coprocessor adoption &amp;gt;&amp;gt; 9to5Mac Azumio has been hoping for a motion coprocessor for quite some time. Rather than having the battery-hog CPU running all the time, placing in a motion coprocessor allows the phone to store all of the information while the CPU can sleep or focus on other tasks. The company told me they were in talks with Android manufacturers about placing motion coprocessors in their phones, and now that Apple has been boasting about this new piece of hardware, there's a good chance other manufacturers will follow suit. The Moto X has its own version of motion tracking and 4.3 includes support for activity detection, but nothing matches the low-power capabilities of the M7. Azumio consumes 25-30% of battery power on non-iPhone 5S devices - a ridiculous amount for something devoted to telling you how many steps you've taken (a pedometer is cheaper and uses zero battery). Let's hope that better uses for the M7 and other coprocessors come along soon. How Microsoft plans to sell millions of Surface tablets to businesses &amp;gt;&amp;gt; CITEworld Surface Commercial director Cyril Belikoff told me that the ARM-based version of Surface - the version that doesn't run traditional Windows apps, and which has sold poorly at retail so far - is actually notching up bigger wins with corporate customers. That's because a lot of companies haven't done any large scale tablet deployments yet, and they're looking to the ARM-based Surface RT (old) or Surface 2 (new) as their first line-of-business tablet. They often build custom apps for these tablets, sometimes locking them down so users can only access these apps, and deploy them all at once to employees in particular functions, like retail or mobile salespeople. In contrast, the Surface Pro is more of a laptop replacement, and will probably trickle in to enterprises according to their regular PC refresh cycle of maybe 10% to 20% new PCs per year. Moreover, some companies are still buying Windows 7 laptops instead of or alongside Windows 8 machines. How Samsung cranked out the Galaxy Gear: The inside story &amp;gt;&amp;gt; CNET News In the case of Gear, the company started testing concept designs in early 2011. Key features and the decision to move forward with a product came in part from surveys Samsung conducted more than a year ago, said Young-hee Lee, the Samsung executive vice president who oversees mobile marketing. Samsung didn't ask people if they wanted smartwatches. Instead, it sought to find out more about what people find annoying with smartphones. Samsung concluded that a big concern for people was missing out on things in the time it takes to get out their phones, such as not being able to take a photo fast enough. That contributed to plans for a camera in the Gear band. Once Samsung had that survey data in hand, it was time to get high-level executives on board. It's unclear who spearheaded Gear - Samsung won't say - but top executives championing Gear early on included Shin and DJ Lee, president and head of sales and marketing for Samsung's mobile business. Once top management made the decision to build the product, things started to come together quickly. &quot;We put all things together and said let's just go for it,&quot; Young-hee Lee told CNET. They're (almost) all dirty: the state of cheating in Android benchmarks &amp;gt;&amp;gt; AnandTech With the exception of Apple and Motorola, literally every single OEM we've worked with ships (or has shipped) at least one device that runs this silly CPU optimization. It's possible that older Motorola devices might've done the same thing, but none of the newer devices we have on hand exhibited the behavior. It's a systemic problem that seems to have surfaced over the last two years, and one that extends far beyond Samsung. Looking at the table above you'll also notice weird inconsistencies about the devices/OEMs that choose to implement the cheat/hack/festivities. None of the Nexus do, which is understandable since the optimization isn't a part of AOSP. This also helps explain why the Nexus 4 performed so slowly when we reviewed it - this mess was going on back then and Google didn't partake. The table that shows who boosts performance for which benchmark is very revealing. Why are people worrying about the NSA stealing their fingerprints? &amp;gt;&amp;gt; VICE UK &quot;We have no set of rules for this yet – there is no convention on what happens and what can be done,&quot; Sam Smith from privacy rights organisation Privacy International told me. &quot;Can the police technically force you to unlock your phone if it's fingerprinted? The police would argue that they can, but they don't get to unilaterally make the rules.&quot; That said, perhaps the paranoia about police being able to access your devices with a copied fingerprint is already hugely outdated. According to Val Swain from NetPol, a police watchdog group, this kind of thing has already been going on for years: &quot;The police routinely download information from mobile phones when anyone is taken into custody, using an ACESO device. This claims to be able to access data from smartphones, including Blackberry devices, even when they are password protected. &quot;It is not clear whether the use of fingerprint locks on mobile phones would be a significant hurdle for the police, or whether the ASECO reader is – or would quickly become – capable of by-passing the requirement for a fingerprint,&quot; she continued. &quot;We would need more technological data in order to know that.&quot; And due to the interest of private sector companies in creating this kind of technology, Val suspects &quot;an answer to Apple's fingerprint technology will not be far behind&quot;. Britain's Times to pull Blackberry app due to lack of interest &amp;gt;&amp;gt; Reuters Britain's The Times newspaper said on Tuesday it would no longer make its mobile app available on a Blackberry because few people used it, in another sign that rival smartphone makers are trumping its technology. Get it before 31 October, or don't get it at all. You can follow Guardian Technology's linkbucket on Pinboard To suggest a link, either add it below or tag it with @gdntech on the free Delicious service. Sign up for the Guardian Today Our editors' picks for the day's top news and commentary delivered to your inbox each morning. Sign up for the daily email Posted by Charles Arthur Thursday 3 October 2013 02.30 EDT theguardian.com Jump to comments ( &amp;hellip; ) Print this Share Contact us Send to a friend Sender&amp;#39;s name Recipient's email address Your IP address will be logged Share Short link for this page: http://gu.com/p/3j8ny StumbleUpon reddit Tumblr Digg LinkedIn Google Bookmarks del.icio.us livejournal Facebook Twitter Contact us Contact the Technology editor tech@theguardian.com Report errors or inaccuracies: userhelp@theguardian.com Letters for publication should be sent to: letters@theguardian.com If you need help using the site: userhelp@theguardian.com Call the main Guardian and Observer switchboard: +44 (0)20 3353 2000 Advertising guide License/buy our content Article history About this article Boot up: benchmark cheats, HTC v Nokia, M7 monitored and more This article was published on the Guardian website at 02.30 EDT on Thursday 3 October 2013 . It was last modified at 02.30 EDT on Thursday 3 October 2013 . Technology Microsoft &amp;middot; Apple &amp;middot; Google Series Newsbucket More from Technology blog on Technology Microsoft &amp;middot; Apple &amp;middot; Google Series Newsbucket More blogposts More news Previous Blog home Share Tweet this Email Comments Click here to join the discussion . We can't load the discussion on theguardian.com because you don't have JavaScript enabled . Today's best video Tiger cub born at London Zoo The moment a tiger gives birth to London Zoo's first tiger cub in 17 years is captured by hidden cameras Does the future belong to the Tories? John Harris reports from the Conservative party conference Plane's emergency landing on Florida road A pilot is forced to land his plane on a road Mesut Özil lauded by Arsène Wenger Arsenal manager praises midfielder after 2-0 Champions League win over Napoli On the Guardian today World news 'Revenge porn' outlawed in California Technology GTA V Online launches, popularity could cause server issues Technology Rockstar says sorry for Grand Theft Auto Online launch problems Film Mia Farrow: Woody Allen's son Ronan may be Frank Sinatra's World news US shutdown: fruitless talks leave bitter stalemate in place Technology FBI claims largest Bitcoin seizure after arrest of alleged Silk Road founder Sponsored feature More from Newsbucket Previous: 2 Oct 2013: Boot up: Windows creep, Samsung's benchmark, Guardian Reddits, and more Newsbucket index Key topics Apple Google Facebook Games blog Game reviews License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US advertising | A - Z index | About us &amp;#169; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) Share Tweet this ;
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:30:03
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Leser geben Berlin-Tipps: Ein Tag zum Feiern in der Hauptstadt
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        SPIEGEL ONLINE - Schlagzeilen
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.spiegel.de/reise/deutschland/tag-der-deutschen-einheit-leser-geben-berlin-tipps-a-925798.html#ref=rss
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        None
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:21:33
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Weltweite Umfrage zu Status: Lehrer werden in Deutschland kaum respektiert
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        SPIEGEL ONLINE - Schlagzeilen
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.spiegel.de/schulspiegel/ausland/weltweite-umfrage-deutsche-lehrer-werden-kaum-respektiert-a-925826.html#ref=rss
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        None
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:18:11
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Rampant cheating by Android knockoffs prompts AnTuTu to launch new benchmark
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        AppleInsider - Frontpage News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://appleinsider.com.feedsportal.com/c/33975/f/616168/s/31ff10c1/sc/5/l/0Lappleinsider0N0Carticles0C130C10A0C0A30Crampant0Echeating0Eby0Eandroid0Eknockoffs0Eprompts0Eantutu0Eto0Elaunch0Enew0Ebenchmark/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        None
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:50:45
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        IndieCade 2013 Festival finalists to receive Desura distribution
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Polygon -  All
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.polygon.com/2013/10/3/4797612/indiecade-2013-festival-finalists-to-receive-desura-distribution
      </link>
      <author>
        Jenna Pitcher
      </author>
      <content>
        IndieCade 2013 Festival finalists to receive Desura distribution | Polygon Menu Polygon News Reports Opinion Culture Recent All News Reviews Recent Nintendo Playstation Xbox Mobile PC/Mac All Reviews Features This Week Last Week Human Angle All Features Videos Recent Today I Played Speed Run Cooperatives Mobile Watch List Human Angle All Videos Forums Recent Polynauts Off-Topic Playstation 4 Xbox One Wii U Meta All Forums Games Just Released Coming Soon Highest Scored All Games Platforms Nintendo Wii U Wii 3DS Playstation Playstation 4 Playstation 3 Playstation Vita Xbox Xbox One Xbox 360 Mobile iOS Android PC / Mac Windows OS X More Platforms Nintendo Playstation Xbox Mobile PC / Mac RSS Feeds All News Reviews Features The Besties Who We Are Jobs Pitch a Story Contact Us Close Login News Reports Opinion Culture News Forums Reviews Games Platforms Nintendo Playstation Xbox Mobile PC / Mac Features Videos All Videos Speed Run Today I Played Cooperatives Human Angle More Who We Are Jobs Pitch a Story Contact Us Stay Connected. Follow Polygon Now! IndieCade 2013 Festival finalists to receive Desura distribution By Jenna Pitcher on Oct 03, 2013 at 2:59a Share Tweet Share IndieCade 2013 Festival finalists will be offered a global distribution agreement on digital distribution platform, Desura, Linden Lab and IndieCade announced today. The bars fees and is only offered to Windows PC, Linux and Mac festival finalists. Finalists will also become part of Desura's new partner program and which includes promotional advertising offered by Linden Lab. &quot;We're a proud supporter of IndieCade and its mission,&quot; said Rod Humble, CEO of Linden Lab. &quot;Celebrating and supporting independent developers is a goal Desura shares with IndieCade, and we're happy to be able to award distribution and promotion to all nominated and official selection games at this year's event.&quot; The IndieCade 2013 Festival runs Oct. 5-6 in Los Angeles. Tap for more stories Source LindenLab Via VG247 Previous Next ← → More Content &amp;#x25a4; about polygon &amp;bull; Jobs &amp;bull; Ethics statement Community Guidelines &amp;bull; Terms of use &amp;bull; Privacy Policy &amp;bull; RSS &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media Inc. all rights reserved &amp;bull; Designed and Developed in house 1.6 Aug 1, 2013 top of page home &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media Inc. all rights reserved Designed in house X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:59:22
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Register
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://go.theregister.com/feed/www.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/so_i_wouldnt_start_from_here/
      </link>
      <author>
        StorageBod
      </author>
      <content>
        How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy • The Register Skip to content Whitepapers | The Channel Data Center Software Networks Security Policy Business Jobs Hardware Science Bootnotes Columnists Forums Servers HPC Cloud Storage Data Networking Virtualisation BOFH Data Center &gt; Storage How to design a storage array: NOT LIKE THAT, buddy Architecture might all look samey, but it's like that for a reason By StorageBod , 3rd October 2013 Post a comment Related stories Storagebod When the SSD came to storage land: How flashy upstarts got their break 5 years in storage: Flash mutants, big data and (WTF is) the cloud Storagebod Those vendor blog sods fog the cogs. Wish they'd slog for user bods Storagebod Storage rage: Like getting a nice steak and being told to only eat 80% of it Supercharge your infrastructure Storagebod We’ve had a few announcements from vendors recently and I've seen all manner of storage roadmaps. If I had one comment to make on all of these, it would be to say that if I were to design an array or a storage product, I probably wouldn’t start from where most of these guys are starting. There appears to be a real fixation on the past, with lots of architectures which are simply re-inventing what has gone before. And although I understand why, I don’t understand why. Stick with me here. Let’s take the legacy vendors. You can’t change things because you will break everything: you will break the existing customer scripts and legacy automation, you will break processes and understanding. So essentially, the vendor can’t build a new architecture because it breaks everything. I get the argument, but I don’t necessarily agree with the result. And then we have the new kids on the block, which want to continue building yesterday’s architecture today. “We’ll build something based on a dual-head filer,” they say, “because everyone knows how to do that and they understand the architecture.” Yet again: I get the argument but I really don’t agree with the result. I’m going to take the new vendors' situation first. If I wished to buy a dual-head filer, I’d probably buy it from one of the leaders of the pack. Certainly if I were a big storage customer, it would be very hard for one of the new vendors get it down to a price that is attractive. Now, you may argue that your new kit is so much better than the legacy vendors that it is worth the extra hassle, but you will almost certainly break my automation and existing processes. Is it really worth that level of disruption? The first situation with the legacy vendors is more interesting. Can I take the new product and make it feel like the old stuff from a management point of view? If storage is truly software (and the management layer is certainly software), I don’t see that it should be beyond the wit of developers to make your new architecture feel like the old stuff. Okay, you might strip out some of the old legacy constructs. You might even fake them ... so if a script creates a LUN utilising a legacy construct, you just fake the responses. There are some more interesting issues around performance and monitoring, but as a whole, the industry is so very poor at it. Breaking this is not such a major issue. Capacity planning and management: well, how many people really do this? The really big customers likely do it, but they might well be the ones who will look at leveraging new technology without a translation layer. So if I were a vendor, I would be looking at ways to make my storage “plug-compatible” with what has gone before – but under the covers, so to speak. I’d be looking for ways to do it a whole lot better and I wouldn’t be afraid to upset some of my legacy engineering teams. I’d build a platform on top of which I could stick &quot;personalities&quot;. And it’s not just about a common look and feel for the GUI, I'd engineer the same for the CLI and the APIs. My advice to the new kids: make the change easy by reducing the friction. ® 5 ways to prepare your advertising infrastructure for disaster Post a comment Previous Story Whitepapers Microsoft’s Cloud OS System Center Virtual Machine manager and how this product allows the level of virtualization abstraction to move from individual physical computers and clusters to unifying the whole Data Centre as an abstraction layer. 5 ways to prepare your advertising infrastructure for disaster Being prepared allows your brand to greatly improve your advertising infrastructure performance and reliability that, in the end, will boost confidence in your brand. Supercharge your infrastructure Fusion­‐io has developed a shared storage solution that provides new performance management capabilities required to maximize flash utilization. High Performance for All While HPC is not new, it has traditionally been seen as a specialist area – is it now geared up to meet more mainstream requirements? Avere FXT with FlashMove and FlashMirror This ESG Lab validation report documents hands-on testing of the Avere FXT Series Edge Filer with the AOS 3.0 operating environment. Search more Resources More from The Register Multipath TCP: Siri's new toy isn't a game-changer This experiment is an alpha and carriers could swat it like a bug 68 Ellison ditches own cloud keynote for billionaires' America's Cup boat race Mass exodus after King Database snubs attendees 42 Barmy Army to get Wi-Fi to the seat for cricket's Ashes Sydney Test Match will offer replays to the smartmobe 14 How many apps does it take to back up your data? Trevor Pott counts the ways 28 Dedupe-dedupe, dedupe-dedupe-dedupe: Flashy clients crowd around Permabit diamond 3 of the top six flash vendors are casing the OEM dedupe tech, claims analyst 8 Seagate to storage bods: You CAN touch this (at last). Stop, HAMR time We've talked about it for a while... next month, you'll actually *see* it 15 Disk-pushers, get reel: Even GOOGLE relies on tape Prepare to be beaten by your old, cheap rival 13 French data cops to Google: RIGHT, you had your chance. PUNISHMENT time Prepare yourself for fines, snarls CNIL 63 Dragons' Den star's biz Outsourcery sends yet more millions up in smoke Telly moneybags went into the cloud and still nobody's making any profit 15 Hong Kong's data centres stay high and dry amid Typhoon Usagi 180 km/h winds kill 25 in China, but the data centres keep humming 9 Most read TUPPERWARE FOUND ON MOON of Saturn Microsoft investors push for Bill Gates defenestration: report GTA V Online hits speed bumps: Short delay before you can rough up that hooker 500 MEELLION PCs still run Windows XP. How did we get here? Review Ubuntu 13.10: Meet the Linux distro with a bizarre Britney Spears fixation Spotlight Oracle muscles way into seat atop the benchmark with hefty ZFS filer How many apps does it take to back up your data? 28 Five reasons why you'll take your storage to the cloud 25 Tracking the history of magnetic tape: A game of noughts and crosses 28 Just how flash is your enterprise storage rig? 11 Gorillas, StorageBeers, sexy flash models: It's all here in Speaking in Tech Got it taped: The business of tape-based disaster recovery 10 Cloud storage: Is the convenience worth the extra expense? 16 Is storage kicking servers in the battle of the bundles? Storage rage: Like getting a nice steak and being told to only eat 80% of it 54 Object storage: The blob creeping from niche to mainstream 12 Speaking in Tech: 'I'm not a pimp just because I wear a fedora' MORE More from the Register Send us News Tips Week’s Headlines Reg Archive Top 20 Stories eBooks Webcasts The Channel Privacy Advertise with Us Company Info © Copyright 1998–2013
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:02:48
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        'Instant translation' glasses to come online for 2020 Olympics
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        The Register
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://go.theregister.com/feed/www.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/ntt_docomo_5g_google_glass_translation/
      </link>
      <author>
        Phil Muncaster
      </author>
      <content>
        'Instant translation' glasses to come online for 2020 Olympics • The Register Skip to content Whitepapers | The Channel Data Center Software Networks Security Policy Business Jobs Hardware Science Bootnotes Columnists Forums Mobile Broadband networks &gt; Broadband 'Instant translation' glasses to come online for 2020 Olympics Japan's NTT Docomo plans 5G network 100 times faster than LTE at Tokyo's games By Phil Muncaster , 3rd October 2013 Post a comment Related stories Japan's largest mobe operator to snub Samsung this winter Analysis Who is Samsung trying to kid? There will NEVER be a 5G network Marketecture wars Samsung sends gigabit '5G' signal TWO WHOLE KILOMETRES NTT Docomo leads 5G push with 10Gbps uplink tests Free ESG report : Seamless data management with Avere FXT NTT Docomo has wasted no time ramping up the excitement ahead of the Tokyo Olympic Games, in announcing a 5G network 100 times faster than LTE and augmented reality “instant translation” glasses – both of which should be ready by 2020. Both innovations were unveiled at IT and electronics show CEATEC 2013 in Tokyo this week. It’s still early days for the network technology – at least, all the Japanese operator seems to have brought to the show was a small illustrated chart snapped by Slashgear . However, it reveals that NTT Docomo is hoping to create a super-speedy network 100 times faster and 1,000 times the capacity of LTE. There’s not much else in the way of detail, apart from the fact the firm is hoping to tap higher frequencies, given that the sub-3GHz space is getting crowded, with small cells used to boost coverage in certain areas. Although NTT conducted a 10Gbps test back in March, it isn’t the first to announce 5G plans. Huawei already showed its hand back in August, speaking of a similarly uber-fast network, and Samsung has demonstrated 1Gbps wireless technology. As El Reg has pointed out in the past, any such associated standard certainly hasn’t been ratified yet and will probably not be called “5G” when it is, but in the absence of any other term, it’ll have to do. On the other front, NTT Docomo showed off its answer to Google Glass – Intelligent Glasses which can translate text on-the-fly. A demo seen by the Beeb put translation time for the prototype at a lengthy five seconds, although improved speeds will certainly come as the technology is honed. They could certainly be popular among tourists to Japan in 2020, although having struggled with hilariously mis-translated menus many times before abroad, those algorithms will have to be spot on for the glasses to be useful. Other features include the ability to interact with a flat surface as if it was a touchscreen, with a specially designed ring worn by the user recording and relaying hand movements. The glasses can apparently also bring up the personal details of people in their line of vision, using facial recognition software – holding out the tantalising prospect of never again being embarrassed after forgetting someone’s name at a party. ® Free ESG report : Seamless data management with Avere FXT Post a comment Previous Story Whitepapers 5 ways to prepare your advertising infrastructure for disaster Being prepared allows your brand to greatly improve your advertising infrastructure performance and reliability that, in the end, will boost confidence in your brand. High Performance for All While HPC is not new, it has traditionally been seen as a specialist area – is it now geared up to meet more mainstream requirements? Email delivery: Hate phishing emails? You'll love DMARC DMARC has been created as a standard to help properly authenticate your sends and monitor and report phishers that are trying to send from your name.. Reg Reader Research: SaaS based Email and Office Productivity Tools Read this Reg reader report which provides advice and guidance for SMBs towards the use of SaaS based email and Office productivity tools. Email delivery: 4 steps to get more email to the inbox This whitepaper lists some steps and information that will give you the best opportunity to achieve an amazing sender reputation. Search more Resources More from The Register US.gov - including NASA et al - quits internet. Is the UN running it now? 'Due to a lapse in funding, the US federal government has shut down' 103 MPs slam bumpkin fibre rollout, demand halt to further £250m cash spaff And an end to BT's 'quasi-monopoly' 43 EE still has fastest, fattest 4G pipe in London's M25 ring RootMetrics unfurls crowd-sourced 4G coverage map 27 Report says PRISM snooped on India's space, nuclear programs New Snowden doc details extensive NSA surveillance of 'ally' India 37 Facebook sharpens ad-shifting tool: Soon users will eat creepily SPECIFIC ad-gloop Just an algorithm tweak and you're all mine ... bitch 23 Highways Agency tracks Brits' every move by their mobes: THE TRUTH We better go back to just scanning everyone's number-plates, then? 65 Google tentacle slips over YouTube comments: Now YOUR MUM is at the top Ad giant tries to dab some polish on the cesspit of the internet 49 WHY didn't Microsoft buy RIM? Us business blokes would have queued for THAT phone Nothing cuts it if you're a sysadmin 124 AT&amp;amp;T takes on Google fiber, fixin' to give Texans GIGABIT GUNS 1Gbps, to a few people, some of the time 10 Reg readers! You've got 100 MILLION QUID - what would you BLOW it on? Because Ofcom wants to know what to do with its lolly 63 Most read TUPPERWARE FOUND ON MOON of Saturn Microsoft investors push for Bill Gates defenestration: report GTA V Online hits speed bumps: Short delay before you can rough up that hooker 500 MEELLION PCs still run Windows XP. How did we get here? Review Ubuntu 13.10: Meet the Linux distro with a bizarre Britney Spears fixation Spotlight Reg hack battles Margaret Thatcher's ghost to bring broadband to the Highlands 49 Spending watchdog SAVAGES rural broadband push 39 Broadband rivals 'pleased' over Ofcom's market shake-up plans. Maybe too pleased 33 UK.gov finally admits it will MISS superfast broadband target 35 All major UK ISPs prepping network-level porn 'n' violence filters 171 Watchdog warns UK.gov not to create 'them and us' digital divide 48 Virgin Media boss to Osbo: Bung city fibre cash into small biz 16 WE CAN still be BETTER than Germany on broadband, says Ofcom 25 Use your loaf, Europe! Eat more fibre - high-speed web lobbyists 58 Reg readers! You've got 100 MILLION QUID - what would you BLOW it on? 63 Nokia drives cars into the clouds: Hear HERE, you're here, hear? 39 OWN GOAL! 100s of websites blocked after UK Premier League drops ball 133 MORE More from the Register Send us News Tips Week’s Headlines Reg Archive Top 20 Stories eBooks Webcasts The Channel Privacy Advertise with Us Company Info © Copyright 1998–2013
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:33:12
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        PhoneArena - News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.phonearena.com/news/Target-makes-Brightspot-official-with-October-6th-launch-for-the-pre-paid-carrier_id47927
      </link>
      <author>
        Phone Arena
      </author>
      <content>
        Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier x PhoneArena is looking for new authors! To view all available positions, click here. PhoneArena All Phones Reviews News Search Share this page Facebook Twitter Digg Follow us: Login Register Home Phones Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile View all Manufacturers Samsung HTC LG BlackBerry Motorola Apple Nokia Sony View all Phone tools Phone finder New phones Popular phones Compare phones Size compare Best phones Camera comparison Tablets Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile Manufacturers Apple Samsung Motorola BlackBerry Tablet tools Tablet finder New tablets Popular tablets Compare tablets News Reviews Discussions Videos Tip us Phone Links Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile more &amp;raquo; Brands Samsung Motorola HTC LG BlackBerry Apple Nokia more &amp;raquo; Tools Phone Finder Compare Size compare Camera comparison Best phones Home &amp;rsaquo; News &amp;rsaquo; Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier Posted: 03 Oct 2013, 01:59 , by Alan F. Categories: T-Mobile T-Mobile Wireless service Wireless service Share: Discuss 1 Tweet On Tuesday, we told you about a tweet from evleaks that revealed all of the important information for Target's new pre-paid carrier service powered by T-Mobile. Brightspot has now been officially announced by the discount retailer and will open for business on October 6th. There are two options available. For $35, you receive unlimited talk and text with no data. For $50, you receive the unlimited talk and text and web. Here is the deal with the unlimited web. Each month you are allowed to consume 1GB of T-Mobile's best vintage 4G data. Exceed that 1GB cap and you are throttled. The MVNO does have some interesting perks. Every 6 months you will receive a $25 Target gift card and Target REDcard holders can take a 5% discount on each plan. If you want to use your own phone, SIM kits will be available for unlocked GSM phones. &quot;We know guests are looking for customizable and convenient mobile plans that won’t break the bank. Starting Oct. 6, Target will offer guests more options and flexibility with brightspot, the Bullseye’s fresh, new mobile program. brightspot brings together the mobile phone plans you want with the devices you desire.&quot; -Target We haven't seen an official list of phones being offered for Brightspot, but one of our loyal readers sent us a picture of the Alcatel One Touch Fierce packaged specifically for the service. This device offers a 4.5 inch screen with a resolution of 540 x 960 (qHD). A MediaTek quad-core 1.2GHz processor is on hand with 1GB of RAM on board. 4GB of native storage can be expanded using a microSD card, and there is an 1800mAh cell keeping the lights on. Back and front cameras weigh in at 5MP and .3MP respectively, and Android 4.2 is pre-installed. We should point out that the device has connectivity for 21Mbps HSPA+ 4G. There is no LTE connectivity with the device. Although pricing is unknown, T-Mobile was charging its own customers $19.99 down and 24 monthly payments of $6 ($163.99) for the model. Target announces its pre-paid carrier Brightspot Fullscreen More popular slideshows iOS 7 release date and time are today (Sep 18), get ready to update! 18 Sep 2013, 04:00 How to download and install the iOS 7 update to your iPhone, iPad or iPod touch 18 Sep 2013, 18:04 Samsung Galaxy Note 3 display ranks on par with the best, AMOLED hugely improved 2 days ago, 10:05 Apple iPhone 5s performance review: CPU and GPU speed compared to top Android phones (benchmarks) 25 Sep 2013, 06:47 Best new Android, iPhone and Windows Phone apps for September 2013 yesterday, 04:54 Sony Honami mini is real: first image and specs surface in Japan, phone to be called Xperia Z1 f 3 days ago, 07:26 Android 4.4 KitKat update: release date, features and rumors 23 Sep 2013, 10:25 Apple iPhone 5s slow motion camera feature inspires video art 3 days ago, 08:37 Apple iPhone 5S: 7 new features of the seventh generation iPhone 10 Sep 2013, 07:02 The Evolution of Android, 5 years later 24 Sep 2013, 09:12 double click to zoom in and out &amp;lsaquo; PREV 1 of 2 NEXT &amp;rsaquo; image image View As One Page &amp;raquo; View As Slideshow &amp;raquo; Target announces its pre-paid carrier Brightspot 1. 2. Thanks, Anonymous Tipster! source: Target via TmoNews Share: Discuss 1 Tweet Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo 03 Oct Prev news Close Now reading: Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid 03 Oct Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo 03 Oct HTC's market value is at an 8-year low; the end may be near 03 Oct Demand for low to mid-range 4G LTE handsets to rise in 2014 03 Oct BBM beta testing starts again with new version of the app 03 Oct Apple seeds iOS 7.0.3 to employees and partners as more bugs are found 02 Oct Rumored LG G Flex has a curved screen and an expected November unveiling 02 Oct Leaked iPad 5 casing fits iPhone 5s fingerprint scanner &quot;perfectly&quot; 02 Oct Amazon smartphone rumors return, claiming 3D user interface 02 Oct Apple could ship 5x more iPad 5 units than iPad mini 2 02 Oct older posts Featured stories Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white LG G Flex to sport curved screen? Nexus 5 to have fastest smartphone camera Nexus 5 coming last week of October, says new rumor Best new Android, iPhone and Windows Phone apps for September 2013 LG and Samsung to introduce curved display smartphones 1 Comments Follow Following Options Close Show comments: default hide low rated show moderated comments Display mode: Threaded Chronological Newest first Save posted on 8 min ago 1 Reply 1. ocilfa (Posts: 132; Member since: 03 Aug 2012) Meh, I kind of think they missed the &quot;target&quot;. Want to comment? Please login or register . Home &amp;rsaquo; News &amp;rsaquo; Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid carrier Popular stories Last week Last 2 days Most commented 1. Nexus 5 to be first smartphone with MEMS camera: fastest on a phone, Lytro like functionality 2. Samsung is now locking all new devices to a region, making life hard 3. Best gadgets of 2013: our favorites so far 4. Road map reveals Android 4.3 update for Samsung Galaxy S4, Galaxy S III and GALAXY Note II 1 2 3 4 Recent Articles Apple iPhone 5s performance review: CPU and GPU speed compared to top Android phones (benchmarks) The Evolution of Android, 5 years later Clash of the titans: iOS 7 vs Android 4.3 comparison 1 2 3 4 Hot Phones Apple iPhone 5s Announced: 10 Sep 2013 OS: iOS Hardware: Dual core, 1300 MHz Display: 4.0 inches, 640 x 1136 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 8 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) 1280x720 (720p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Samsung Galaxy S4 Announced: 14 Mar 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1900 MHz, Krait 300, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.0 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS LG G2 Announced: 07 Aug 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 2260 MHz, Krait 400, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.2 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900), CDMA (800 1900) Data: LTE-A LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS EV-DO Rev.A Sony Xperia Z1 Announced: 04 Sep 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 2200 MHz, Krait 400, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.0 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 20.7 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 13.83 hours of Talk Time, 880 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat4 Downlink 150 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Samsung Galaxy Note 3 Announced: 04 Sep 2013 OS: Android 4.3 Hardware: Quad core, 2300 MHz, Krait 400, 3072 MB RAM Display: 5.7 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 3840x2160 (4K) 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 25 hours of Talk Time, 528 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat4 Downlink 150 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS HTC One Announced: 19 Feb 2013 OS: Android 4.3 4.2.2 4.1.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1700 MHz, Krait 300, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.7 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 4 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900), CDMA (800 1900) Data: LTE HSPA (unspecified) UMTS EDGE GPRS Nokia Lumia 1020 Announced: 11 Jul 2013 OS: Windows Phone 8 Hardware: Dual core, 1500 MHz, Krait, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.5 inches, 768 x 1280 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 41 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 19.1 hours of Talk Time, 384 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Google Nexus 4 Announced: 29 Oct 2012 OS: Android 4.3 4.2.2 4.2.1 4.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1500 MHz, Krait, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.7 inches, 768 x 1280 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 8 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 15.3 hours of Talk Time, 390 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS 1 2 Interesting stories Nexus 5 to have fastest smartphone camera Best new Android, iPhone and Windows Phone apps for September 2013 LG and Samsung to introduce curved display smartphones Best gadgets of 2013: our favorites so far Apple iPad 5 rumor round-up Apple iPhone 5s performance review Microsoft Surface 2 specs review The Evolution of Android, 5 years later Home Manufacturers Carriers News Reviews Discussions Videos PhoneArena network: CDN services by: Affiliates: Mobile Burn , Speed Guide , Cell Phone Accessories About Us . Advertise . Contact Us . Database Licensing . Links . Jobs All content (phone reviews, news, specs, info), design and layouts are Copyright 2001-2013 phoneArena.com. All rights reserved. Reproduction in whole or in part or in any form or medium without written permission is prohibited! Privacy . Terms of use . Cookies View mobile version
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:59:00
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        PhoneArena - News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.phonearena.com/news/Nokia-Lumia-929-leaks-dolled-up-in-white-and-Verizon-logo_id47929
      </link>
      <author>
        Phone Arena
      </author>
      <content>
        Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo x PhoneArena is looking for new authors! To view all available positions, click here. PhoneArena All Phones Reviews News Search Share this page Facebook Twitter Digg Follow us: Login Register Home Phones Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile View all Manufacturers Samsung HTC LG BlackBerry Motorola Apple Nokia Sony View all Phone tools Phone finder New phones Popular phones Compare phones Size compare Best phones Camera comparison Tablets Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile Manufacturers Apple Samsung Motorola BlackBerry Tablet tools Tablet finder New tablets Popular tablets Compare tablets News Reviews Discussions Videos Tip us Phone Links Carriers Verizon AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile more &amp;raquo; Brands Samsung Motorola HTC LG BlackBerry Apple Nokia more &amp;raquo; Tools Phone Finder Compare Size compare Camera comparison Best phones Home &amp;rsaquo; News &amp;rsaquo; Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo Posted: 03 Oct 2013, 01:36 , by Daniel P. Categories: Verizon Verizon Nokia Nokia Windows Windows Share: Discuss 4 Tweet The more manageable version of the giant Lumia 1520 , Lumia 929 , is heading to Verizon next month, and we already saw it leaked in black , with the 20 MP Pureview camera stamp clearly visible on the rear. Now the handset's press render has leaked again, this time dressed up in white shiny armor, and the same Verizon logo and 4G LTE stamp on the back. The Lumia 929 is expected to sport a 5&quot; Full HD display, fast Snapdragon processor, and is said to be launched on Verizon in the beginning of November. The rumored price is $500 unsubsidized, or $99 on contract, which would be a pretty decent tag for such a powerhouse if it materializes. source: evleaks Share: Discuss 4 Tweet HTC's market value is at an 8-year low; the end may be near 03 Oct Prev news Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid 03 Oct Next news Close Target makes Brightspot official with October 6th launch for the pre-paid 03 Oct Now reading: Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo 03 Oct HTC's market value is at an 8-year low; the end may be near 03 Oct Demand for low to mid-range 4G LTE handsets to rise in 2014 03 Oct BBM beta testing starts again with new version of the app 03 Oct Apple seeds iOS 7.0.3 to employees and partners as more bugs are found 02 Oct Rumored LG G Flex has a curved screen and an expected November unveiling 02 Oct Leaked iPad 5 casing fits iPhone 5s fingerprint scanner &quot;perfectly&quot; 02 Oct Amazon smartphone rumors return, claiming 3D user interface 02 Oct Apple could ship 5x more iPad 5 units than iPad mini 2 02 Oct older posts Related phones Nokia Lumia 929 Specifications News (2) Review User Reviews Discussions (0) Photos Size it 360&amp;deg; Manual Related News (Lumia 929) Nokia Lumia 929 is coming to Verizon: release date is early November and price is affordable 4 Comments Follow Following Options Close Show comments: default hide low rated show moderated comments Display mode: Threaded Chronological Newest first Save posted on 29 min ago 1 Reply 1. pokharkarsaga (Posts: 294; Member since: 23 Feb 2012) lumia 929 with snapdragon 800 processor &amp; 2gb ram will be a beast. posted on 19 min ago 0 Reply 2. CX3NT3_713 (Posts: 967; Member since: 18 Apr 2011) That is one sexy device..GO Nokia posted on 19 min ago 0 Reply 3. jedpatrickdatu (Posts: 124; Member since: 24 Jan 2013) The material on the sides looks metallic. It'll probably have iPhone-esque antennas like the Lumia 925. posted on 18 min ago 0 Reply 4. sri_tech (Posts: 96; Member since: 21 May 2013) I hope they release this globally because 6 inch (Lumia 1520) will be too big for most of the people. Want to comment? Please login or register . Home &amp;rsaquo; News &amp;rsaquo; Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo Nokia Lumia 929 leaks dolled up in white and Verizon logo Popular stories Last week Last 2 days Most commented 1. Nexus 5 to be first smartphone with MEMS camera: fastest on a phone, Lytro like functionality 2. Samsung is now locking all new devices to a region, making life hard 3. Best gadgets of 2013: our favorites so far 4. Road map reveals Android 4.3 update for Samsung Galaxy S4, Galaxy S III and GALAXY Note II 1 2 3 4 Recent Articles Apple iPhone 5s performance review: CPU and GPU speed compared to top Android phones (benchmarks) The Evolution of Android, 5 years later Clash of the titans: iOS 7 vs Android 4.3 comparison 1 2 3 4 Hot Phones Apple iPhone 5s Announced: 10 Sep 2013 OS: iOS Hardware: Dual core, 1300 MHz Display: 4.0 inches, 640 x 1136 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 8 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) 1280x720 (720p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Samsung Galaxy S4 Announced: 14 Mar 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1900 MHz, Krait 300, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.0 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS LG G2 Announced: 07 Aug 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 2260 MHz, Krait 400, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.2 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900), CDMA (800 1900) Data: LTE-A LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS EV-DO Rev.A Sony Xperia Z1 Announced: 04 Sep 2013 OS: Android 4.2.2 Hardware: Quad core, 2200 MHz, Krait 400, 2048 MB RAM Display: 5.0 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 20.7 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 13.83 hours of Talk Time, 880 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat4 Downlink 150 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Samsung Galaxy Note 3 Announced: 04 Sep 2013 OS: Android 4.3 Hardware: Quad core, 2300 MHz, Krait 400, 3072 MB RAM Display: 5.7 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 13 megapixels, 3840x2160 (4K) 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 25 hours of Talk Time, 528 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat4 Downlink 150 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS HTC One Announced: 19 Feb 2013 OS: Android 4.3 4.2.2 4.1.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1700 MHz, Krait 300, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.7 inches, 1080 x 1920 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 4 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900), CDMA (800 1900) Data: LTE HSPA (unspecified) UMTS EDGE GPRS Nokia Lumia 1020 Announced: 11 Jul 2013 OS: Windows Phone 8 Hardware: Dual core, 1500 MHz, Krait, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.5 inches, 768 x 1280 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 41 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 19.1 hours of Talk Time, 384 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: LTE Cat3 Downlink 100 Mbit/s LTE Cat3/4 Uplink 50 Mbit/s HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS Google Nexus 4 Announced: 29 Oct 2012 OS: Android 4.3 4.2.2 4.2.1 4.2 Hardware: Quad core, 1500 MHz, Krait, 2048 MB RAM Display: 4.7 inches, 768 x 1280 pixels, Capacitive Touchscreen Camera 8 megapixels, 1920x1080 (1080p HD) video Battery: 15.3 hours of Talk Time, 390 hours of Stand-by Technology: GSM (850 900 1800 1900) Data: HSDPA+ (4G) 42.2 Mbit/s HSUPA 5.76 Mbit/s UMTS EDGE GPRS 1 2 Interesting stories Nexus 5 to have fastest smartphone camera Best new Android, iPhone and Windows Phone apps for September 2013 LG and Samsung to introduce curved display smartphones Best gadgets of 2013: our favorites so far Apple iPad 5 rumor round-up Apple iPhone 5s performance review Microsoft Surface 2 specs review The Evolution of Android, 5 years later Home Manufacturers Carriers News Reviews Discussions Videos PhoneArena network: CDN services by: Affiliates: Speed Guide , Mobile Burn , Cell Phone Accessories About Us . Advertise . Contact Us . Database Licensing . Links . Jobs All content (phone reviews, news, specs, info), design and layouts are Copyright 2001-2013 phoneArena.com. All rights reserved. Reproduction in whole or in part or in any form or medium without written permission is prohibited! Privacy . Terms of use . Cookies View mobile version
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:36:00
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Mark Rowsthorn’s Stake in McAleese Worth $134 Million After IPO
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        MoneyBeat
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://blogs.wsj.com/moneybeat/2013/10/03/mark-rowsthorns-stake-in-mcaleese-worth-134-million-after-ipo/?mod=WSJBlog
      </link>
      <author>
        Gillian Tan
      </author>
      <content>
        Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s Stake in McAleese Worth $134 Million After IPO - MoneyBeat - WSJ WSJ WSJ Facebook Twitter WSJ Live WSJ Live MarketWatch MarketWatch Barron's Barron's Portfolio Portfolio Product X Product X rt f r&amp;amp;c pe&amp;amp;vc wsj b More All Things Digital WSJ Briefcase BigCharts Financial News Professor Journal SmartMoney Student Journal Virtual Stock Exchange WSJ Classifieds WSJ Classroom WSJ Radio WSJ Wine SEARCH headline gold man Companies GOLD Ran gold Resources Ltd. ADS U.S. View All Search Results &amp;raquo; The Wall Street Journal Menu HomePage World U.S. New York Business Tech Markets Market Data Opinion Life &amp;amp; Culture Real Estate Management CIO Journal CFO Journal Risk &amp;amp; Compliance Also in WSJ.com: Latest News Today's Paper Most Popular Streams (TBD) Video Blogs Editions U.S. Asia Europe Am&amp;#233;rica Latina Brasil 中文-简体 (China) Deutschland India Indonesia 日本 (Japan) 한국 (Korea) T&amp;#252;rkiye Log In Profile My News Saved Portfolio Old Portfolio Watchlist Newsletters &amp; Alerts Community Customer Center LOGOUT Message Center ( new) Markets Morning MoneyBeat: Worrying About Profit Warnings Asia Some Clouds Creep Into Global Outlook Markets Stocks Commodities Credit Currencies Stocks Commodities Credit Currencies Deals Banks Private Equity Hedge Funds Bankruptcy Select a Region: Global U.S. Europe Latin America Asia Australia U.S. Europe Latin America Asia Australia Hot Topics: J.P. Morgan Verizon Wireless Microsoft-Nokia Taper Talk SAC Capital Apple 2:25 am Oct 3, 2013 Australia Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s Stake in McAleese Worth $134 Million After IPO Article Comments Initial Public Offerings Logistics Mark Rowsthorn Transport smaller Larger facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print smaller Larger facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print By Gillian Tan @GillianTanAU Gillian Tan Biography CONNECT @GillianTanAU Gillian Tan Biography Australian transport and logistics company McAleese Group is planning an initial public offering that will raise 155 million Australian dollars (US$146 million), and value chairman Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s remaining 32% stake at around US$134 million, people familiar with the matter said Thursday. The IPO, which is being managed by Credit Suisse AG , J.P.Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. and Macquarie Group Ltd. , is being conducted at A$1.65 a share, and will give the company a market value of A$446.5 million, the people said.  McAleese could list as soon as this month. The price is 9.5 times estimated earnings for the fiscal year through June, representing a discount to already listed peers like Toll Holdings and Asciano Ltd. . Mr. Rowsthorn is the former chief executive of Asciano, which demerged from Toll Holdings in 2007. He was named among Forbes Magazine&amp;#8217;s 40 richest people from Australia and New Zealand as recently as 2007 , with a fortune of US$460 million. Other major shareholders in McAleese after it lists include executive directors Keith Price and Gilberto Maggiolo, who will own 7.5% and 7.4% of the company, respectively. Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s McAleese Group is set to list on the Australian Securities Exchange Bloomberg News McAleese&amp;#8217;s services include heavy and bulk haulage and liquid fuels distribution. Its clients include Atlas Iron Ltd. , South Africa&amp;#8217;s Gold Fields Ltd. and Theiss, a unit of Leighton Holdings . Outside Australia, it has operations in Singapore and the U.S. McAleese&amp;#8217;s market value will be less than half the size of its IPO that it planned last July . It had hoped to list to raise additional funds for the acquisition of Champ Private Equity&amp;#8217;s LCR Group. McAleese paid about US$309 million last April for another Champ Private Equity business, International Energy Services, which offers transport logistics services including fluid handling to the energy, resources and aviation industries. US$1.8 billion has been raised in Australian initial public offerings in the year-to-date, more than five times the US$340 million that was raised by this time in 2012, according to Dealogic. Initial Public Offerings Logistics Mark Rowsthorn Transport previous Europe&amp;#8217;s Morning MoneyBeat: Shutdown Glowers Over All MoneyBeat HOME PAGE Add a Comment Error message Name We welcome thoughtful comments from readers. Please comply with our guidelines . Our blogs do not require the use of your real name. Comment previous Europe&amp;#8217;s Morning MoneyBeat: Shutdown Glowers Over All Search MoneyBeat1 close Email This Recipient's Email Address (Separate multiple address with commas) Your Email Address Message (Optional) Send me a copy or Cancel close Thank You Your email has been sent. close Error. An error has occured and your email has not been sent. Please try again . &amp;bull; Invalid email address. &amp;bull; You can't enter more than 20 emails. &amp;bull; Seperate multiple addresses with Commas. &amp;bull; Must enter an email address. &amp;bull; You must enter the verification code below to send. &amp;bull; Invalid entry: Please type the verification code again. Popular Now What's This? Close Content engaging our readers now, with additional prominence accorded if the story is rapidly gaining attention. Our WSJ algorithm comprises 30% page views, 20% Facebook, 20% Twitter, 20% email shares and 10% comments. 1 Shutdown Closes 3,200 Preschoolers' Head Start Programs Twitter Facebook Email Comments 2 Tom Clancy, RIP Twitter Facebook Email Comments 3 Apple Now Holds 10% of All Corporate Cash: Moody's Twitter Facebook Email Comments 4 Zynga Founder Pincus: I'm Bored With Games Twitter Facebook Email Comments 5 iMessages to Nowhere? Twitter Facebook Email Comments Show 5 More 6 Centrist Republicans Lobby Boehner to End Shutdown Twitter Facebook Email Comments 7 Who Treats Their Workers Best? Twitter Facebook Email Comments 8 Which Government Workers Are Affected by Shutdown? Twitter Facebook Email Comments 9 How to Track the Economy During A Government Shutdown Twitter Facebook Email Comments 10 Fears of Stalling Housing Recovery Are Overblown Twitter Facebook Email Comments Show Less The MoneyBeat Team RSS Stephen Grocer Editor Phillipa Leighton-Jones European Editor Paul Vigna Reporter New York Steven Russolillo Reporter New York David Benoit Reporter New York Isabella Steger Reporter Hong Kong Gillian Tan Reporter Sydney David Cottle Reporter London MoneyBeat Columnists Ronald Barusch Dealpolitik Francesco Guerrera Current Account David Weidner Writing on the Wall Jason Zweig The Intelligent Investor Michael J. Casey Horizons Spencer Jakab Ahead of the Tape Simon Nixon E.S. Browning Newsletters WSJ.com Email Features Morning MoneyBeat U.S. Morning MoneyBeat Europe Morning MoneyBeat Asia Submit Sign Up SIGN UP Symbols and Alerts Manage Email Preferences WSJ Web Slice CONTENT LINKS TO ACTUAL PAGE CONTAINING WEB SLICE FUNCTIONALITY. 15 Wall Street Journal Facebook Twitter LinkedIn FourSquare Google+ YouTube Podcasts RSS Feed AppStore Subscribe / Login Back to Top &amp;laquo; Customer Service Customer Center New! Live Help Contact Us WSJ Weekend Contact Directory Corrections Policy Privacy Policy Data Policy Copyright Policy Subscriber Agreement &amp;amp; Terms of Use Your Ad Choices Advertise Advertise Place a Classified Ad Sell Your Home Sell Your Business Commercial Real Estate Ads Recruitment &amp; Career Ads Franchising Advertise Locally Tools &amp;amp; Features Apps Newsletters and Alerts Graphics &amp;amp; Photos Columns Topics Guides Portfolio Old Portfolio More Register for Free Reprints Content Partnerships Conferences SafeHouse Mobile Site Price &amp; Volume Keyword &amp; Symbol News Archive Jobs at WSJ Copyright &amp;copy;2013 Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company , Inc. All Rights Reserved. Schlie&amp;szlig;en Subscribe Now close Email This Recipient's Email Address (Separate multiple address with commas) Your Email Address Message (Optional) Send me a copy or Cancel close Thank You Your email has been sent. close Error. An error has occured and your email has not been sent. Please try again . &amp;bull; Invalid email address. &amp;bull; You can't enter more than 20 emails. &amp;bull; Seperate multiple addresses with Commas. &amp;bull; Must enter an email address. &amp;bull; You must enter the verification code below to send. &amp;bull; Invalid entry: Please type the verification code again.
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:25:54
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Europe’s Morning MoneyBeat: Shutdown Glowers Over All
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        MoneyBeat
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://blogs.wsj.com/moneybeat/2013/10/03/europes-morning-moneybeat-shutdown-glowers-over-all/?mod=WSJBlog
      </link>
      <author>
        WSJ Staff
      </author>
      <content>
        Europe's Morning MoneyBeat: Shutdown Glowers Over All - MoneyBeat - WSJ WSJ WSJ Facebook Twitter WSJ Live WSJ Live MarketWatch MarketWatch Barron's Barron's Portfolio Portfolio Product X Product X rt f r&amp;amp;c pe&amp;amp;vc wsj b More All Things Digital WSJ Briefcase BigCharts Financial News Professor Journal SmartMoney Student Journal Virtual Stock Exchange WSJ Classifieds WSJ Classroom WSJ Radio WSJ Wine SEARCH headline gold man Companies GOLD Ran gold Resources Ltd. ADS U.S. View All Search Results &amp;raquo; The Wall Street Journal Menu HomePage World U.S. New York Business Tech Markets Market Data Opinion Life &amp;amp; Culture Real Estate Management CIO Journal CFO Journal Risk &amp;amp; Compliance Also in WSJ.com: Latest News Today's Paper Most Popular Streams (TBD) Video Blogs Editions U.S. Asia Europe Am&amp;#233;rica Latina Brasil 中文-简体 (China) Deutschland India Indonesia 日本 (Japan) 한국 (Korea) T&amp;#252;rkiye Log In Profile My News Saved Portfolio Old Portfolio Watchlist Newsletters &amp; Alerts Community Customer Center LOGOUT Message Center ( new) Markets Morning MoneyBeat: Worrying About Profit Warnings Asia Some Clouds Creep Into Global Outlook Markets Stocks Commodities Credit Currencies Stocks Commodities Credit Currencies Deals Banks Private Equity Hedge Funds Bankruptcy Select a Region: Europe Global U.S. Latin America Asia Australia Global U.S. Latin America Asia Australia Hot Topics: J.P. Morgan Verizon Wireless Microsoft-Nokia Taper Talk SAC Capital Apple 2:22 am Oct 3, 2013 Capital Markets Europe&amp;#8217;s Morning MoneyBeat: Shutdown Glowers Over All Article Comments Breakfast Morning MoneyBeat Europe Stocks smaller Larger facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print smaller Larger facebook twitter google plus linked in Email Print Good Morning Europe Anyone who went to bed last night expecting to awake to a fully functioning U.S. Federal Government is going to be disappointed Thursday. The impasse continues in Washington, and so does the shutdown. Although the markets&amp;#8217; base case seems to be that a deal will be struck, because one always is in the end, stocks are going to find the going tough. U.S. indexes closed lower, beset by Congress&amp;#8217;s truculence and a weaker report on private sector job creation. Their Asian counterparts were given an initial fillip by a blockbuster service sector survey out of China, but the Nikkei couldn&amp;#8217;t shake those shutdown blues. It pared gains and has closed marginally lower. In Europe, stock futures are pointing to a modestly lower open, with the December FTSE contract down nine points. Oil is lower, with Brent off $0.42 and Nymex down $0.50. Gold is also $5 lower. There&amp;#8217;s plenty of European economic data on tap. The local service sector Purchasing Managers Indexes are often market movers, and there&amp;#8217;s euro-zone retail sales data too. Out of the U.S. we should get weekly jobless claims numbers, which are apparently shutdown-proof and not compiled by government agencies. There are plenty of Fed speakers due too, it&amp;#8217;s doubtful they&amp;#8217;ll go easy on Congress. By David Cottle What you may have missed from MoneyBeat: What to Look for in Twitter’s IPO Filing :  With the paperwork for Twitter’s IPO expected as soon as this week, here are some of the key metrics money managers will be eyeing. “ Dear Sotheby’s”; Highlights From Dan Loeb’s Letter : Wednesday, Dan Loeb took out his poison pen and drew an ugly picture for Sotheby’s. Low Rates Will Be Around for Years, Gross Says : &amp;#8220;Bet against” the Fed raising interest rates to even 2% by the end of 2016, Pimco’s Bill Gross says in his latest outlook. Deleveraging will push the Fed to keep rates ultra-low for years, if not decades. From The Wall Street Journal: Lawmakers Look to Break Budget Impasse :   U.S. lawmakers and President Barack Obama made overtures on Wednesday aimed at sparking negotiations to end the government shutdown, but neither side budged on demands that have polarized the debate. Draghi Warns of Shutdown Risk :   The U.S. government shutdown could threaten economic recoveries in the U.S. and around the world if it persists, European Central Bank President Mario Draghi warned. Philippine President Accuses Earlier Administration of Misusing Funds : Philippine President Benigno Aquino III said Wednesday that the administration of former President Gloria Macapagal-Arroyo may have misused at least $19 billion in public funds by manipulating the budget and other means over the course of her nearly 10 years in power. BlackBerry Draws Interest of Cerberus : BlackBerry has drawn the interest of distressed-investing specialists including Cerberus Capital Management, according to people familiar with the matter, as the smartphone maker seeks a buyer to rescue the company. Marc Jacobs Prepares IPO : Marc Jacobs is leaving Louis Vuitton to focus on his own label and prepare it for an initial public offering, Louis Vuitton Chief Executive Michael Burke said Wednesday, ending the 16-year tenure of the highest profile American designer at the helm of a major European fashion house. Breakfast Morning MoneyBeat Europe Stocks previous RBS Morgans Says Buy Warrnambool Cheese &amp;#038; Butter next Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s Stake in McAleese Worth $134 Million After IPO MoneyBeat HOME PAGE Add a Comment Error message Name We welcome thoughtful comments from readers. Please comply with our guidelines . Our blogs do not require the use of your real name. Comment previous RBS Morgans Says Buy Warrnambool Cheese &amp;#038; Butter next Mark Rowsthorn&amp;#8217;s Stake in McAleese Worth $134 Million After IPO Search MoneyBeat1 close Email This Recipient's Email Address (Separate multiple address with commas) Your Email Address Message (Optional) Send me a copy or Cancel close Thank You Your email has been sent. close Error. An error has occured and your email has not been sent. Please try again . &amp;bull; Invalid email address. &amp;bull; You can't enter more than 20 emails. &amp;bull; Seperate multiple addresses with Commas. &amp;bull; Must enter an email address. &amp;bull; You must enter the verification code below to send. &amp;bull; Invalid entry: Please type the verification code again. Popular Now What's This? Close Content engaging our readers now, with additional prominence accorded if the story is rapidly gaining attention. Our WSJ algorithm comprises 30% page views, 20% Facebook, 20% Twitter, 20% email shares and 10% comments. 1 Shutdown Closes 3,200 Preschoolers' Head Start Programs Twitter Facebook Email Comments 2 Tom Clancy, RIP Twitter Facebook Email Comments 3 Apple Now Holds 10% of All Corporate Cash: Moody's Twitter Facebook Email Comments 4 Zynga Founder Pincus: I'm Bored With Games Twitter Facebook Email Comments 5 iMessages to Nowhere? Twitter Facebook Email Comments Show 5 More 6 Centrist Republicans Lobby Boehner to End Shutdown Twitter Facebook Email Comments 7 Who Treats Their Workers Best? Twitter Facebook Email Comments 8 Which Government Workers Are Affected by Shutdown? Twitter Facebook Email Comments 9 How to Track the Economy During A Government Shutdown Twitter Facebook Email Comments 10 Fears of Stalling Housing Recovery Are Overblown Twitter Facebook Email Comments Show Less The MoneyBeat Team RSS Stephen Grocer Editor Phillipa Leighton-Jones European Editor Paul Vigna Reporter New York Steven Russolillo Reporter New York David Benoit Reporter New York Isabella Steger Reporter Hong Kong Gillian Tan Reporter Sydney David Cottle Reporter London MoneyBeat Columnists Ronald Barusch Dealpolitik Francesco Guerrera Current Account David Weidner Writing on the Wall Jason Zweig The Intelligent Investor Michael J. Casey Horizons Spencer Jakab Ahead of the Tape Simon Nixon E.S. Browning Newsletters WSJ.com Email Features Morning MoneyBeat U.S. Morning MoneyBeat Europe Morning MoneyBeat Asia Submit Sign Up SIGN UP Symbols and Alerts Manage Email Preferences WSJ Web Slice CONTENT LINKS TO ACTUAL PAGE CONTAINING WEB SLICE FUNCTIONALITY. 15 Wall Street Journal Facebook Twitter LinkedIn FourSquare Google+ YouTube Podcasts RSS Feed AppStore Subscribe / Login Back to Top &amp;laquo; Customer Service Customer Center New! Live Help Contact Us WSJ Weekend Contact Directory Corrections Policy Privacy Policy Data Policy Copyright Policy Subscriber Agreement &amp;amp; Terms of Use Your Ad Choices Advertise Advertise Place a Classified Ad Sell Your Home Sell Your Business Commercial Real Estate Ads Recruitment &amp; Career Ads Franchising Advertise Locally Tools &amp;amp; Features Apps Newsletters and Alerts Graphics &amp;amp; Photos Columns Topics Guides Portfolio Old Portfolio More Register for Free Reprints Content Partnerships Conferences SafeHouse Mobile Site Price &amp; Volume Keyword &amp; Symbol News Archive Jobs at WSJ Copyright &amp;copy;2013 Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company , Inc. All Rights Reserved. Schlie&amp;szlig;en Subscribe Now close Email This Recipient's Email Address (Separate multiple address with commas) Your Email Address Message (Optional) Send me a copy or Cancel close Thank You Your email has been sent. close Error. An error has occured and your email has not been sent. Please try again . &amp;bull; Invalid email address. &amp;bull; You can't enter more than 20 emails. &amp;bull; Seperate multiple addresses with Commas. &amp;bull; Must enter an email address. &amp;bull; You must enter the verification code below to send. &amp;bull; Invalid entry: Please type the verification code again.
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:22:10
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Toshiba wants majority stake in British nuclear consortium: CEO
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://news.yahoo.com/toshiba-wants-majority-stake-british-nuclear-consortium-ceo-061910147--finance.html
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Toshiba wants majority stake in British nuclear consortium: CEO - Yahoo News Home Mail News Sports Finance Weather Games Groups Answers Screen Flickr More omg! Shine Movies Music TV Health Shopping Travel Autos Homes Mobile Yahoo News Search News Search Web Sign In Mail Go to Mail.&quot; data-nosubject=&quot;[No Subject]&quot; data-timestamp='short'&gt; Help Account Info Help Suggestions Yahoo News Home U.S. World Politics Tech Science Health Odd News Opinion Local Dear Abby Comics ABC News Yahoo Originals Toshiba wants majority stake in British nuclear consortium: CEO Content preferences Done Sophie Knight and Maki Shiraki 53 minutes ago . View gallery Toshiba Corp President and Chief Executive Hisao Tanaka speaks during the company's corporate strategy &amp;hellip; By Sophie Knight and Maki Shiraki TOKYO (Reuters) - Toshiba Corp wants a majority stake in British nuclear consortium NuGen and aims to decide on the matter before the end of the year, its chief executive said, as it seeks its first order for a nuclear reactor since the Fukushima crisis in 2011. Hisao Tanaka told Reuters in an interview on Thursday that the company was confident about securing orders for 29 new nuclear reactors by March 2018 and that he sensed post-Fukushima anti-nuclear sentiment had begun to thaw. Spanish utility Iberdrola SA is in talks to sell its 50 percent stake in NuGen, according to a source with knowledge of the talks. Taking a majority stake would require Toshiba subsidiary Westinghouse to buy shares both from Iberdrola and from joint NuGen shareholder GDF Suez. Toshiba will make a decision on capital investment in its NAND flash chip operation by March of next year, Tanaka added. The company is expanding its fifth fabrication plant in Japan and questions remain as to when it will install equipment and begin production, which would depend on the outlook for demand for NAND chips, used in smartphones and tablets. Tanaka said the ideal scenario would be to install equipment immediately when construction is complete on the expansion project next summer, and begin production as soon as possible. Toshiba and its partner SanDisk Corp have pledged to invest a maximum of 400 billion yen ($4.11 billion), split 50-50, on equipment for the factory. Tanaka also said that the restructuring of Toshiba's TV division had been completed with an announcement earlier this week that the company would shrink the unit, shutting two of its three overseas factories and reducing its worldwide workforce by half to 3,000. The CEO said he was confident that the division would be able to pull into the black after these measures have been implemented. (Additional reporting by Reiji Murai; Editing by Edmund Klamann) Investment &amp; Company Information Toshiba Corp Hisao Tanaka nuclear reactor majority stake Click to view comments View Comments Share this Recommended for You Obama stressed to congressional leaders he will not negotiate over shutdown, debt limit WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Barack Obama stressed to congressional leaders on Wednesday in White House talks that he will not negotiate with Republicans over a government shutdown or raising the U.S. debt limit, the White House said. After more than an hour of talks that did not lead to a… Reuters Save More like this Remove Rouhani: Iran to discuss nuke details, not rights TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — President Hassan Rouhani said Wednesday that Iran is open to discussing &amp;quot;details&amp;quot; of nuclear activities including the enrichment of uranium, hinting that the Islamic Republic is willing to broaden the terms of negotiations with world powers. He spoke shortly after receiving… Associated Press Save More like this Remove Stream TV Shows and Movies Anywhere Any Time Take Netflix anywhere you go. Unlimited streaming from your favorite device for only $7.99/month. AdChoices Netflix Sponsored Suspect arraigned in motorcycle-SUV brawl in NYC NEW YORK (AP) — A motorcyclist was charged Wednesday with reckless driving after prosecutors said he touched off a tense encounter with the driver of an SUV and a throng of other bikers that ended with blood and broken bones on a Manhattan street. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Mia Farrow: &amp;#39;Possible&amp;#39; son is Sinatra&amp;#39;s NEW YORK (AP) — Mia Farrow says in an interview with Vanity Fair that it&amp;#39;s possible her son with Woody Allen is instead Frank Sinatra&amp;#39;s. Associated Press Save More like this Remove China&amp;#39;s Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes By Kanupriya Kapoor JAKARTA (Reuters) - Chinese President Xi Jinping showed no sign of bending to Southeast Asian pressure to resolve increasingly irascible territorial disputes over the South China Sea on Thursday, simply repeating past calls for dialogue. Xi, in the first address by a foreign… Reuters 44 mins ago Save More like this Remove Wife: Biker husband is victim in NYC altercation NEW YORK (AP) — Shaky camera footage depicts the gory scene: A driver who police say was frightened when a group of motorcyclists swarmed his Range Rover plowed through them, striking a rider in a purple T-shirt and black helmet. Associated Press Save More like this Remove EPIC FAIL: Los Angeles high schools now confiscate all free iPads they gave students Hilariously, officials at high schools in the Los Angeles Unified School District are now taking back a couple thousand iPads a week or so after giving them to students as part of a 47-school pilot program. The Daily Caller Save More like this Remove The Hidden Costs of &amp;#39;Affordable&amp;#39; Health Insurance Plans The Affordable Care Act promises to expand access to health care by providing affordable coverage to millions of Americans. But finding a policy that meets your health care needs and your budget requirements can be daunting. U.S.News &amp; World Report LP Save More like this Remove With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) recently released this stunning photo of an estimated 10,000 walruses crammed onto a tiny Alaskan beach. The Sideshow Save More like this Remove View In the wild photo competition (9 photos) In The Wild Photo Competition via ZUMA Press   All creatures great and small are depicted in these wonderful images from a top wildlife competition. From a leopard hauling a wildebeest kill into a tree to a jackdaw picking parasites off a deer in Bushy Park, these were just some of the hundreds of… Save More like this Remove Dazzling Bayern Munich can improve, warns Guardiola Manchester (United Kingdom) (AFP) - Manager Pep Guardiola watched his Bayern Munich team outclass Manchester City 3-1 and then warned the rest of Europe that the Champions League holders can get even better. AFP Save More like this Remove Video reveals final design of Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia Madrid (AFP) - It has been under construction for more than 130 years and there is another 13 to go, but the world has been given a glimpse of what Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia will look like when finally completed. AFP Save More like this Remove Tesla Says Car Fire Began in Battery APNewsBreak: Tesla Model S car fire began in battery; stock falls after video goes online         ABC News Save More like this Remove House Dems offer immigration bill, fate uncertain WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Wednesday unveiled an immigration bill that provides a path to citizenship for the 11 million immigrants living here illegally and tightens border security, and they warned of political fallout if House Republicans fail to act. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Auto Dealers Cut Prices on New Cars &amp;amp; Trucks Local auto dealers are cutting their prices on all vehicle types. If you're looking for a new car this month, buy now and save as much as ... AdChoices Auto-Price-Finder.com Sponsored Shutdown Hampers Search for Missing Woman in Idaho National Park Ten Park Service rangers furloughed as a result of the government shutdown are volunteering their time to scour a national park in Idaho for a missing physician, whose search has been complicated by federal closures. Jo Elliott-Blakeslee, 63, was last seen in Craters of the... ABC News Save More like this Remove South Carolina drops extradition order for Baby Veronica&amp;#39;s biological father By Brendan O&amp;#39;Brien (Reuters) - The biological father of &amp;quot;Baby Veronica,&amp;quot; a Native American girl who was at the heart of a protracted custody battle, will not be extradited to South Carolina to face felony charges for interfering with her adoption, Oklahoma Governor Mary Fallin said on Wednesday.… Reuters Save More like this Remove 22 dogs will get lucky on new CBS television show LOS ANGELES (AP) — Brandon McMillan has trained as many as 10,000 dogs for television, movies, commercials, videos and people. Then he started saving dogs from animal shelters, training them and finding homes for them. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Play Hundreds of Students Involved in Violent Hazing Incident More than one hundred students at a Seattle high school were caught taking part in a dangerous hazing incident. Tribune Save More like this Remove iPhone 5s Review: A Great Phone With Some More Forward Thinking Needed Is Apple&amp;#39;s Latest Really the &amp;#39;Forward Thinking&amp;#39; Phone it Promises? Good Morning America Save More like this Remove LA Coroner&amp;#39;s office IDing 4 bodies found in jet LOS ANGELES (AP) — Just as he had so many times before, Mark Benjamin rode his small jet from a town in the Idaho wilderness he loved to the Southern California airport he knew so well. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Load more stories Top Stories Meeting yields no breakthrough in shutdown Service academy football games will go on Tesla car fire involved battery pack Latest Videos Obama: Shutdown Result of Ideological Crusade 01:34 Vets Cross Barricades Despite Shutdown 01:15 Shutdown Ripple Effect Felt Across Country 00:02 Government shutdown: 15,000 FAA employees furloughed 01:59 Obama cancels stops on overseas trip in wake of shutdown 01:55 Latest Slideshows Sectarian violence between Rohingyas and Buddhists Photos of the day - October 2, 2013 In the wild photo competition Government shutdown begins US-Mexico border helicopter patrol continues through &amp;hellip; Yahoo News Originals Lottery Luck: Learn the recipe for winning the lottery (Video) Shutdown stories: How congressional quarreling is affecting us Veterans swarm ‘closed’ WWII memorial, knock politicians Awesome Magic Trick Prank Gives Pizza Deliverymen Surprise Tips Our Very Own Lip Sync Battle - Vote Now! Skeletons get hungry, too The biggest complaints about iOS 7 so far Obama, lawmakers huddle but no shutdown breakthrough The Last Word on...the Kindle Fire HDX With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Check for restrictions at: http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Yahoo - ABC News Network Help / Suggestions Privacy About Our Ads Terms
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:19:10
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Britain's William Hill warns on profit after slow third quarter
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://news.yahoo.com/britains-william-hill-warns-profit-slow-third-quarter-063534610--finance.html
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Britain's William Hill warns on profit after slow third quarter - Yahoo News Home Mail News Sports Finance Weather Games Groups Answers Screen Flickr More omg! Shine Movies Music TV Health Shopping Travel Autos Homes Mobile Yahoo News Search News Search Web Sign In Mail Go to Mail.&quot; data-nosubject=&quot;[No Subject]&quot; data-timestamp='short'&gt; Help Account Info Help Suggestions Yahoo News Home U.S. World Politics Tech Science Health Odd News Opinion Local Dear Abby Comics ABC News Yahoo Originals Britain's William Hill warns on profit after slow third quarter Content preferences Done 38 minutes ago LONDON (Reuters) - British bookmaker William Hill said a poor retail performance in its third quarter meant operating profit had fallen 20 million pounds ($32.5 million) below expectations, warning that shortfall may not be recovered by the year end. Quiet trading in July helped push retail net revenue in the 13 week period to Oct 1 down 4 percent on an underlying basis, the firm said on Thursday, with gross margin wins falling 0.8 percentage points as football results went the way of customers. Overall underlying group revenue increased 4 percent in the third quarter, but operating profit fell 31 percent, or by 24 million pounds. (Reporting by Neil Maidment, editing by Keith Weir) Company Earnings Finance Click to view comments View Comments Share this Recommended for You Obama stressed to congressional leaders he will not negotiate over shutdown, debt limit WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Barack Obama stressed to congressional leaders on Wednesday in White House talks that he will not negotiate with Republicans over a government shutdown or raising the U.S. debt limit, the White House said. After more than an hour of talks that did not lead to a… Reuters Save More like this Remove Rouhani: Iran to discuss nuke details, not rights TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — President Hassan Rouhani said Wednesday that Iran is open to discussing &amp;quot;details&amp;quot; of nuclear activities including the enrichment of uranium, hinting that the Islamic Republic is willing to broaden the terms of negotiations with world powers. He spoke shortly after receiving… Associated Press Save More like this Remove Stream TV Shows and Movies Anywhere Any Time Take Netflix anywhere you go. Unlimited streaming from your favorite device for only $7.99/month. AdChoices Netflix Sponsored Suspect arraigned in motorcycle-SUV brawl in NYC NEW YORK (AP) — A motorcyclist was charged Wednesday with reckless driving after prosecutors said he touched off a tense encounter with the driver of an SUV and a throng of other bikers that ended with blood and broken bones on a Manhattan street. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Mia Farrow: &amp;#39;Possible&amp;#39; son is Sinatra&amp;#39;s NEW YORK (AP) — Mia Farrow says in an interview with Vanity Fair that it&amp;#39;s possible her son with Woody Allen is instead Frank Sinatra&amp;#39;s. Associated Press Save More like this Remove China&amp;#39;s Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes By Kanupriya Kapoor JAKARTA (Reuters) - Chinese President Xi Jinping showed no sign of bending to Southeast Asian pressure to resolve increasingly irascible territorial disputes over the South China Sea on Thursday, simply repeating past calls for dialogue. Xi, in the first address by a foreign… Reuters 44 mins ago Save More like this Remove Play Hundreds of Students Involved in Violent Hazing Incident More than one hundred students at a Seattle high school were caught taking part in a dangerous hazing incident. Tribune Save More like this Remove Wife: Biker husband is victim in NYC altercation NEW YORK (AP) — Shaky camera footage depicts the gory scene: A driver who police say was frightened when a group of motorcyclists swarmed his Range Rover plowed through them, striking a rider in a purple T-shirt and black helmet. Associated Press Save More like this Remove EPIC FAIL: Los Angeles high schools now confiscate all free iPads they gave students Hilariously, officials at high schools in the Los Angeles Unified School District are now taking back a couple thousand iPads a week or so after giving them to students as part of a 47-school pilot program. The Daily Caller Save More like this Remove The Hidden Costs of &amp;#39;Affordable&amp;#39; Health Insurance Plans The Affordable Care Act promises to expand access to health care by providing affordable coverage to millions of Americans. But finding a policy that meets your health care needs and your budget requirements can be daunting. U.S.News &amp; World Report LP Save More like this Remove With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) recently released this stunning photo of an estimated 10,000 walruses crammed onto a tiny Alaskan beach. The Sideshow Save More like this Remove Dazzling Bayern Munich can improve, warns Guardiola Manchester (United Kingdom) (AFP) - Manager Pep Guardiola watched his Bayern Munich team outclass Manchester City 3-1 and then warned the rest of Europe that the Champions League holders can get even better. AFP Save More like this Remove Video reveals final design of Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia Madrid (AFP) - It has been under construction for more than 130 years and there is another 13 to go, but the world has been given a glimpse of what Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia will look like when finally completed. AFP Save More like this Remove Tesla Says Car Fire Began in Battery APNewsBreak: Tesla Model S car fire began in battery; stock falls after video goes online         ABC News Save More like this Remove Play Government shutdown affecting DHHS services Some parents could soon be without healthy food options if the governement shutown lingers. WTVD – Raleigh/Durham Save More like this Remove Auto Dealers Cut Prices on New Cars &amp;amp; Trucks Local auto dealers are cutting their prices on all vehicle types. If you're looking for a new car this month, buy now and save as much as ... AdChoices Auto-Price-Finder.com Sponsored House Dems offer immigration bill, fate uncertain WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Wednesday unveiled an immigration bill that provides a path to citizenship for the 11 million immigrants living here illegally and tightens border security, and they warned of political fallout if House Republicans fail to act. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Shutdown Hampers Search for Missing Woman in Idaho National Park Ten Park Service rangers furloughed as a result of the government shutdown are volunteering their time to scour a national park in Idaho for a missing physician, whose search has been complicated by federal closures. Jo Elliott-Blakeslee, 63, was last seen in Craters of the... ABC News Save More like this Remove South Carolina drops extradition order for Baby Veronica&amp;#39;s biological father By Brendan O&amp;#39;Brien (Reuters) - The biological father of &amp;quot;Baby Veronica,&amp;quot; a Native American girl who was at the heart of a protracted custody battle, will not be extradited to South Carolina to face felony charges for interfering with her adoption, Oklahoma Governor Mary Fallin said on Wednesday.… Reuters Save More like this Remove 22 dogs will get lucky on new CBS television show LOS ANGELES (AP) — Brandon McMillan has trained as many as 10,000 dogs for television, movies, commercials, videos and people. Then he started saving dogs from animal shelters, training them and finding homes for them. Associated Press Save More like this Remove iPhone 5s Review: A Great Phone With Some More Forward Thinking Needed Is Apple&amp;#39;s Latest Really the &amp;#39;Forward Thinking&amp;#39; Phone it Promises? Good Morning America Save More like this Remove LA Coroner&amp;#39;s office IDing 4 bodies found in jet LOS ANGELES (AP) — Just as he had so many times before, Mark Benjamin rode his small jet from a town in the Idaho wilderness he loved to the Southern California airport he knew so well. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Load more stories Top Stories Meeting yields no breakthrough in shutdown Service academy football games will go on Tesla car fire involved battery pack Latest Videos Obama: Shutdown Result of Ideological Crusade 01:34 Vets Cross Barricades Despite Shutdown 01:15 Shutdown Ripple Effect Felt Across Country 00:02 Government shutdown: 15,000 FAA employees furloughed 01:59 Obama cancels stops on overseas trip in wake of shutdown 01:55 Latest Slideshows Sectarian violence between Rohingyas and Buddhists Photos of the day - October 2, 2013 In the wild photo competition Government shutdown begins US-Mexico border helicopter patrol continues through &amp;hellip; Yahoo News Originals Lottery Luck: Learn the recipe for winning the lottery (Video) Shutdown stories: How congressional quarreling is affecting us Veterans swarm ‘closed’ WWII memorial, knock politicians Awesome Magic Trick Prank Gives Pizza Deliverymen Surprise Tips Our Very Own Lip Sync Battle - Vote Now! Skeletons get hungry, too The biggest complaints about iOS 7 so far Obama, lawmakers huddle but no shutdown breakthrough The Last Word on...the Kindle Fire HDX With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Check for restrictions at: http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Yahoo - ABC News Network Help / Suggestions Privacy About Our Ads Terms
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:35:34
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/3/4797506/netflix-updates-ios-app-for-hd-streaming-and-airplay
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay | The Verge The Verge The big story FBI busts massive internet black market Silk Road California bans revenge porn Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) A city in flames: Detroit firefighters battle arson Samsung Galaxy Gear Review Facebook Twitter Google+ YouTube Subscribe to The Verge via RSS 19 New articles back next October 03, 2013 Snapchat's next big thing: 'Stories' that don't just... LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone... Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to... October 02, 2013 This video game photographer creates art out of virtual... Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and... Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It... Bizarre shirts turn famous faces into Facebook-confusing... Amazon reportedly has two phones in the works, one with a... Target officially unveils Brightspot, a prepaid wireless... Google acquires Flutter to bring Kinect-like features to... The FBI busted Silk Road, but not the 'dark web' behind it Snowden's email provider Lavabit fought government... Despite blocking 'Catcher in the Rye' films, J.D. Salinger... Why we don't want our Roombas to look human Obama's $100 million effort to map the human brain... The PicoBrew Zymatic is the Nespresso of beer brewing Facebook's check-in based free Wi-Fi rolling out nationally... 23andMe receives patent to create designer babies, but... Silk Road may be gone, but Topix is still a haven for drug... Drone reportedly plummets dozens of stories and crash lands... Intelligence head says cutting 'non-essential' CIA, NSA... Justice Department says tech companies would help... Bitcoin price nosedives after bust of underground drug... August's beautiful smart lock goes up for pre-order at... Mummy medicine: how ancient bodies can help create modern... Kia launching its first all-electric vehicle for US market... A city in flames: inside Detroit's war on arson Dell's new XPS 15 aims to be the king of portable Windows... Dell unveils first four Venue tablets, including a... BlackBerry's dark road ahead detailed in new filings Target reportedly taking on Straight Talk with its own... Lake of doom: deadly waterway calcifies any animal that... FBI seizes underground drug market Silk Road, owner... The NSA tracked US cellphone locations during secret... One month after Nokia deal, what is Microsoft's plan? Author Tom Clancy dead at age 66 East Village to East End: Airbnb's chief mapmaker charts... Microsoft brings classic 'Hover!' Windows 95 game to the web Jellyfish force shutdown of nuclear power plant 'Grand Theft Auto V' players join forces to manipulate the... Windows 8.1 now available to pre-order for $119 ahead of... California bans 'revenge porn,' could punish offenders with... This is the Fitbit Force, a smarter fitness tracking watch Bulgarians trade free will for free beer Abandoned house given a facade-melting facelift FAA panel: Wi-Fi use is safe during takeoff and landing Internet proves that only four things are better than... Apple hires veteran cable TV exec to engineer 'something... Chromecast support for Hulu Plus coming today Valve's Steam Box won't challenge consoles, says... Apple's rumored iPad mini with Retina display could face... 'Breaking Bad' finale song sees 9,000 percent surge in... Apple promises fix for iMessage bug in iOS 7 Iran's president tweets with Jack Dorsey, hints at... Amazon Kindle Fire HDX review (7-inch) October 01, 2013 Netflix expands its streaming library with final seasons of... 'Warcraft' movie slated for December 18th, 2015 release Spin for iOS puts a new twist on video chatting 'Mega Man' spiritual successor coming to PS4 and Xbox One... Bill Gates should step down, say three top Microsoft... Mars Curiosity rover to continue operation despite federal... Banksy launches New York City street art show with... New programming language could code DNA to deliver drugs... The 'Breaking Bad' writers' room and the endings that could... Ford CEO Mulally sidesteps rumors that he could become... Apple's next iPad may come in space gray like the iPhone 5s Jeff Bezos officially takes over as owner of The Washington... Google updates Chrome with one-click image search, adds new... Will this gnarly, 3D-printed mold be your next toothbrush? Billionaire investor Carl Icahn pushing Tim Cook for a $150... Checking email now means breaking the law for many federal... The nuclear terror of 1983 Qualcomm joins Power Matters Alliance, hopes to 'harmonize'... FCC looks to fine TracFone and others $14 million for... Timothy Leary's 'Neuromancer' video game could have been... FTC won't interfere with Google's $1 billon purchase of Waze Alleged Logitech game controller could turn your iPhone... Scribd launches ebook rental service Valve files 'Half-Life 3' trademark in Europe The Verge Mobile Show 064 - October 1st, 2013 Samsung again caught rigging benchmark scores on Galaxy... Regulators approve Dell's $25 billion buyout deal President Obama compares buggy new healthcare site to iOS 7 Latest 'Destiny' trailer shows an epic sci-fi battle on the... Infertile woman gives birth after new method allows her to... Season premieres of Showtime's 'Homeland' and HBO's... America offline: tracking the US government's shutdown Users report bugs, long delays on new government-run health... Future Surface tablets planned in 'multiple aspect ratios... Etsy relaxes policies, allows sellers to outsource... Quirky hires former head of Frog Design as president US government shutdown kicks NASA and other agencies off... Can a new round of NSA transparency bills make it through... Who is the mystery man behind 'The Room,' the 'Citizen Kane... Samsung brings out the puppets in its first ad for the Note... AT&amp;T tries to beat Google to Austin, launches fiber... Palo Alto will require all new homes to support electric... 'Gravity' review: try not to scream 4chan, the cesspool of the internet, turns 10 today Feeling lonely? Boot up this romance sim and meet your next... Google celebrates Yosemite's anniversary with a Doodle... 'The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug' trailer moves Bilbo... Samsung Galaxy Gear review 'Rain' on the PS3 is a haunting homage to silent French film FreedomPop launches its freemium phone service without LTE Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 review (2014 Edition) Samsung Galaxy Note 3 review Paper on paper: FiftyThree and Moleskine partner to print... Toyota doesn't see opportunity for an all-electric car Double Kickstarter failure 'Shadow of the Eternals' is put... Grand Theft Auto Online launches with early server issues Spotify now lets users follow artists and tastemakers... Your next Bang won't be With Friends GoPro debuts smaller, more wearable cameras with improved... A day at Japan's biggest tech show EU responds favorably to Google's latest antitrust proposal Google Drive makeover puts the focus on your work, not the... One ruling doesn't make Airbnb sublets legal, warns New... YouTube looks to dethrone MTV with its own music awards Obamacare's online health insurance exchanges open up as... When it comes to online rape threats, Chvrches singer won't... US government shuts down after Congress fails to agree on... Log in or join Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World Forums Back to top Search Go Previous Story Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to avoid a ruling on... Next Story LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Apple Apps Mobile Tech Netflix updates iOS app for HD streaming and AirPlay By Aaron Souppouris on October 3, 2013 02:33 am @AaronIsSocial 4 Comments Don't miss stories Follow The Verge Follow Netflix has updated its iOS app to support HD streaming and AirPlay. After noting that HD streaming was coming well over a year ago , today's update apparently brings high-quality video to iOS devices for the first time. We've been unable to get the feature working in either the UK or the US. We had similar issues with AirPlay. The update claims to enable AirPlay streaming for iOS 7, so long as you disable AirPlay mirroring. We've been unable to stream anything but audio to an Apple TV, however, and also don't see the dedicated AirPlay button within the new app as depicted in Netflix's promotional imagery. It's not clear why the new functions aren't working right now, but it could be a case of Apple offering up the app update before Netflix's web-based interface is ready. We've reached out to Netflix for clarification on the new features, and will update this article when we hear back. Source Netflix (App Store) Related Items update hd streaming iphone netflix apple ipad video on demand ios airplay hd streaming ios 7 Headlines LG could follow Samsung with curved-screen 'G Flex' phone next month Patent troll Lodsys backs out of lawsuit at last minute to avoid a ruling on its claims This video game photographer creates art out of virtual worlds Tesla stock hits a bump after burning Model S video and analyst downgrade Microsoft fires back at Yale professor who calls 'Bing It On' claims bogus Latest Media Video Silk Road, Apple TV, and Tom Clancy: 90 Seconds on The Verge about 8 hours ago 2 comments Gallery August smart lock promo photos about 13 hours ago 1 comments Video Detours: Detroit-area firefighters battle a plague of burning buildings about 14 hours ago 4 comments Gallery Dell Venue 8 Pro, Venue 11 Pro, Venue 7 and Venue 8 about 15 hours ago Gallery Dell Venue tablet lineup press pictures about 15 hours ago 1 comments Discussions Meta Guys, stop using numerical scores. 30 minutes ago by ryallen23 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Has Microsoft been neglecting the desktop and not keeping pace with competition? about 1 hour ago by MetroPedro 9 comments Science NASA To Announce Alien Life On November 13th, 2013?! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 5 comments Web &amp; Social NASA &quot;Earth Shaking&quot; Announcement Going Viral! about 2 hours ago by richieverb09 3 comments Meta I chatted with Netflix customer service just to give them a hard time. Turns out they are super helpful. about 2 hours ago by Ceveret3 2 comments Microsoft Tribe Dell Venue 8 Pro - HDMI? about 3 hours ago by debacle 1 comment Microsoft Tribe Can Surface RT Appeal to the Masses? about 3 hours ago by 1Rahtid 18 comments Microsoft Tribe Devil's Advocate on Venue 11 Pro about 3 hours ago by meelahi 8 comments Apps &amp; Software Best way to read The Verge articles on Kindle? about 4 hours ago by Soorms Googleplex I'm thinking about buying the Moto X. A few Questions... about 5 hours ago by mrusert 9 comments All Go Ethics Statement - Community Guidelines Terms of Use - Privacy Policy v1.9.1, September 30, 2013 The Sections Longform Video Reviews Tech Science Culture Design Business US &amp; World The Basics Site Status About Contact Tip Us Forums Jobs Mobile Site The Elsewhere Facebook Twitter Google+ Tumblr YouTube Instagram Subscribe Vox Media &amp;copy; 2013 Vox Media , Inc. All rights reserved. Designed in collaboration with Code and Theory . X Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more options forgot? Remember me? Log In Sign Up T F G Y O more service options or Forgot password? We'll email you a reset link. If you signed up using a 3rd party account like Facebook or Twitter, please login with it instead. Forgot password? Try another email? Almost done, Authenticating Great! Choose an available username to complete sign up. In order to provide our users with a better overall experience, we ask for more information from Facebook when using it to login so that we can learn more about our audience and provide you with the best possible experience. We do not store specific user data and the sharing of it is not required to login with Facebook. Yes, share my data Please don't share my data
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:33:40
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Netflix brings HD video and AirPlay streaming to iPhone, iPad
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.engadget.com/2013/10/03/netflix-5-ios-hd-video-airplay?ncid=txtlnkusaolp00000589
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Netflix brings HD video and AirPlay streaming to iPhone, iPad Engadget Menu News Reviews Features Galleries Videos Events Podcasts Engadget Show Topics Buyers Guides Sagas Store HD Mobile Alt Announcements Cameras Cellphones Desktops Displays Gaming GPS Handhelds Home Entertainment Household Internet Laptops Meta Misc Networking Peripherals Podcasts Robots Portable Audio/Video Science Software Storage Tablets Transportation Wearables Wireless Acer Amazon AMD Apple ASUS AT&amp;T Blackberry Canon Dell Facebook Google HP HTC Intel Lenovo LG Microsoft Nikon Nintendo Nokia NVIDIA Samsung Sony Sprint T-Mobile Verizon About Us Subscribe Like Engadget @engadget tip us Netflix brings HD video and AirPlay streaming to iPhone, iPad HD By Richard Lawler posted Oct 3rd, 2013 at 1:17 AM 0 Netflix brought 1080p streaming to Android 4.3 this summer , and now iPhone / iPad users can experience HD streams as well, provided they've updated to iOS 7. Another new feature in the latest update is support for AirPlay streaming (if you prefer that to using the Apple TV's built-in app, it also means disabling AirPlay mirroring and requires iOS 7), along with other miscellaneous fixes. Hit the link below to grab version 5.0 right away, unless you're still busy testing out the just-released Chromecast support from Hulu Plus . Source: iTunes Tags: airplay , apple , hd , hdpostcross , mobilepostcross , netflix , streaming Previous Rockstar responds to GTA Online issues, is working 'around the clock' to fix things Next Microsoft explains how it built a better Kinect, boosted accuracy without sacrificing performance (video) Sites We Like Tech Apple News gdgt Boing Boing Slashdot MAKE Ars Technica TechMeme Phone Scoop Design FFFFOUND! Core77 Popcorn Shower MoCo Loco Design*Sponge The Sartorialist News HuffPost Politics The Daily Beast Huffington Post Tech News Business News Investing News Lifestyle Lifehacker HuffPost Women Stylelist Automotive Translogic Gadling Environmental Inhabitat Good Autoblog Green Huffpost Green Entertainment Joystiq Massively The Onion i09 HuffPost Celebrity Spinner Moviefone About Us Subscribe via RSS Like Engadget on Facebook @engadget on Twitter Español 繁體中文 简体中文 日本版 Deutschland Joystiq Stealth Inc bringing its sneaky platforming to iOS All nominated IndieCade games offered Desura distribution and promotion Namco Bandai trademarks 'Soulcalibur: Unbreakable Soul' Tuaw Daily Deals for October 2, 2013, featuring the Call of Duty Bundle for Mac In contrast to Android OEMs, Apple and Motorola don't fudge their benchmarking results eleMount iPhone/iPad mount Kickstarts its way into production TechCrunch Cue, The Startup Formerly Known As Greplin, Shuts Down Its App Quantopian, A Community Of Quants, Picks Up $6.7M From Khosla, Spark Penn Jillette Turns To FundAnything To Become A Bad Guy HuffPost Tech A TALE OF TWO FACEBOOKS Here's The Seemingly Ordinary Man Who Ran The Internet's Biggest Black Market MORE : FBI Shutters 'Silk Road' AOL Tech. &amp;copy; 2013 AOL Inc. All rights reserved. Reprints and Permissions Privacy Policy Terms of Use Trademarks AOL A-Z Help Advertise with Us
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:15:18
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Tech News Headlines - Yahoo! News
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://news.yahoo.com/calif-man-charged-black-market-drug-scheme-060819404--finance.html
      </link>
      <author>
        None
      </author>
      <content>
        Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme - Yahoo News Home Mail News Sports Finance Weather Games Groups Answers Screen Flickr More omg! Shine Movies Music TV Health Shopping Travel Autos Homes Mobile Yahoo News Search News Search Web Sign In Mail Go to Mail.&quot; data-nosubject=&quot;[No Subject]&quot; data-timestamp='short'&gt; Help Account Info Help Suggestions Yahoo News Home U.S. World Politics Tech Science Health Odd News Opinion Local Dear Abby Comics ABC News Yahoo Originals Calif. man charged in black market drug scheme Content preferences Done PAUL ELIAS 12 minutes ago SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — FBI agents found him in the science fiction section of a small branch of the San Francisco public library, chatting online. The man known as Dread Pirate Roberts — 29-year-old Ross William Ulbricht — was on his personal laptop Tuesday afternoon, authorities said, talking about the vast black market bazaar that is believed to have brokered more than $1 billion in transactions for illegal drugs and services. When a half-dozen FBI agents burst into the library in a quiet, blue collar neighborhood they abruptly ended Ulbricht's conversation with a cooperating witness, pinned the Austin, Texas, native to a floor-to-ceiling window and then took him off to jail, law enforcement and library spokeswomen said. Ulbricht was later charged in criminal complaints in federal courts in New York and Maryland. He's accused of making millions of dollars operating the secret Silk Road website and of a failed murder-for-hire scheme, all while living anonymously with two roommates whom he paid $1,000 to rent a room in a modest neighborhood. Federal authorities shut down the website. Ulbricht has not entered pleas to any of his charges. His federal public defender in San Francisco declined comment Wednesday. Ulbricht is due back in San Francisco federal court Friday morning to discuss bail and his transfer to New York, where the bulk of the charges have been filed. He is charged in New York with being the mastermind of Silk Road, where users could browse anonymously through nearly 13,000 listings under categories like &quot;Cannabis,&quot; ''Psychedelics&quot; and &quot;Stimulants.&quot; Ulbricht also is charged in Maryland with ordering first the torture, and then the murder, of an employee from an undercover agent. He feared the employee would expose his alias as Dread Pirate Roberts, a fictional character. Court records say he wired the agent $80,000 after he was shown staged photos of the employee's faked torture. His arrest culminated a two-year-investigation that painstakingly followed a small trail of computer crumbs Ulbricht carelessly left for the FBI to find, according to court documents. Ulbricht first came to the attention of federal agents in 2011 when they figured out he was &quot;altoid,&quot; someone who they say was marketing Silk Road on other drug-related websites the FBI was watching. In October 2011, &quot;altoid&quot; posted an advertisement for a computer expert with experience in Bitcoin, an electronic currency, and gave an email address. From there, investigators began to monitor Ulbricht's online behavior closely, according to the court records. Investigators said Ulbricht was living within 500 feet of a San Francisco Internet cafe on June 3, 2013 when someone &quot;logged into a server used to administer the Silk Road website.&quot; Court documents show investigators slowly connected Ulbricht to Silk Road by monitoring his email and picking up on some slipups, including using his real name to ask a programmers' website a highly technical question about connecting to secret sites like Silk Road. His final mistake, according to the court papers, was ordering fake identification documents from a Silk Road vendor from Canada. One of the nine documents was a California driver's license with Ulbricht's photograph, birthdate but a different name. The package was intercepted at the border during a routine U.S. Customs search. On July 26, Homeland Security investigators visited Ulbricht at his San Francisco residence. He &quot;generally refused to answer questions,&quot; the agents said. The investigators left that day without arresting Ulbricht, who holds a bachelor's of science degree in physics from the University of Texas at Dallas and a master's degree from Penn State. They returned Tuesday and arrested him at the library. He faces the prospect of life in prison if convicted of all the charges. The Silk Road website protected users with an encryption technique called &quot;onion routing,&quot; which is designed to make it &quot;practically impossible to physically locate the computers hosting or accessing websites on the network,&quot; court papers said. One listing for heroin promised buyers &quot;all rock, no powder, vacuum sealed and stealth shipping,&quot; and had a community forum below where one person commented, &quot;Quality is superb.&quot; The defendant announced in a website forum in 2012 that to avoid confusion he needed to change his Silk Road username, according to court papers released Wednesday. He wrote, &quot;drum roll please ... my new name is: Dread Pirate Roberts,&quot; an apparent reference to a swashbuckling character in &quot;The Princess Bride,&quot; the 1987 comedy film based on a novel of the same name. As of July, there were nearly 1 million registered users of the site from the United States, Germany, Russia, Australia and elsewhere around the globe, the court papers said. The site generated an estimated $1.2 billion since it started in 2011 and collected $80 million by charging 8 to 15 percent commission on each sale, they said. ___ Associated Press writer Tom Hays and AP researcher Barbara Sambriski in New York contributed to this report. Crime &amp; Justice Society &amp; Culture Dread Pirate Roberts San Francisco Click to view comments View Comments Share this Recommended for You Obama stressed to congressional leaders he will not negotiate over shutdown, debt limit WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Barack Obama stressed to congressional leaders on Wednesday in White House talks that he will not negotiate with Republicans over a government shutdown or raising the U.S. debt limit, the White House said. After more than an hour of talks that did not lead to a… Reuters Save More like this Remove Rouhani: Iran to discuss nuke details, not rights TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — President Hassan Rouhani said Wednesday that Iran is open to discussing &amp;quot;details&amp;quot; of nuclear activities including the enrichment of uranium, hinting that the Islamic Republic is willing to broaden the terms of negotiations with world powers. He spoke shortly after receiving… Associated Press Save More like this Remove Stream TV Shows and Movies Anywhere Any Time Take Netflix anywhere you go. Unlimited streaming from your favorite device for only $7.99/month. AdChoices Netflix Sponsored Suspect arraigned in motorcycle-SUV brawl in NYC NEW YORK (AP) — A motorcyclist was charged Wednesday with reckless driving after prosecutors said he touched off a tense encounter with the driver of an SUV and a throng of other bikers that ended with blood and broken bones on a Manhattan street. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Mia Farrow: &amp;#39;Possible&amp;#39; son is Sinatra&amp;#39;s NEW YORK (AP) — Mia Farrow says in an interview with Vanity Fair that it&amp;#39;s possible her son with Woody Allen is instead Frank Sinatra&amp;#39;s. Associated Press Save More like this Remove China&amp;#39;s Xi sidesteps SE Asia pressure over South China Sea disputes By Kanupriya Kapoor JAKARTA (Reuters) - Chinese President Xi Jinping showed no sign of bending to Southeast Asian pressure to resolve increasingly irascible territorial disputes over the South China Sea on Thursday, simply repeating past calls for dialogue. Xi, in the first address by a foreign… Reuters 44 mins ago Save More like this Remove Wife: Biker husband is victim in NYC altercation NEW YORK (AP) — Shaky camera footage depicts the gory scene: A driver who police say was frightened when a group of motorcyclists swarmed his Range Rover plowed through them, striking a rider in a purple T-shirt and black helmet. Associated Press Save More like this Remove EPIC FAIL: Los Angeles high schools now confiscate all free iPads they gave students Hilariously, officials at high schools in the Los Angeles Unified School District are now taking back a couple thousand iPads a week or so after giving them to students as part of a 47-school pilot program. The Daily Caller Save More like this Remove The Hidden Costs of &amp;#39;Affordable&amp;#39; Health Insurance Plans The Affordable Care Act promises to expand access to health care by providing affordable coverage to millions of Americans. But finding a policy that meets your health care needs and your budget requirements can be daunting. U.S.News &amp; World Report LP Save More like this Remove Play Hundreds of Students Involved in Violent Hazing Incident More than one hundred students at a Seattle high school were caught taking part in a dangerous hazing incident. Tribune Save More like this Remove With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) recently released this stunning photo of an estimated 10,000 walruses crammed onto a tiny Alaskan beach. The Sideshow Save More like this Remove Dazzling Bayern Munich can improve, warns Guardiola Manchester (United Kingdom) (AFP) - Manager Pep Guardiola watched his Bayern Munich team outclass Manchester City 3-1 and then warned the rest of Europe that the Champions League holders can get even better. AFP Save More like this Remove Video reveals final design of Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia Madrid (AFP) - It has been under construction for more than 130 years and there is another 13 to go, but the world has been given a glimpse of what Barcelona&amp;#39;s Sagrada Familia will look like when finally completed. AFP Save More like this Remove Play Government shutdown affecting DHHS services Some parents could soon be without healthy food options if the governement shutown lingers. WTVD – Raleigh/Durham Save More like this Remove Tesla Says Car Fire Began in Battery APNewsBreak: Tesla Model S car fire began in battery; stock falls after video goes online         ABC News Save More like this Remove Auto Dealers Cut Prices on New Cars &amp;amp; Trucks Local auto dealers are cutting their prices on all vehicle types. If you're looking for a new car this month, buy now and save as much as ... AdChoices Auto-Price-Finder.com Sponsored House Dems offer immigration bill, fate uncertain WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Wednesday unveiled an immigration bill that provides a path to citizenship for the 11 million immigrants living here illegally and tightens border security, and they warned of political fallout if House Republicans fail to act. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Shutdown Hampers Search for Missing Woman in Idaho National Park Ten Park Service rangers furloughed as a result of the government shutdown are volunteering their time to scour a national park in Idaho for a missing physician, whose search has been complicated by federal closures. Jo Elliott-Blakeslee, 63, was last seen in Craters of the... ABC News Save More like this Remove South Carolina drops extradition order for Baby Veronica&amp;#39;s biological father By Brendan O&amp;#39;Brien (Reuters) - The biological father of &amp;quot;Baby Veronica,&amp;quot; a Native American girl who was at the heart of a protracted custody battle, will not be extradited to South Carolina to face felony charges for interfering with her adoption, Oklahoma Governor Mary Fallin said on Wednesday.… Reuters Save More like this Remove 22 dogs will get lucky on new CBS television show LOS ANGELES (AP) — Brandon McMillan has trained as many as 10,000 dogs for television, movies, commercials, videos and people. Then he started saving dogs from animal shelters, training them and finding homes for them. Associated Press Save More like this Remove iPhone 5s Review: A Great Phone With Some More Forward Thinking Needed Is Apple&amp;#39;s Latest Really the &amp;#39;Forward Thinking&amp;#39; Phone it Promises? Good Morning America Save More like this Remove LA Coroner&amp;#39;s office IDing 4 bodies found in jet LOS ANGELES (AP) — Just as he had so many times before, Mark Benjamin rode his small jet from a town in the Idaho wilderness he loved to the Southern California airport he knew so well. Associated Press Save More like this Remove Load more stories Top Stories Meeting yields no breakthrough in shutdown Service academy football games will go on Tesla car fire involved battery pack Latest Videos Obama: Shutdown Result of Ideological Crusade 01:34 Vets Cross Barricades Despite Shutdown 01:15 Shutdown Ripple Effect Felt Across Country 00:02 Government shutdown: 15,000 FAA employees furloughed 01:59 Obama cancels stops on overseas trip in wake of shutdown 01:55 Latest Slideshows Sectarian violence between Rohingyas and Buddhists Photos of the day - October 2, 2013 In the wild photo competition Government shutdown begins US-Mexico border helicopter patrol continues through &amp;hellip; Yahoo News Originals Lottery Luck: Learn the recipe for winning the lottery (Video) Shutdown stories: How congressional quarreling is affecting us Veterans swarm ‘closed’ WWII memorial, knock politicians Awesome Magic Trick Prank Gives Pizza Deliverymen Surprise Tips Our Very Own Lip Sync Battle - Vote Now! Skeletons get hungry, too The biggest complaints about iOS 7 so far Obama, lawmakers huddle but no shutdown breakthrough The Last Word on...the Kindle Fire HDX With sea ice disappearing, thousands of walruses cram an Alaskan beach Copyright 2013 The Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten or redistributed. Yahoo - ABC News Network Help / Suggestions Privacy About Our Ads Terms
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 07:14:42
      </updated_at>
    </item>
  </body>
</opml>
