<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<opml version="1.0">
  <!--Generated by FeedDigger-->
  <head>
    <title>
      grep last 15 minutes 201310030719
    </title>
    <dateCreated>
      2013-10-03 07:19:46.522724
    </dateCreated>
    <dateModified>
      2013-10-03 07:19:46.522724
    </dateModified>
  </head>
  <body>
    <item>
      <title>
        Who Is Ross Ulbricht? Piecing Together The Life Of The Alleged Libertarian Mastermind Behind Silk Road
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Forbes Real Time
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanmac/2013/10/02/who-is-ross-ulbricht-piecing-together-the-life-of-the-alleged-libertarian-mastermind-behind-silk-road/
      </link>
      <author>
        Ryan Mac, Forbes Staff
      </author>
      <content>
        Who Is Ross Ulbricht? Piecing Together The Life Of The Alleged Libertarian Mastermind Behind Silk Road - Forbes Log in with your social account: Or, you can log in or sign up using Forbes. New Posts Most Popular Hip-Hop's Top Earners Lists The Forbes 400 Video America's Richest Women The ONE Stock to Buy in October Help | Connect | Sign up | Log in Ryan Mac , Forbes Staff I cover the world's billionaires for the rest of the 99.9999999%. Follow Following Unfollow Lists | 10/02/2013 @ 5:56PM | 43,347 views Who Is Ross Ulbricht? Piecing Together The Life Of The Alleged Libertarian Mastermind Behind Silk Road 11 comments, 8 called-out Comment Now Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Comment Now Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Ross William Ulbricht, 29, was arrested on Tuesday and is alleged to be the &amp;quot;Dread Pirate Roberts&amp;quot; behind Silk Road's drug black market. (Photo: LinkedIn) If you ask his family members, Ross William Ulbricht did not seem like a criminal mastermind. “He’s an exceptionally bright and smart kid,” said his half-brother Travis Ulbricht. “He’s always been upstanding and never had any trouble with the law that I knew of.” But according to the FBI, Ross Ulbricht is the owner and manager of the Silk Road, an anonymous narcotics marketplace that has been responsible for over $1.2 billion in transactions since early 2011. On Tuesday afternoon, the FBI arrested Ulbricht at a San Francisco public library. The 29-year-old now faces charges of money laundering, narcotics trafficking conspiracy and computer hacking. A criminal complaint filed in the Southern District of New York portrays Ulbricht as a notorious criminal who knowingly violated the law by cultivating an anonymous online drug bazaar and soliciting the murder of a person who threatened to reveal site users. Calling himself the “Dread Pirate Roberts,” the complaint alleges Ulbricht generated more than $80 million in commissions from running the site, which was shut down by the FBI as of Wednesday. In August, FORBES interviewed the Dread Pirate Roberts in an exclusive interview via a completely anonymous online chat after he refused to meet in person. Back then he wouldn’t reveal his full name or even nationality, stating that “the highest levels of government are hunting me.” “I don’t meet in person even with my closest advisors,” the Dread Pirate said at the time. According to interviews with his family members, however, Ulbricht did meet with relatives, who had no idea of his alleged illegal online activities. Half-brother Travis mentions meeting with and talking with Ulbricht “a few weeks ago” in the San Francisco area, while his parents also visited him in California after making the trip from Texas. “This is somewhat shocking and the first I’ve heard of it,” said Travis Ulbricht when contacted for comment on the arrest. “I really don’t know anything about Silk Road … I know it’s part of the underweb essentially.” In an interview with technology news site, The Verge , close friend Ren&amp;eacute; Pinnell, who lived with Ulbricht in San Francisco, was in disbelief that his roommate could have been the notorious drug kingpin named after a masked protagonist from fantasy film, The Princess Bride. He said he thought Ulbricht was trading the anonymous currency Bitcoin to make a living. “I don’t know how they messed it up and I don’t know how they got Ross wrapped into this, but I’m sure it’s not him,” Pinnell said. A Texas native who moved to San Francisco in the fall of 2012, Ulbricht listed himself as an “investment adviser and entrepreneur” on his LinkedIn page , though there is no mention of current employment. He attended the University of Texas at Dallas, where relatives say he was on full scholarship and studied physics. From there, he went on to be a graduate research assistant at Penn State University, earning his Master’s Degree in Materials Science and Engineering with a thesis entitled “Growth of EuO Thin Films By Molecular Beam Epitaxy.” While at Penn State, Ulbricht was also politically active. A member of the school’s College Libertarians group, he took part in on-campus debates that were documented by the school’s newspaper, The Daily Collegian. In one article from March 2008, Ulbricht is identified as a supporter of Ron Paul who had attempted to become a delegate for the then-presidential candidate at the Republican National Convention. “There’s a lot to learn from him and his message of what it means to be a U.S. citizen and what it means to be a free individual,” he told the school paper. “He doesn’t compromise his integrity as a politician and he fights quite diligently to restore the principles that our country was founded on.” In Silk Road’s community forums , the Dread Pirate Roberts always made the libertarian underpinnings of his organization clear. In Oct. 2012, he noted in a post: “Silk Road was founded on libertarian principles and continues to be operated on them … The same principles that have allowed Silk Road to flourish can and do work anywhere human beings come together. The only difference is that the State is unable to get its thieving murderous mitts on it.” He called Paul “a mighty hero in my book” in a note from Nov. 2012. After leaving Penn State in 2010, Ulbricht mentioned on his LinkedIn page that his “goals have shifted” and that he was moving away from his physics education and toward the study and use of economic theory to “abolish the use of coercion and aggression against mankind.” Move up http://i.forbesimg.com t Move down Meet The Dread Pirate Roberts, The Man Behind Booming Black Market Drug Website Silk Road Andy Greenberg Forbes Staff End Of The Silk Road: FBI Says It's Busted The Web's Biggest Anonymous Drug Black Market Andy Greenberg Forbes Staff Feds Say They've Arrested 'Dread Pirate Roberts,' Shut Down His Black Market 'The Silk Road' Alex Konrad Forbes Staff Feds Allege Silk Road's Boss Paid For Murders Of Both A Witness And A Blackmailer Andy Greenberg Forbes Staff Page 1 2 « Previous Page Next Page » 11 comments, 8 called-out Comment Now Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Comment Now Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Print Report Corrections Reprints &amp;amp; Permissions Post Your Comment Cancel reply Post Your Reply Please log in or sign up to comment. Enter Your Comment Submit Comment Forbes writers have the ability to call out member comments they find particularly interesting. Called-out comments are highlighted across the Forbes network. You'll be notified if your comment is called out. Comments Called-Out Expand All Comments Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Nishi Hundan 7 hours ago Bwhahahahahahaha…what a loser Permalink Flag Reply Ethan Crispo 7 hours ago I’m truly amazing at the amount of money involved here. The man had a great idea and made a lot of money. Let’s all keep in mind the fact that he never even touched the drugs. Should Ebay’s creator be arrested for the illegal things that have been sold on the site? I think not. Permalink Flag Reply Ryan Mac , Forbes Staff 6 hours ago I’m not so sure about the idea that the Dread Pirate Roberts never touched the drugs. The Dread Pirate Roberts told my colleague Andy Greenberg that he enjoyed smoking “a bowl of sticky indica buds at the end of a long day” in an interview. See here: http://www.forbes.com/sites/andygreenberg/2013/08/14/meet-the-dread-pirate-roberts-the-man-behind-booming-black-market-drug-website-silk-road/2/ I agree that $1.2 billion in transactions over a 2.5 year period is quite astonishing. Permalink Flag Reply Bryan Laurie 5 hours ago “a bowl of sticky indica buds at the end of a long day” Who gives a s***? Practically everyone over the age of 12 smokes bud in California, hell, pretty much anywhere but that doesn’t mean he had his hands on the merchandise as Mac was saying. Way to miss the point. Moron. Plus that’s not even how SR worked, do some actual research if you’re going to write about something. Permalink Flag Reply Elz Ferreira 19 minutes ago Uh, he conspired with someone (really, an undercover agent) to have another person killed. He wired money to the undercover agent twice for this execution that he thought had really happened, and discussed the murder over several messages with the agent and asked for visual proof. He also seems to have conspired with another person for another murder. They also caught him on money laundering and on computer intrusion. The undercover agent also trapped him by asking him for help in finding a way to unload large amounts of drugs – thus, gathering evidence that Ulbricht knew that the site was a traffic center for drug deals. They were watching him for a while, trapped him, and assembled a bunch of charges against him. And he fell for the whole thing. This not about smoking a little pot. Permalink Flag Reply Nathan Merrill 19 minutes ago Laundering money is a big-time crime. He probably also engaged in tax evasion, knowing such folk. He also was complicit in illegal activities, tried to arrange two hits (badly, as it turns out), and of course was an accessory in drug dealing. Dude did a lot of bad things. I hope he likes jail. Permalink Flag Reply David Sutherland 6 hours ago The anonymity issue seems tricky. Will the government have clear enough evidence that DPR is actually Ulbricht? Something to prevent him from claiming he was a low level programmer there? Permalink Flag Reply Nathan Merrill 20 minutes ago They got his computer after he logged in with his password. Anything he had on there is accessible to them. Permalink Flag Reply Elz Ferreira 13 minutes ago Uh, he used his actual email address all over the place, including on a post that mentioned the Silk Road. He made social media profiles of himself all over the place, with clear photos of himself, and with posts about how he was working on a new economy, etc. He posted programming questions online about Tor, etc. And the Feds actually got a hold of someone else first that led them to him, and used this to spring their trap. Uh, yeah, the government will have enough clear evidence. He also logged on at a cafe in S.F. and logged into his administrator account while using the wi-fi. Permalink Flag Reply Max 9 minutes ago Thank you Forbes for covering such a unique, historical, event. I will take this opportunity to discourage the public from scapegoating us Libertarians for being drug addicts. Instead, we will take this opportunity to note that the United States of America was founded on freedom. DPR successfully exploited our unacceptable state of the union. This is a country of freedom. Its your choice to shoot up heroine or to create the next Apple inc. Government has been manipulated to provide to those who cant take care of themselves. And its spreading like a disease. In turn government “gets in the way” of entrepreneurs like DPR and dare I say myself. (I am a director of photography, not Heisenberg) Case and point. DPR is in custody at this current moment. He is an entrepreneur and one helluva successful one. You think Facebook is hot.. End this worthless and expensive drug war, and foster actual businesses like the Silk Road. USA, take yer taxes from it. You are currently loosing. (ahem, government shutdown, multiple wars, and this unacceptable deficit!?) America, we are failing. Its a crime itself that we have elected officials to tell us what to do with our lives and bodies. It is the last thing the writers of the Constitution intended. Lets get back to basics. I encourage you to educate yourself in your local, state, and federal politics. // GO VOTE Permalink Flag Reply Max 1 minute ago Looking forward to the progression of this historical case. Keep me updated. Thank you. Permalink Flag Reply Follow Comments Following Comments Unfollow Comments Most Read on Forbes News People Places Companies + show more Ryan Mac Forbes Staff Follow Following Unfollow + show more I'm a San Francisco-based reporter and a member of Forbes' wealth team. I track some of the 1,426 (and counting) billionaires across the world and report on how they make and spend their money. I've worked at a number of publications including The New York Times, Bloomberg News, The Bay Citizen, The Orange County Register and the Half Moon Bay Review. I got my first fix for news as a reporter at The Stanford Daily and haven't looked back since. I work with Kerry Dolan, Luisa Kroll and a team of reporters to bring you the Forbes World's Billionaires list and the Forbes 400 Richest Americans list. My other interests include tech and music. Follow me on twitter @RMac18 and feel free to send story ideas or tips to RMac[at]forbes[dot]com. Ryan Mac&amp;#8217;s Popular Posts The Mad Billionaire Behind GoPro: The World's Hottest Camera Company 218,420 views Mark Zuckerberg's Good Week Gets Better After He Marries Longtime Girlfriend 192,752 views Professor Billionaire: The Stanford Academic Who Wrote Google Its First Check 150,020 views Ten Lessons from Peter Thiel's Class On Startups 119,616 views No One Is More Excited For Google Glass Than Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg 92,092 views More from Ryan Mac Follow Ryan Mac on Twitter Ryan Mac&amp;#8217;s RSS Feed Ryan Mac&amp;#8217;s Profile Ryan Mac&amp;#8217;s Website Inside Forbes FORBES 400: The Ranking Of America's Richest People The average net worth of America's 400 richest rose $800 million to a record $5 billion Baseball Postseason Ratings Could Flop, Does It Matter? Shutdown: 9M Moms At Risk As WIC Program Halts see photos The Cities Most At Risk To A Government Shutdown Real-Time Billionaires Channels Business Investing Technology Entrepreneurs Op/Ed Leadership Lifestyle Lists Company Info Forbes Careers Advertising Information Forbes Press Room Forbes Newsfeeds Investment Newsletters Reprints &amp;amp; Permissions Terms and Conditions Privacy Statement Contact Us Sitemap Help Affiliate Sites Forbes China Forbes India Forbes Israel Forbes Mexico Forbes Middle East Forbes Poland Forbes Romania Forbes Russia Forbes Ukraine RealClear Politics RealClear Markets RealClear World RealClear Sports Forbes Conferences Forbes Asia’s Power Business Women Forbes Women’s Summit Forbes 400 Philanthropy Summit Global CEO Conference Forbes Healthcare Summit Forbes CMO Summit Forbes Asia's Best Under A Billion Techonomy Forbes Innovators Forbes and NAPFA Advisor iConference Forbes Reinventing America Summit Publications Free Trial Issue Subscriber Services Buy Back Issues Data Partners Market Data by Morningstar Thomson Reuters AdChoices 2013 Forbes.com LLC&amp;#153; All Rights Reserved
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:12:16
      </updated_at>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech
      </title>
      <feed_title>
        Technology news, comment and analysis | theguardian.com
      </feed_title>
      <link>
        http://feeds.theguardian.com/c/34708/f/663871/s/31ff5f48/sc/21/l/0L0Stheguardian0N0Ctechnology0C20A130Coct0C0A30Calgorithims0Egoogle0Einternet0Esearch0Esecurity0Eonlin/story01.htm
      </link>
      <author>
        Alex Hern
      </author>
      <content>
        From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech | Technology | theguardian.com Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to comments [c] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life &amp;amp; style Data News Technology Programming From search to security: the five most important algorithms in tech Algorithms such as those run by Google are the brains of the internet, encrypting data and helping us navigate online Share Tweet this Email Alex Hern theguardian.com , Thursday 3 October 2013 03.05 EDT Jump to comments ( &amp;hellip; ) Algorithms power music discovery, encrypt our personal information and help us navigate through online worlds. Photograph: Google Algorithms, simple functions that hover between mathematical problems and computer programs, are everywhere. Whether dealing with lost packets when using Wi-Fi, or getting your credit-card details securely to an online store, most consumer technology couldn't work without some ingenious solutions to common problems. And when Google decides to change its search algorithm - as it did with Hummingbird last week, it can make or break whole companies . Here are just five which you couldn't live without. Pagerank &amp;ndash; how Google calculates search results The broad strokes of how Google's search algorithm works have been public for over fifteen years, though the exact way it organises search results remains the company's most closely guarded secret. PageRank is the system at the heart of it all, and the key invention behind Google's rapid dominance of internet search. Ten years ago, when competitors relied on human-maintained indexes of webpages, it allowed the company to assess the value of websites automatically - a massive advantage as the web grew exponentially. The algorithm works by looking at every link to and from every page on the internet. A link to a page is, in effect, a vote for that page's validity, because it means that someone thought that whatever was on that page was worth sharing. So the more inbound links a page has, the higher its PageRank is. But then it adds a second measure: links from pages which have a high PageRank themselves confer a higher PageRank. So being linked to by Stanford , the Google creators' alma mater, is significantly more valuable than being linked to by Stanford's , the map shop. On top of PageRank are myriad tweaks and adjustments to improve the results further. Some of those, such as the decision to punish 'link farms', vast networks of sites which link to each other in an effort to boost their PageRank , are directly connected to the core algorithm. Others, like the company's attempts to leverage what it knows about users based on their previous searches to deliver personalised results, were bolted on later. But as the demands we make of search have got ever more intensive, the company has been forced to adapt. The most recent update to the algorithm, Hummingbird is &quot;a new engine built on both existing and new parts&quot;, according to Danny Sullivan of the search blog Search Engine Land . Hummingbird was built to deal with the fact that increasing familiarity with search, as well as the rise of voice control , mean that we now ask Google actual questions, rather than just typing in relevant words. In the future, new problems will require further tweaks, but the position of PageRank at the heart of it all seems secure. Two Enigma machines at the London Science Museum. Photograph: DAVID HOLT/flickr Public key cryptography - keeping credit card data secure Public key cryptography is the name for a broad collection of algorithms which lie at the heart of nearly every form of security online. Using what is perhaps best described as 'magic maths ', public key cryptography lets people encode data with a key which cannot then decode it. If Alice has a piece of information which she needs to get to Bob without anyone else seeing it &amp;ndash; maybe a credit card number which she's using to buy a computer with, or perhaps evidence of state wrongdoing which she's leaking to a national newspaper &amp;ndash; she has to encrypt it. Way back in history, the only way to do this would be to use a shared secret: a cipher which both Alice and Bob know, but no-one else does. That's how encryption all the way up to the second world war worked. But the obvious problem is that Alice and Bob can't use open channels to agree on their cipher. That's fine if they can meet in person to swap codes, but less effective if Alice is a consumer and Bob a multinational corporation. Public key cryptography means that Bob can tell the world his public key, and let them know that anything encoded with that will be readable by him and only him. Alice sees the public key, locks up her credit card data using it, and then sends that packet on the way. Only Bob, using a second, private, key can decrypt the data and read the number. Unfortunately, doing all of this every time is pretty hard on a computer's processor, so another step, where both Alice and Bob use their keys together to generate a shared secret, is frequently added in most practical uses of public key encryption. That shared secret can then be used in old-fashioned symmetrical ciphers. But it all comes back to the public and private keys. Correcting errors CDs are temperamental beasts. When they were introduced, they were hailed as being a resilient replacement for vinyl and cassettes, but as anyone who has tried to play a carelessly preserved album found in their car's glovebox can attest to, that's only half true. Still, it could a lot worse. When you're storing data using microscopic pits on a sheet of metal covered with a thin layer of plastic, it's quite a feat to read every single pit correctly, a feat only compounded by later generations of optical media, which shrink the pits still further. Playback. Photograph: Stockdisc/Getty Images Error correction lies at the heart of that reliability, thanks to the use of a cunning algorithm which lets CDs be readable even with quite a lot of damage to the data stored on them. In hugely simplified form, imagine the data on a CD as a grid of 1s and 0s. Like this: 101 010 000 If there's an error reading the CD, one of those 0s may turn into a 1. Without error correction, there's no way to tell if that's happened, and no way to fix it. The simplest way to correct errors is to add another load of data. Each row and column is counted up, and if there's an even number of 1s, another 1 is added on the end. If there isn't, a 0 is added instead: 101 1 010 0 000 1 000 Now, if one of the 0s is misread, the player can check with the error correction codes, and tell that there's been a mistake &amp;ndash; and even, assuming there's not too much damage, what the real value should be. Suppose the bottom right 0 is read as a 1: by reading the error correction code for that row, the player can tell that there's one too many 1s. It can then cross-check with the error correction codes for each column, and spot that there are also too many 1s in one column as well. Now the player knows where the error is, and can carry on with those sweet tunes. Error correction isn't just used by disc drives, though. Nearly every electronic device which gets data from one place to another will have some error correction on it, from WiFi to DSL. Even ISBN numbers on the back of books have error correction: the final digit serves the role. Protecting passwords Sometimes, it's really important to check that the file you have been given is exactly the one you expected. Maybe you are worried it's been tampered with, or just want to check that a large download finished without corruption. One way to do that is to look at its hash. There isn't really one algorithm which can be used to make 'hashes' of data: any process which can take information and spit out something which fulfils a few criteria will do. A good cryptographic hash function will give the same output every time it's given the same input; the hash will change if the message changes; it would be nearly impossible to work backwards from the hash to the message; and it would be nearly impossible for two messages to have the same hashes. Logging in. Photograph: Jan Miks/Alamy But there's a much more important use for hashing data than just checking files: password protection. As is painfully obvious these days, not many organisations can guarantee they won't lose your data . That's particularly problematic if it's your password they've lost, because &amp;mdash; well, you don't have a different password for every service, do you ? These days, companies shouldn't be keeping passwords in plaintext at all. Instead, when a user types in their password for the first time, the site should hash the password, and only keep that. Every time they come back to log in, it can take another hash, and compare it to the one on file. If they match, the password's correct. But now, if the site's hacked, the only thing which gets lost is a table full of hashes which can't be reverse engineered into passwords, so everyone is happy. (Technically, site owners should be salting their hashes - an oh-so-cute term which means adding a little bit of extra data into the password hash to prevent it being reverse engineered .) Perlin noise: generating landscapes in games Games are just big bags of algorithms. There's art, music, writing, direction, design and playtesting too, but a lot of algorithms. Take procedurally generated terrain, the favoured way of filling in the vast expanses of games like Minecraft or Dwarf Fortress. It's not enough just to generate random noise, and apply it to a landscape, because if you do, you end up with something which is too random: all noise, no pattern. Instead, you want terrain which demonstrates the same fractal nature as the real world, with mountains, hills, boulders and pebbles all having effects on different scales. That's what Perlin noise can do. It's a simple enough algorithm: generate some random noise at a load of different frequencies, smooth it out, and then add them together . But when you do, you go from this: Random noise. Photograph: /http:/freespace.virgin.net/hugo.elias/models/m_perlin.htm To this: Perlin noise Photograph: /http:/freespace.virgin.net/hugo.elias/models/m_perlin.htm Or consider trying to get enemies to take an intelligent route through a map. The obvious way to do it is easy enough: consider every possible route, then take the shortest one from A to B. But that's so computationally intensive that it's unusable in most situations. Instead algorithms like the A* search can be used. How it works is tricky to explain (essentially, it finds a path by always taking the step where the number of steps already taken plus the number of steps in a straight line to the destination is lowest), but it is entrancing in action . &amp;bull; In August 2011, a rogue algorithm lost its owners $440m on the stock market before it was eventually shut down . Sign up for the Guardian Today Our editors' picks for the day's top news and commentary delivered to your inbox each morning. Sign up for the daily email Print this Share Contact us Send to a friend Sender&amp;#39;s name Recipient's email address Your IP address will be logged Share Short link for this page: http://gu.com/p/3j6mf StumbleUpon reddit Tumblr Digg LinkedIn Google Bookmarks del.icio.us livejournal Facebook Twitter Contact us Contact the Technology editor tech@theguardian.com Report errors or inaccuracies: userhelp@theguardian.com Letters for publication should be sent to: letters@theguardian.com If you need help using the site: userhelp@theguardian.com Call the main Guardian and Observer switchboard: +44 (0)20 3353 2000 Advertising guide License/buy our content Technology Programming &amp;middot; Search engines &amp;middot; Internet &amp;middot; Data and computer security &amp;middot; Google &amp;middot; Games Search World news Privacy More blogposts Share Tweet this Email Comments Click here to join the discussion . We can't load the discussion on theguardian.com because you don't have JavaScript enabled . Today's best video Tiger cub born at London Zoo The moment a tiger gives birth to London Zoo's first tiger cub in 17 years is captured by hidden cameras Does the future belong to the Tories? John Harris reports from the Conservative party conference Plane's emergency landing on Florida road A pilot is forced to land his plane on a road Mesut Özil lauded by Arsène Wenger Arsenal manager praises midfielder after 2-0 Champions League win over Napoli Technology Programming &amp;middot; Search engines &amp;middot; Internet &amp;middot; Data and computer security &amp;middot; Google &amp;middot; Games Search World news Privacy More blogposts On the Guardian today World news 'Revenge porn' outlawed in California Technology GTA V Online launches, popularity could cause server issues Technology Rockstar says sorry for Grand Theft Auto Online launch problems Film Mia Farrow: Woody Allen's son Ronan may be Frank Sinatra's World news US shutdown: fruitless talks leave bitter stalemate in place Technology FBI claims largest Bitcoin seizure after arrest of alleged Silk Road founder Sponsored feature Key topics Apple Google Facebook Games blog Game reviews License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US advertising | A - Z index | About us &amp;#169; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) ;
      </content>
      <updated_at>
        2013-10-03 08:05:30
      </updated_at>
    </item>
  </body>
</opml>
